Chapter 2133: Shi Zong's Tribulation

Fang Yuan was secretly observing his subordinates' reactions.

He had issued the exchange list after careful consideration.

Previously, Fang Yuan had thought the sovereign immortal aperture's chaotic phenomena would pass with time. But they were instead becoming more severe.

Sometimes, some strange situations occurred, which were so serious that Fang Yuan's main body had to deal with them.

If he could increase the strength of the sovereign immortal aperture's Gu Immortals by a level or two, the chaotic state of the sovereign immortal aperture would be dealt with much more properly.

Fang Yuan had no way to completely resolve the issues in the sovereign immortal aperture, so he could only alleviate them.

Naturally, regardless of how he strengthened them, these subordinates would not have the ability to take part in the contest within Crazed Demon Cave. Fang Yuan also did not have such extravagant hopes.

Nurturing these subordinates required a large amount of resources.

Fang Yuan had devoured many of the two heavens' grotto-heavens and plundered the countless years of accumulations of these grotto-heavens, he naturally did not lack the resources to nurture them.

On the basis of cultivation resources, Fang Yuan had already surpassed most of the super forces in the world.

Even if Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven had much more accumulation than Fang Yuan, they could not copy his action.

Fang Yuan possessed Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool, it was extremely easy for him to refine rank six and rank seven Immortal Gu. That was why he could domineeringly place all kinds of Immortal Gu on the exchange list and let his subordinates exchange for them.

If Fang Yuan needed to use some Immortal Gu that they exchanged for in the future, he could just throw a compulsory mission at the person. Who would dare to go against Fang Yuan's decree?

At that time, Fang Yuan would give even more contribution points in exchange, the subordinate whose Immortal Gu was seized might even be quite happy.

The heated reactions of his subordinates was within Fang Yuan's expectations.

These Gu Immortals who were stimulated by the exchange list began to crazily accept the tasks, and took the initiative to go to various areas of the sovereign immortal aperture to work like bees.

As for the first task on the mission board, the Gu Immortals were discussing if Lord Fang Yuan had made a mistake?

But even after a few days, the task content had not changed.

The Gu Immortals became increasingly covetous, the contribution point reward of this task was sizable.

Shi Zong was the person to study the new exchange list for the longest time.

Recently, Shi Zong had been distressed over a huge issue.

He was the first supreme elder of Northern Plains' rockman tribe, he was rank seven and was about to face his third grand tribulation.

Rank seven Gu Immortals faced an earthly calamity every ten years, a heavenly tribulation every fifty years, and a grand tribulation every one hundred years.

Earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations were not big issues to Shi Zong. But a grand tribulation was huge trouble, the previous two grand tribulations had almost destroyed Shi Zong's confidence.

The third grand tribulation was imminent, Shi Zong was thinking of ways to delay the grand tribulation.

But he had turned the whole exchange list inside out and was still unable to find a trace of hope.

"The exchange list doesn't have any methods to delay calamities and tribulations!" Shi Zong frowned.

"Does master not have such methods? Obviously not!" Shi Zong's gaze locked on the first task in the mission board.

"Looks like master is encouraging us to accept this task."

Shi Zong was enticed.

His rockman tribe came from Northern Plains' northern icy plain, Fang Yuan had forced them on his ship.

But by now, Shi Zong found that this ship had already become a warship with a bright future and unimaginable fortune.

Since ancient times, the main criteria of a leader was — making use of both benevolence and authority.

Fang Yuan had no lack of authority, so when the exchange list appeared, it changed many people's hearts.

Shi Zong did not dare to betray Fang Yuan and had seen the benefits of following Fang Yuan, he thought for a long while and decided to take the risk, accepting that task!

He accepted the task openly and did not conceal it.

And soon, the news regarding him accepting the first task spread throughout the sovereign immortal aperture's Gu Immortal world.

"Shi Zong is a veteran rank seven Gu Immortal. If he can pass the tribulation successfully, he will become a rank eight!"

"Let's see what's going on with this task."

"Sigh, I also wanted to accept this task. I did not expect Shi Zong to seize the initiative. This is a good opportunity to express loyalty to master."

Not long after Shi Zong accepted the task, he was summoned by Fang Yuan's time path clone.

The time path clone was going to manage Shi Zong's immortal aperture and make preparations for the tribulation.

Shi Zong opened his immortal aperture, Fang Yuan's time path clone personally took control and stuffed earth path immortal materials inside his immortal aperture.

Worry soil, green pond rotten soil, diamond soil, great lake soil, concealing heaven dust, grand soil, region sand, impermanence rock, smoky warm jade, thousand year frost jade essence, dark inkstone, marrow sucking stone, regret water rock, round kun stone, hibiscus stalactite, stone heart liquid, eight-parts jade, and so on; the large number of earth path immortal material made Shi Zong speechless.

After coming to his senses, Shi Zong's heart jumped in fright.

"Gu Immortal calamities and tribulations are the result of Heavenly Dao seeking balance. Right now, my earth path foundation has increased to such an astonishing amount; my grand tribulation will become even more terrifying. Ordinary Gu Immortals want their calamities and tribulations to be as weak as possible, but master is completely the opposite, it is as if he wants the grand tribulation to become a myriad tribulation!"

Several days later, the time to undergo tribulation was here.

Fang Yuan's main body arrived at an ordinary sea area of Eastern Sea and opened his immortal aperture, letting Shi Zong out.

Shi Zong greeted Fang Yuan first before placing his aperture in the outside world.

The blessed land's door was opened and started absorbing a large amount of the outside world's heaven and earth qi.

Fang Yuan stood outside the entrance.

He could not go in.

He had too many dao marks; previously, when he attacked Fire Plain grotto-heaven, he was unable to go in as well, let alone this tiny rank seven blessed land.

The grand tribulation was on time.

First was the arrival of heaven path dao marks, then these heaven path dao marks transformed into dao marks of other paths based on the state of Shi Zong's blessed land.

Most of these dao marks were of earth path.

The transformed dao marks used and expended heaven and earth qi to turn into calamities and tribulations.

If Fang Yuan used big family qi Gu right now, he could absorb the tribulation qi and weaken the grand tribulation.

Right now, Fang Yuan was looking forward to the grand tribulation becoming even stronger.

Soon the grand tribulation took shape, Shi Zong's face turned pale.

"Yellow sky dust cloud! Heavens, it saw my immortal aperture was very prosperous and I had too many earth path resources, so this is specially targeting them."

Yellow sky dust cloud would gain increasingly powerful suction force along with time and absorb the immortal aperture's earth path resources.

The more earth path resources it absorbed, the stronger it would become, its range would increase and it would become denser with much more powerful suction force.

Among all the grand tribulations, yellow sky dust cloud was absolutely among the top few hated grand tribulations.

Shi Zong tried several killer moves, although they were effective, the effect was very little on such a large yellow sky dust cloud.

"I can only rely on master now!" Shi Zong's expression was dismal.

Right at this time, Shi Zong saw multi-colored and dazzling totems fly out of Fang Yuan's body and enter the blessed land, before charging into the yellow sky dust cloud.

These totems were of various types and shapes. There existed ferocious tiger and leopard, agile deer and rabbit, lush trees, as well as spinning flying rocks.

But no matter which one, they all emitted rank eight aura!

Shi Zong's body and mind shook together: "Oh heavens! More than twenty killer moves, all at rank eight level. Master actually has such terrifying strength!"

These were all totem killer moves.

Ever since Fang Yuan obtained the cultivation method of thousands of basic totems from Zhan Bu Du, he would cultivate this move whenever he had some free time.

Myriad Beast Fusion Color Heaven was the sacred land for cultivating totem killer moves, it was very difficult to cultivate totems outside of this place. Because there was no such food path environment, almost all the food recipes would lose their effect when placed in the outside world.

Fang Yuan, however, was different.

He had deep food path attainment, he modified these food recipes and turned them into killer moves.

With the help of these food path killer moves and countless Gu materials, Fang Yuan was able to cultivate over twenty totems.

These totems were all at rank eight level and were carefully selected by Fang Yuan, their power naturally would not be low. What was even more amazing was once these totem killer moves were formed, they were extremely easy and convenient to activate.

Fang Yuan willed, activating over twenty totems at once. In other words, he activated over twenty rank eight killer moves in an instant!

It was because he possessed the sovereign immortal body that he could fearlessly cultivate totems of so many paths. If it were other Gu Immortals, they would never be able to accomplish this.

Shi Zong watched with a stupefied expression.

Because at that moment, the extremely thick yellow sky dust cloud that covered the sky was shredded by these totems.

"Too vicious, too terrifying!" Shi Zong's thoughts fluctuated intensely.

But although the grand tribulation was destroyed violently, it did not stop. Instead it was trying hard to condense again.

However, the moment a trace of yellow sky dust cloud condensed, it was instantly torn into pieces by the totems.

Heaven's will did not give up but the totems were even fiercer.

Inexplicably, Shi Zong suddenly felt that the grand tribulation was somewhat pitiful.

Immortal killer move — Heaven-Human Sensation.

Immortal killer move — Human Executing Heaven's Work.

Immortal killer move — Unrestrained Heavenly Mark!

Fang Yuan made his move from outside the entrance, refining all the heaven path dao marks from the grand tribulation.

But the unrestrained heavenly marks fell on Shi Zong's blessed land.

But it was not a problem.

Fang Yuan took out an Immortal Gu House, it was the repaired Thieves Den.

Thieves Den's killer move — Steal Dao!

The theft path killer move's working principle was to use theft path immortal materials as the catalyst, the theft path dao marks in the immortal materials would be consumed instantly and the dao marks in the outside world would be stolen. The stolen dao marks must be attached to these theft path immortal materials.

So, if the stolen dao marks were disorderly, the immortal materials would have no value, like those immortal materials found everywhere in Crazed Demon Cave.

In short, Thieves Den had the ability to steal the outside world's dao marks but did not have a method to use them.

Moreover, Thieves Den was already a peak level creation and could not be modified, it had no room or potential for improvement.

These stolen unrestrained heavenly marks formed a heaven path immortal material.

Fang Yuan took this heaven path immortal material and activated a food path killer move — Devour Heaven and Earth!

This killer move was Fang Yuan's gain from his recent cultivation.

Fang Yuan's food path attainment level was grandmaster, he had countless food path killer moves and deep wisdom path attainment, it was not difficult for him to create a killer move to devour heaven path immortal materials.

Chapter 2134: Fang Yuan, Just You Wait!

After consuming this heaven path immortal material, Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture gained nine more heaven path dao marks.

The grand tribulation that sent Shi Zong into despair, when turned into heaven path dao marks, merely amounted to nine. Moreover, this grand tribulation's strength was much higher than normal, a normal grand tribulation would give less than nine heaven path dao marks when transformed.

"Probably around seven." Fang Yuan estimated.

This could not compare to the gains from annexing the two heavens' grotto-heavens.

Each of the two heavens' grotto-heavens gave Fang Yuan several thousand heaven path dao marks. Fang Yuan devoured grotto-heavens one after the other, his sovereign immortal aperture's development had already reached eighty percent.

At present, his heaven path dao marks numbered over two hundred thousand!

Fang Yuan wanted to become venerable through refinement path, so he prioritized annexing refinement path grotto-heavens, which increased his refinement path dao marks to over six million!

"Currently, the sovereign immortal aperture cannot annex any more grotto-heavens. So I can only use this method to gain heaven path dao marks."

"Although the increase each time is small, Gu Immortals undergoing tribulations is a process that will never stop. Little droplets of water make a mighty ocean, I can accumulate a substantial amount with this method."

In the long run, this path of helping Gu Immortals undergo tribulation was quite bright.

The two heavens' grotto-heavens accumulated for a million or so years to have such foundations. But if Fang Yuan annexed one, there would be one less.

There was, however, an unending stream of Gu Immortals.

Shi Zong's tribulation succeeded and he advanced to rank eight.

When he returned to the sovereign immortal aperture, he immediately received the congratulations of many people and was asked about the exact details.

Shi Zong was already prepared, he had used Gu worms to record the complete video of his tribulation.

When this video was spread, it brought a strong impact to the sovereign immortal aperture's Gu Immortal world.

"Master is so strong!"

"He used over twenty rank eight killer moves in an instant, is he still human?"

"These are totem killer moves? They look quite convenient!"

From the start, the Gu Immortals were attracted by the totem killer moves. When Thieves Den appeared, they exclaimed in shock again.

When the video reached the end and the yellow sky dust cloud was completely destroyed by Fang Yuan, the Gu Immortals sighed, deeply moved.

"Master's methods are unimaginable, he can really destroy calamities and tribulations beforehand."

"In history, these calamities and tribulations will calm down only after they have vented everything. But Lord Fang Yuan has unfathomable powers, he can get rid of calamities and tribulations ahead of time."

"It can be inferred that this task is a huge fortune. Not only can we increase our cultivation level, we can also get a sizable amount of contribution points."

"Didn't you hear what Shi Zong said? Although he passed the tribulation and became a rank eight Gu Immortal, he did not gain any new dao marks."

"Ah? There was such a thing. No wonder this task compensated us with contribution points."

Shi Zong did not hide this, he was somewhat hesitant at first, but after the tribulation, Fang Yuan personally ordered him to publicize the truth.

No gain in dao marks, this news was like a bucket of cold water that poured on these excited Gu Immortals.

The Gu Immortals began to calm down.

This result needed to be properly considered.

No gain of dao marks was a huge loss to Gu Immortals. After all, undergoing tribulation was the main way of gaining dao marks.

Over the next few days, there was no movement. But when Shi Zong used these contribution points to exchange for two rank seven earth path Immortal Gu and three earth path killer moves, another person accepted the task of undergoing tribulation.

After that, more and more Gu Immortals began to imitate this, and it soon formed a wave in the sovereign immortal aperture's Gu Immortal world.

These Gu Immortals were shrewd, they had calculated the gains and losses.

Although they would lose a batch of dao marks, the value of the gained contribution points was far higher than the losses.

The Gu Immortal's battle strength and immortal aperture's environment would indeed weaken from the loss of these dao marks, but dao marks was only one of the factors.

There were many factors which determined a Gu Immortal's battle strength. For instance, Immortal Gu was a main factor, immortal killer moves as well were much more important than some thousands of dao marks.

The immortal aperture's environment would be influenced, but the Gu Immortals could exchange for all kinds of immortal materials to create even more resource points to fill this gap.

What made the Gu Immortals choose this path was that there was a special entry in the exchange list that allowed the Gu Immortals to supply the immortal materials and expend some contribution points, to ask for Fang Yuan's clone to use food path killer moves to increase their corresponding dao marks!

These various reasons created an unending supply of Gu Immortals who underwent tribulation.

Fang Yuan's heaven path dao marks continued to increase.

Southern Border.

Ke Xin Hong was flying through the clouds.

He was communicating with his friend.

"You don't know that all the Gu Immortals are accepting the assisted tribulation task. Some Gu Immortals whose tribulations are still far away will choose an option in the exchange list, it requests master's time path clone to accelerate their immortal aperture's time flow! They are using every means possible to accept this task."

Ke Xin Hong read up to here before replying with the information path Immortal Gu: "It is because the contribution points for this task are sizable, moreover, whoever obtains the contribution points first will be able to move a step ahead and do more missions, entering a beneficial feedback loop. Look at that Shi Zong, he has been thriving recently. His strength has surged, he can do and take on more difficult tasks, obtaining even more contribution points much faster."

"Unfortunately, I received a mandatory task now and have to go on a diplomatic mission to Wu clan. Otherwise, I would have been the first to accept this task."

His friend replied soon: "You need to be careful, you are going to Wu clan's headquarters to demand Hu Land. That is a secluded domain of heaven and earth, and Wu Yong is the Southern Alliance's Leader!"

Ke Xin Hong, however, was confident: "I am quite hopeful for this trip. Even if it fails, Wu Yong won't do anything to me. You have not personally realized and witnessed master's power and influence. Alright, I have arrived, I will contact you later."

Ke Xin Hong slowly flew down.

Below him was Wu Yi Mountain.

Wu clan's headquarters was located here.

Seeing Ke Xin Hong, two Gu Immortals immediately flew up from Wu Yi Mountain, at the front was Wu clan's second supreme elder Wu Ba Chong.

Ke Xin Hong had already notified them before coming here.

Wu clan's earnestness could be seen, they had sent Wu Ba Chong to welcome him.

"Envoy, please come in." Wu Ba Chong led Ke Xin Hong to Wu clan's headquarters.

"You came from afar and must be tired, how about resting for a while." Wu Ba Chong was polite.

Ke Xin Hong shook his hand: "Let's get down to business first."

"Alright. Please wait a while, our first supreme elder is handling some clan affairs."

Ke Xin Hong nodded and waited patiently.

He could understand that the leader of the great Wu clan could not be available so casually. Whether he was really busy or not, they had to put up this show.

After five minutes, Wu Ba Chong came again and led Ke Xin Hong towards the guest hall.

Ke Xin Hong saw Wu Yong there.

Ke Xin Hong did not speak nonsense and said directly: "Lord Wu Yong, I come with master's sincerity to have another transaction with your noble clan."

Wu Yong and Wu Ba Chong looked at each other, they had profited a lot in the previous transaction. Wu Yong asked with a smile: "I wonder what transaction it is?"

Ke Xin Hong smiled: "Master is willing to pay a price to buy the Hu Land in your possession."

Instantly, Wu Yong's pupils shrank and killing intent surged in his heart!

"What?!" Wu Ba Chong could not sit still, he stood, "What Hu Land? How could my Wu clan have this secluded domain of heaven and earth? Fang Yuan is definitely mistaken."

Ke Xin Hong smiled and did not refute.

Wu Yong's expression was dark as he interrupted Wu Ba Chong: "Alright, Ba Chong."

Wu Ba Chong immediately stopped denying it, but there was indignance and anger on his face. Veins popped up on his clenched fists as he stared rigidly at Ke Xin Hong.

If gazes could kill, at this moment, Wu Ba Chong would have already killed Ke Xin Hong a hundred times with his gaze.

Ke Xin Hong only looked at Wu Yong, turning a deaf ear to Wu Ba Chong.

He bowed: "Lord Wu Yong, what is your reply?"

Wu Yong suddenly showed a smile: "Since Fang Yuan wants to trade, of course we can. I believe he will definitely pay a satisfying price."

Ke Xin Hong could not help but feel a chill when he saw Wu Yong's attitude.

Wu Yong was really terrifying, in such a short period of time, he accepted this fact and made the most sensible choice!

Ke Xin Hong took a deep breath and said the price: "Master is aware that Lord Wu Yong desires rank eight Immortal Gu, Eight-faced Prestige Wind. Master is willing to personally refine this rank eight Immortal Gu."

"What?" Wu Ba Chong's expression changed again as he bellowed furiously: "Hu Land can be seen as a quasi-rank nine Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan is not taking out even one rank eight Immortal Gu and wants to exchange with such conditions. You are too insincere!"

Wu Yong said through clenched teeth: "This is indeed somewhat too overboard."

Ke Xin Hong smiled: "Wu clan excels in wind path, your only qi path foundation is in Sheng Tian true inheritance. Although Hu Land is a secluded domain of heaven and earth, it doesn't have much value for Wu clan."

Wu Ba Chong immediately refuted: "You can't say that, any path's attainment can be developed. Although my Wu clan excels in wind path, could it be that we cannot excel in qi path in the future? With Hu Land, I would rather change to qi path and replace my vital Gu! With such huge prospects, which super force would be willing to give it up?"

Ke Xin Hong glanced at Wu Ba Chong: "Second supreme elder, you are spot on, quite insightful. It is indeed correct, with Hu Land, the prospect of qi path is highly favorable. But..."

As he said this, Ke Xin Hong intentionally paused before saying deeply: "The prerequisite is... you need to possess Hu Land."

"You!!!" Wu Ba Chong's killing intent erupted and he looked ready to attack.

Ke Xin Hong's hidden meaning was that Wu clan could not keep Hu Land. Since they could not keep Hu Land, it was useless to mention any qi path prospects.

Ke Xin Hong looked towards Wu Yong and bowed again, saying respectfully: "Lord Wu Yong, I will be frank. If your noble clan is not satisfied with this price, we are willing to refine three rank eight Immortal Gu for your clan."

He then continued with a bitter smile: "This is my side's bottom line and there won't be any concession. Lord Wu Yong, please understand. I am only a messenger, I cannot make decisions."

Wu Yong was silent for a while before smiling: "You are an excellent messenger. I agree to your conditions. Wu Ba Chong, bring Ke Xin Hong to take Hu Land and send the rank seven fan wind Gu as well."

"First supreme elder!" Wu Ba Chong was indignant.

"Go." Wu Yong was solemn.

"Sigh!" Wu Ba Chong heaved a deep sigh as he looked at Ke Xin Hong with hatred.

"Follow me!" Wu Ba Chong quickly moved past Ke Xin Hong and walked out of the hall.

Wu Yong sat on his seat without moving.

The guest hall had bright lighting, but Wu Yong's face was dark and heavy.

Losing Hu Land had a huge impact on him!

"How did Fang Yuan know about Hu Land? Did he capture Kong Ri Tian?"

Wu Yong had a lot of doubts but he did not want to investigate it. Since the matter had already reached this stage, there was no meaning in talking about this.

After a long while, Wu Ba Chong returned to report: "Ke Xin Hong has left. Lord, should we send some people in disguise and ambush him?"

Wu Yong shook his head: "With Fang Yuan's wisdom, how could he not have expected such a loophole? Don't do unnecessary things."

Wu Ba Chong said through clenched teeth: "Damn it. Our grand Wu clan cannot protect Hu Land!"

Wu Yong said with a heavy voice: "We need to remember this. In here, in Wu clan's headquarters, we were forced to sell the secluded domain of heaven and earth! This is my disgrace, and also Wu clan's disgrace. In the future, if there is a chance, I will clear this humiliation and pay it back a thousand fold. Fang Yuan, just you wait!"

Chapter 2135: Liver Life Formation

Fang Yuan was holding heaven's envy Immortal Gu in his hand.

Under the continuous supply of rank eight white litchi immortal essence, heaven's envy Immortal Gu let out a light, crystal-like radiance.

This Immortal Gu seemed like a flea made of crystal, it was as large as a fist and was curled up like a ball.

Suddenly, the crystal radiance from heaven's envy Immortal Gu burst, turning into countless broken crystal lights that shone dazzlingly!

"Success!" Fang Yuan was shocked, at that moment just now, he had actually refined this rank seven heaven's envy Immortal Gu.

The curled-up crystal flea stretched its body and meekly lay on Fang Yuan's palm.

"I am probably the first person in history to completely refine heaven's envy Immortal Gu."

At this moment, Fang Yuan had created history!

But, within an instant, his excited emotions calmed down.

He already had many unprecedented achievements.

"In this recent period of time, I have repeatedly helped my subordinates undergo tribulations. Although the heaven path dao marks gained each time are small in quantity, the numbers accumulate eventually."

"Adding these heaven path dao marks, I am finally able to refine heaven's envy Immortal Gu completely, breaking the previous limit."

"My guess was right!"

The fact was proved in front of him: As long as the unrestrained heavenly marks reached a certain number, heaven path Immortal Gu could be refined.

In the long river of history, there were countless Gu cultivators with geniuses as numerous as stars in the sky, and the ten venerables like ten large suns. But none of them truly cultivated heaven path.

Limitless Demon Venerable and Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable might have grasp of the killer move unrestrained heavenly mark, but from what Fang Yuan knew, they had not delved deeply into heaven path.

The former cultivated rule path and the latter cultivated earth path. Maybe Limitless Demon Venerable researched unrestrained heavenly mark to cultivate heaven path, but he had already become a rule path Demon Venerable at that time and could not turn back anymore.

From this, the advantage of the sovereign immortal aperture could be seen again.

Cultivate every path!

A brand-new unknown path emerged before Fang Yuan.

Heaven path!

Unrestrained heavenly mark was the key to starting heaven path cultivation.

This path had huge prospects and terrifying advantages, even mortals could understand a thing or two!

"Heaven path comprises everything and balances everything, all living beings, be they immortals or mortals, powerful or weak, are included in heaven path. All kinds of Immortal Gu, secluded domains of heaven and earth, are also under the restrictions of heaven path. Heaven path controls calamities and tribulations, it controls lifespan Gu. Venerables were powerful for an era, but when compared to heaven path, they are like a burning torch."

"If I walk this path...."

Fang Yuan could not help but daydream.

Apart from anything else, just lifespan Gu and fate Gu, these two factors made him feel a trace of excitement.

Every venerable in history was troubled by lifespan Gu, and fate Gu had never been directly controlled by Heavenly Court. Even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not have any solution, she could only become one with the Dao to interfere with heaven's will and distort the power of fate Gu.

"Among all the paths, the starting threshold of heaven path is the highest. One must grasp the killer move unrestrained heavenly mark first."

"I have only stepped on the road of heaven path, I still need to walk a long distance before I can touch the deeper profundities like lifespan Gu and fate Gu!"

"The battle of Crazed Demon Cave is imminent, I won't be able to accomplish this before the battle."

Although he had officially stepped on the cultivation path of heaven path and its prospects were bright and huge, Fang Yuan did not intend to fully delve into it.

The situation did not allow him to do so.

"At most, I can invest once more in heaven's envy Immortal Gu."

Cooking Luck Pot brought enormous convenience to Fang Yuan, letting him know that heaven's envy Immortal Gu might be the key in the battle of Crazed Demon Cave.

Heaven path's cultivation road was going to be long, and Fang Yuan had just taken the initial step. But heaven's envy Immortal Gu could be developed further.

"I have completely refined heaven's envy Immortal Gu, but it is only at rank seven. If I create its corresponding killer moves, it might be quite impressive at rank eight level. However, in my battle with venerables, rank seven will not be enough."

"I need to raise heaven's envy Immortal Gu to rank eight!"

Fang Yuan possessed Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool, but this was slightly troublesome.

Fang Yuan had a batch of heaven path immortal materials. It might not be enough if he were to try to refine many heaven path Immortal Gu, but it was enough to use on just heaven's envy Immortal Gu.

However, Fang Yuan's heaven path attainment was ordinary, he was not even at master level. Although his refinement path was as high as quasi-supreme, it would be quite difficult to research heaven's envy Immortal Gu's rank eight recipe.

It was not that there was no chance of success, but it would take too much time and energy.

In his initial estimation, it was going to require two to three years of deductions at the very least.

This was undoubtedly not feasible for Fang Yuan.

"Looks like I need to copy Wu Yong and raise some Gu Immortal seeds, before helping them undergo the ascension tribulation." Fang Yuan quickly found a way.

Fang Yuan did not care about the minimal gains in heaven path dao marks from immortal ascension of rank five Gu Masters. But when Gu Masters undergo immortal ascension, they would have a one-time opportunity to experience natural inspiration.

With this opportunity, the Gu Master questioned heaven and earth, and almost all their questions would be answered.

Since heaven and earth could produce heaven's envy Immortal Gu naturally, it definitely had heaven's envy Immortal Gu's recipe.

Fang Yuan did not demand much, he only needed a correct version of the Immortal Gu recipe of heaven's envy Gu, he could rely on his refinement path attainment to modify it to suit himself.

Moreover, Fang Yuan could also ask for some insights when asking heaven and earth.

For instance: "On the basis of certain kinds of heaven path immortal materials and the current situation, which heaven's envy Immortal Gu recipe is the easiest to refine?"

As he thought of this, he put a new task on the mission board and listed it at number one.

"Search for loyal and devoted Gu Immortal seeds who are suitable to undergo immortal ascension!"

Almost at the next instant, all the Gu Immortals in the sovereign immortal aperture knew of this task.

Ever since the establishment of the exchange list, these Gu Immortals had gone crazy!

Many of them had not even slept for months, using Gu worms to forcibly maintain their conditions, to complete tasks and earn contribution points.

Fang Yuan offered them the most suitable environment, reducing the difficulty of these Gu Immortals' cultivation to the minimum. Almost every day, they could feel their strength increasing.

Even if this increase was only a little, a little progress every day would accumulate to a terrifying amount after several days.

It was this euphoric feeling of experiencing the increase in their cultivation and strength that made these Gu Immortals unable to stop.

What gave Fang Yuan a pleasant surprise was that one of the human Gu Immortals developed an incomplete transformation path Immortal Gu recipe because of this — hard liver Gu.

This human Gu Immortal primarily cultivated transformation path, he was Solid Rock Warrior, who came from Beast Calamity grotto-heaven.

Hard liver Gu strengthened the Gu Immortal's liver, giving them lasting and vigorous energy which then allowed them to complete all kinds of laborious tasks without needing to rest. But if it was used excessively, the liver would harden to the limit and trigger a terrifying explosion, inflicting heavy injuries and even death.

After Fang Yuan got familiar with the Gu, he modified and completed it, and even created rank six to rank eight Gu recipes.

After using Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool to refine it, rank eight hard liver Immortal Gu was used as the core of a Gu formation.

Fang Yuan named this Gu formation as liver life formation[1], it operated all year round and collected a fee for every use. If the Gu Immortals were interested, they could hand over some contribution points to enter, after they come out, they will be full of energy and motivation!

"Did you liver today?"

"How much longer can you liver for?"

"I feel like my liver is about to explode."

Such conversations had already become a common daily topic between the Gu Immortals.

So, when Fang Yuan put up this task, the Gu Immortals were like red-eyed sharks that had smelled blood.

"Great task!"

"It was published by master himself."

"The reward is extremely abundant!"

"I cannot, I have not slept in three months. I want to rest a little."

"What rest! Go and liver! The great era is in front of us, we must grasp this excellent cultivation opportunity!"

The Gu Immortals moved out towards all kinds of places to gather Gu Immortal seeds.

In just a short while, this task was completely taken.

The Gu Immortals who could not take it were extremely vexed.

Some shouted regretfully: "Oh, this task was quite excellent, but I missed it!"

Every task on the mission board had a limited quota to prevent Gu Immortals from taking just the tasks with the highest rewards, which would result in unreasonable and wasteful distribution of manpower.

Fang Yuan handed the task of gathering Gu Immortal seeds to his subordinates.

He estimated there would be quite a lot of Gu Immortal seeds, it was going to surpass super forces like Wu clan.

It was because Fang Yuan had annexed many forces like Lang Ya Sect and the two heavens' grotto-heavens, which had extremely deep foundations and long history. They definitely did not lack Gu Immortal seeds.

Using the little spare time he had, Fang Yuan personally went to strengthen Ni clan.

He quietly set up a year essence sub-pool in Ni clan's territory, forming a time path zone.

Ni clan's time would pass much faster, which would increase the rate of Immortal Gu production, it would become much more convenient for Fang Yuan to comprehend Gu refinement profundities of human isolation style.

"The sovereign immortal aperture has a huge number of variant humans, but not many humans."

"Most of the humans are from Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, but it can be foreseen that in the future, Mini Yellow Heaven's Ni clan will probably become the top human force."

Fang Yuan thought to himself.

He had just finished setting up the time path zone when Ke Xin Hong's message arrived.

The latter's diplomatic mission to Wu clan was successful and had obtained Hu Land.

Immortal killer move — Heaven and Earth Travel!

At the next moment, Fang Yuan moved from Eastern Sea to Southern Border, appearing in front of Ke Xin Hong.

After putting Ke Xing Hong in the sovereign immortal aperture, Fang Yuan returned to Eastern Sea.

He secretly arrived in a nameless sea area and toyed around with Hu Land as he waited for Qi Sea Ancestor.

"For you." Fang Yuan handed Hu Land to Qi Sea Ancestor.

The Qi Sea clone quickly received it and said excitedly: "Good, good, I have a premonition! With Hu Land, my combat system will be completed!"

"I will wait in anticipation." Fang Yuan's main body left shortly after.

He was also pondering about his combat system and had made much progress, but was still far away from completing it.

[1] In Chinese medicine, the liver gets damaged/heaty if one does not sleep properly at night. In this case, 'livering/ liver torture' is a common Chinese Internet term for staying up all night to game etc. Back

Chapter 2136: Fang Yuan's Secluded Domains of Heaven and Earth

Immortal killer move — Landscape as Before!

Fang Yuan activated the killer move.

The previous landscape as before Immortal Gu was only at rank six. But two months ago, Fang Yuan had successfully raised it to rank eight.

Rank eight was the limit of landscape as before Immortal Gu.

The limit of most Immortal Gu was at rank eight. After advancing to rank eight, they would have arrived at their peak and could not be advanced anymore.

Gu were the essence of heaven and earth, fragments of the Great Dao. These fragments had their respective limits, those with higher limits could accumulate slowly and reach rank nine, while those with lower limits might even be forced to stay at rank six.

There were many Immortal Gu, although they were unique, they covered almost all aspects imaginable. For instance, Fang Yuan used the killer move lingering poisonous ant plague, which gave birth to two Immortal Gu — red copper immortal ant Gu and white noodle immortal ant Gu. If there was a slight change, there might be another kind of Immortal Gu. For instance, dark-gold immortal ant, black noodle immortal ant, and so on.

Among all the Immortal Gu, only a small portion could truly advance to rank nine.

Rank eight landscape as before Immortal Gu was still a time path Immortal Gu. But the killer move Fang Yuan was using right now was a compound killer move.

It contained profundities of not only time path, but also earth path, water path, rule path, soul path, and other paths.

Under the effect of this compound killer move, Reverse Flow River let out soft gushing sounds as it started expanding at a rapid pace.

After Fang Yuan's nurturing over this period of time, the compound killer move that was used dozens of times showed great effects, Reverse Flow River, which previously only had a little trace left of it, had become a long narrow river!

Fang Yuan had all along been trying to restore Reverse Flow River, and he finally got a good result now.

He had previously thought of using orderly well.

This killer move was a rank nine killer move and came from Shadow Sect's true inheritance. This move used City Well as the core, it could modify secluded domains of heaven and earth, removing the conflict between dao marks, which made it convenient to restore them.

Dang Hun Mountain, Luo Po Valley, and Miniscule Mountain had experienced this move.

But Fang Yuan had never been able to grasp this killer move.

Because he lacked its crucial core Immortal Gu, Immortal Gu was unique, that core Immortal Gu was already in someone else's possession. Fang Yuan had thought of modifying this killer move but it was extremely difficult.

This was a rank nine rule path killer move, it had already reached a peak level where it had no room for improvement.

At least, Fang Yuan was unable to see any.

His rule path attainment level was at great grandmaster, and not quasi-supreme. He was still some distance away from seeing through this kind of rank nine killer move.

"Reverse Flow River is recovering faster right now, but at the later stage of its recovery, Landscape as Before's compound killer move will experience a fall in effectiveness continually, until it becomes negligible."

Landscape as Before's compound killer move was at rank eight level, while the complete Reverse Flow River was a secluded domain of heaven and earth, which was equivalent to rank nine in terms of quantity of dao marks. Because of the huge amount of dao marks, they could sometimes be used as quasi-rank nine Immortal Gu.

Naturally, this depended on the Gu cultivator's ability.

Conceptualizing killer moves with the secluded domain of heaven and earth as the core was only the start, the crucial point was how exceptional the created killer moves were, and if they could fully use the secluded domain of heaven and earth or not.

For instance, Fang Yuan's reverse flow protection seal made use of Reverse Flow River only at the intermediate level.

His Luo Po seal was only at the elementary level of secluded domain usage.

Orderly well killer move was different, it made use of City Well to the highest degree, and was at the advanced level.

There was no killer move that completely used secluded domains of heaven and earth.

Secluded domains of heaven and earth were not Immortal Gu, after all.

Immortal Gu was alive and could be used fully as long as immortal essence was transferred into them. But secluded domains of heaven and earth were non-living, their usage was limited.

An Immortal Gu was a connected body of fragments of dao marks. A secluded domain of heaven and earth was an amalgamation of countless dao marks, these dao marks were piled together, some were straight or bent, some were continuous threads, some were entirely different, and some were intertwined. There was no way to make use of all the dao marks.

Even venerables were not an exception.

This could be seen from the killer move orderly well.

"I have gathered quite a lot of secluded domains of heaven and earth. Dang Hun Mountain, Luo Po Valley, Reverse Flow River, City Well, Hu Land, as well as the incomplete Refinement Sea, Human Sea, and Qian Kun Crystal Wall."

Dang Hun Mountain was the first secluded domain obtained by Fang Yuan, he even entered Northern Plains to find a way to repair it.

Luo Po seal, which used Luo Po Valley as the core, had once helped Fang Yuan kill Gu Immortal experts.

There was no need to talk about Reverse Flow River, in that event of Old Ancestor Xue Hu refining fortune rivalling heaven Gu, Fang Yuan had relied on reverse flow protection seal to shock the world while being hunted by Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court.

City Well was obtained from the turbulent flow sea area, Fang Yuan had used it as a trap to kill many Eastern Sea Gu Immortals.

Hu Land was the easiest to obtain, he bought it forcefully from Wu Yong. Naturally, it was possible because of Fang Yuan's strength and reputation. These things had been accumulated since his rebirth, while being on the verge of life and death, and going through countless large battles.

The incomplete Refinement Sea came from Lang Ya blessed land, it showed Long Hair Ancestor's ambition. Unfortunately, although Fang Yuan obtained it, he did not have enough spare effort, time, and resources to complete it. Currently, the incomplete Refinement Sea was being intensely consumed by Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool.

The incomplete Human Sea came from Eastern Sea's Xia clan. Wu Shuai led the variant human alliance to invade Xia clan's territory, killing or driving Xia clansmen away, and looting this incomplete Human Sea.

The last was Qian Kun Crystal Wall. Put simply, it was a bunch of grey-white stone slabs.

The surface of the grey-white stone slabs were filled with black ink lines. Some were straight while others were curled, there were thin and thick lines. The lines were drawn over one another, some looked like letters while others looked like drawings of scenery.

Legends said that if one gathered all of the stone slabs, they could piece back Qian Kun Crystal Wall and the Gu cultivator would be able to enter Book Mountain again.

If one looked at the history of humanity, they would find that generations of Gu Masters, Gu Immortals, or even Immortal and Demon Venerables collected these stone slabs before.

Fang Yuan had obtained countless grey-white stone slabs from Great Wisdom Immortal Mother. According to what Great Wisdom Immortal Mother said, these stone slabs could form half the Qian Kun Crystal Wall!

Fang Yuan had obtained a batch of grey-white stone slabs from other sources like Lang Ya Sect, and the storage of the two heavens' grotto-heavens. Naturally, the number of these stone slabs could not compare to what Great Wisdom Immortal Mother had, and there were also fake goods among them.

Great Wisdom Immortal Mother's grey-white stone slabs were from the inkman race's true inheritance.

There were many fake goods among the stone slabs circulated in the market. But the grey-white stone slabs in the inkman race's true inheritance were all genuine.

"According to the records in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, Primordial Domain was originally inside Qian Kun Crystal Wall. Unfortunately, Limitless Demon Venerable took it away and put it in Crazed Demon Cave. Even if I construct Qian Kun Crystal Wall now, I won't be able to enter Primordial Domain."

Fang Yuan tried all ways to increase his battle strength, these secluded domains of heaven and earth were naturally going to be made use of.

Reverse Flow River was being restored, killer moves using Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley as the core were also being developed. Hu Land was given to the Qi Sea clone, Fang Yuan did not have time to put his effort into this.

Among all the secluded domains of heaven and earth, Fang Yuan paid the most attention to the incomplete Human Sea.

Back then, he chose to invade Eastern Sea's Xia clan mainly because of this artificial secluded domain of heaven and earth.

"All the venerables have human path killer moves, so I need to have some foundation in human path. Even if I don't become dominant in this path, I need to have means to defend against it."

Fang Yuan had suffered during the fate war.

The venerable methods were mostly human path methods, every move was terrifyingly powerful or had amazing effects, influencing the whole war.

Previously, Fang Yuan had ordered his subordinates to kill a hundred million humans in Fire Plain grotto-heaven to use in the incomplete Human Sea.

But this was not enough.

The previous resources were all spent, Human Sea was still some distance from completion.

"The variant human alliance also has many human grotto-heavens with large numbers of humans. But it is not convenient to target these humans."

"Firstly, it will cause dissension in these human grotto-heavens' Gu Immortals. Secondly, these humans will be moved to the sovereign immortal aperture in the future, and are foundations for me to develop human path. Lastly, there are so many humans in the world, why do I need to sacrifice my own people?"

Fang Yuan then issued a task — slaughter humans and gather resources.

Compared to the previous tribulation task, this task was obviously cruel and reeked of blood.

"Master is a demonic path member after all." Many human Gu Immortals lamented.

"But, I quite enjoy slaughtering the outside world's humans!" This task resonated with variant human Gu Immortals.

"Forget it, as long as it is not our grotto-heavens suffering, what does it have to do with us if other humans die?" Those owners of human grotto-heavens were glad about their allegiance.

Soon, over ten Gu Immortals quietly moved out from the territory of Eastern Sea's Xia clan.

There were many fishing villages in Eastern Sea's islands.

Birds chirped and dogs barked, smoke spiraled upwards.

"Kill." A miniman Gu Immortal flew towards these fishing villages and ruthlessly activated Immortal Gu.

Leaves fell down like a rainstorm, killing countless men and women, old and young, blood splashing everywhere.

"Back then, us minimen were captured by you humans. My mother was strangled to death in front of me by human Gu Immortals. I am only taking back some interest!" The miniman Gu Immortal's face was filled with hatred.

On a certain island in Eastern Sea, there was an enormous city.

Two variant human Gu Immortals united to bring forth a tens of feet high tsunami.

At the juncture of life and death, an Eastern Sea lone immortal walked out and blocked the tsunami.

"Stop, I am Gu Ming Xu. This is my homeland, I wonder what the issue is? Why are you implicating these innocent people?" This Gu Immortal shouted furiously.

The two variant human Gu Immortals came down from above the clouds and revealed their appearance.

"So it was Warm Sun Immortal Lord."

"Immortal Lord, you are wrong. Back then, this place had been the homeland of us hairy men. But you humans occupied it forcefully, my hairy man tribe fortunately had the protection of our supreme elder, so we were able to survive in the two heavens."

Gu Ming Xu could not restrain his anger when he saw the two variant human Gu Immortals: "So you are variant humans. You are really audacious, this place is near Eastern Sea's Tang clan. I have already requested reinforcements. Get lost, if you don't escape now, it will be too late!"

The two variant human Gu Immortals laughed loudly as they said: "Immortal Lord, why do you pretend to not know from where we came? Our master is Lord Gu Yue Fang Yuan! Let alone Tang clan, even if the whole of Eastern Sea's righteous path arrive together, they will be like chickens and dogs in front of our master."

"Gu Ming Xu, stop trying to put up a front."

"We are here to kill your fellow humans, to let you taste the pain and suffering we felt back then."

Gu Ming Xu lamented inwardly: "How can there be a demon like Fang Yuan, he actually sent variant humans to attack his own race! He is a traitor to humans, he has no bottom line and no sense of propriety. Damn it! Damn it!!"

Chapter 2137: Fang Yuan Deserves Death!

Qi sea.

Because Qi Sea Ancestor lived here, the qi sea sea area had become the Righteous Qi Alliance's headquarters.

At this moment, a banquet was being held inside the qi sea formation.

Qi Sea Ancestor sat on the main seat while the representatives of Eastern Sea righteous path forces sat to his left and right.

Sitting to the left of Qi Sea Ancestor was a food path Gu Immortal.

He was an old man with a brandy nose, he raised his wine cup high and toasted Qi Sea Ancestor: "Lord Ancestor, I offer this toast of spring sea blossom wine to you!"

Qi Sea Ancestor nodded, his seat was high above the others which gave him a naturally overlooking vision.

Qi Sea Ancestor took a sip before commenting lightly: "Zui Xian Weng, your spring wind petals wine is quite good, it has a vague poetic flavor of youth."

This food path Gu Immortal was Zui Xian Weng.

After he inherited Green Ant Ascetic and Wine Fairy's true inheritance in Central Continent, he was then silently persuaded by Qin Ding Ling to be a chess piece.

According to Qin Ding Ling's arrangements, Zui Xian Weng returned to Eastern Sea and rested for a period of time before taking the initiative to side with the Righteous Qi Alliance.

Everyone in the Righteous Qi Alliance welcomed him warmly.

Because Zui Xian Weng was among the outstanding lone cultivators of Eastern Sea's Gu Immortal world.

Zui Xian Weng possessed wine sea, he held a wine reception every year where he invited heroes and warriors of Eastern Sea. His connections were extremely wide, and he himself had good relations with all the large Eastern Sea righteous path forces.

There was a huge political significance for a representative character like him to join the Righteous Qi Alliance, just this significance itself had a huge value.

Because, although the Righteous Qi Alliance was established, most of its members were of Eastern Sea righteous path super clans. Besides them, there were also some two heaven's Gu Immortals who had joined Qi Sea clone.

Few Eastern Sea lone immortals joined the Righteous Qi Alliance.

Demonic immortals were even rarer.

Zui Xian Weng joining the alliance would definitely be a model example which would change some trend of Eastern Sea's Gu Immortal world, maybe, other lone and demonic immortals would take the initiative to join.

Besides these, there was another reason which was somewhat connected to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's lingering poisonous ant plague killer move had caused a huge disturbance in Eastern Sea's righteous path. They were forced to take out their hidden true inheritances to research the killer move, only then were they able to find a way to restrain it.

During this event, the Righteous Qi Alliance had wanted to invite Zui Xian Weng. However, at that time, Zui Xian Weng had already gone to Central Continent and was secretly searching for Green Ant's true inheritance.

Zui Xian Weng cultivated food path, which was rare in the five regions and two heavens.

While rarer things were often more precious.

Zui Xian Weng was worthy of being recruited!

Qi Sea Ancestor discussed with Eastern Sea's super forces and held a large welcoming banquet. Not only were they trying to leave a good impression and gain the approval of Zui Xian Weng, they were also proclaiming the Righteous Qi Alliance's attitude towards lone and demonic immortals.

When Zui Xian Weng saw Fang Yuan, he was extremely respectful and even had a flattering expression.

For instance, now.

Zui Xian Weng's wine was clearly called spring sea blossom wine. But Qi Sea Ancestor called it spring wind petals wine.

Whether Qi Sea Ancestor had not heard clearly or if it was a slip of tongue, Zui Xian Weng did not ponder on it, he bowed: "Many thanks to Ancestor for bestowing the name!"

"Amazing, amazing, spring wind petals wine not only suits the characteristics of this wine, it is also filled with poetic sentiment, making one feel like they are being caressed by spring wind, while flower petals flutter in the air."

"It is a great honor for this wine to be bestowed a name by Ancestor. With Ancestor's granting of this name, I believe this wine will be known throughout the five regions!"

"Hahaha." Qi Sea Ancestor laughed heartily as he pointed at Zui Xian Weng, "Old Weng, you are quite witty."

The various clan representatives also chimed in, their complements were like waves that followed Zui Xian Weng and moved towards Qi Sea Ancestor.

These Gu Immortals were praising while cursing silently.

'I did not think this old guy Zui Xian Weng to have such a shameless side."

"Truly a boot licker."

"But it is not strange. He holds a wine reception every year where he invites all the forces. He has some skills in social interaction."

Tang clan's Gu Immortal Tang Tang was just about to raise his wine cup, when an information path mortal Gu flew in.

He viewed it with his divine sense.

'What?! The variant human alliance has attacked!' His body jolted, he was greatly shocked.

But after reading the information properly, he relaxed somewhat.

"Fang Yuan only sent ten or so Gu Immortals over different areas of Eastern Sea to kill mortals."

"What is he trying to do?"

"Not long ago, he invaded Fire Plain grotto-heaven and slaughtered a hundred million humans!"

Tang Tang was pondering, when he recalled the incomplete Human Sea.

After Fang Yuan invaded Eastern Sea's Xia clan, the information about this artificial secluded domain of heaven and earth had spread far and wide. So the Righteous Qi Alliance was well aware of it.

At this time, another information path Gu worm flew over.

"Gu Ming Xu is requesting reinforcements from my clan?" Tang Tang's heart stirred slightly.

This Warm Sun Immortal Lord was a lawful lone immortal, Tang clan had always wanted to recruit him but was rejected by him. Who could have expected a crisis to appear out of nowhere, Gu Ming Xu actually offended the variant human alliance.

In the request letter, Gu Ming Xu had clearly expressed: If Tang clan can provide help, he will join Tang clan!

"My Tang clan cannot offend a person like Fang Yuan! Isn't this trying to push my Tang clan into the fire?" Tang Tang sneered mentally.

They could not give support.

Tang Tang immediately crushed this information path mortal Gu and treated it like he had not seen it.

Fang Yuan's target this time were only the mortals, moreover, he avoided the people of the super clans.

So, Tang clan did not suffer any losses.

As for reputation, Tang clan's reputation would fall a little because they did not retaliate. But, other clans were also the same, Fang Yuan's action was not targeting just Tang clan.

Since everyone was losing reputation, it was same as nobody losing any reputation.

"As long as the situation doesn't worsen, this is only a small matter. Let Fang Yuan kill however many he wants." Tang Tang continued to enjoy the banquet.

After receiving this message, he began to deliberately observe the surrounding Gu Immortals.

Sure enough, these people received the news one after the other.

"Fang Yuan's subordinates are slaughtering mortals?"

"They are not our clansmen anyway, why provoke Fang Yuan because of this?"

"Eastern Sea has so many mortals, even if some are killed, the population will be restored in ten years."

"Let's drink, let's drink."

"Hahaha, good wine!"

The atmosphere became even more lively. As the banquet continued, these Gu Immortals were starting to get drunk, their faces flushed red as they enjoyed themselves.

Tribulation clouds surged continually.

A large amount of water splashed around in the time path clone's immortal aperture, like fish jumping madly.

This was a grand tribulation — Jumping Time Fish Tribulation.

"The outcome is set." The time path clone was observing the whole process calmly.

With the main body helping personally, there would definitely be no issue.

The jumping time fish tribulation was not strong, it was an ordinary type of grand tribulation.

Heaven's will did not trouble Fang Yuan, which was rare. But the time path clone was not surprised.

"In the recent period of time, my main body has not only helped Gu Immortals to undergo tribulations, he is also helping those Gu Immortal seeds to undergo immortal ascension. With him present, unless it is a dream path tribulation, there will be no issue. Heaven's will realizes this fully, the calamities and tribulations are ordinary so that the main body won't gain more heaven path dao marks."

While the time path clone was thinking, the tribulation clouds in the sky were almost gone.

Fang Yuan did not continue to attack, instead he took out ability Gu to give it a try.

But ability Gu was almost destroyed.

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> clearly stated ability Gu would continue to grow stronger in calamities and tribulations. But Fang Yuan was unable to find a way to strengthen it.

According to simple deduction, the records in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> stated that calamities and tribulations were Gu materials to advance the rank of ability Gu.

Fang Yuan gave it a try right now, but discovered that calamities and tribulations were not suitable as Gu materials and were extremely hard to control. Fortunately, Fang Yuan had made ample preparations and was able to preserve ability Gu.

After obtaining this outcome, Fang Yuan did not hold back and destroyed the final lump of tribulation cloud.

This time, he did not devour the heaven path dao marks.

He left behind the time path dao marks from the tribulation in the time path clone's immortal aperture.

He did not touch the clone's foundation.

"Now, I also have rank eight cultivation." The time path clone was filled with emotions, "From now onwards, I shall use the name He Chun Qiu, what do you think?"

"Up to you." Fang Yuan's main body replied plainly.

Currently, among Fang Yuan's eight clones, Qi Sea Ancestor, Wu Shuai, the time path clone He Chun Qiu, and Zhan Bu Du had advanced to rank eight.

But Fang Yuan already did not lack rank eight Gu Immortals under him at present.

Southern Border.

Human Smoke Mountain.

This was Chai clan's headquarters.

Almost all of Chai clan's Gu Immortals were assembled, and with Chai clan's first supreme elder leading them, they welcomed three variant human Gu Immortals.

These three variant humans were snowman, hairy man, and rockman; they were Bing Yuan, Golden Fur Immortal Monarch, and Shi Zong.

"People of Chai clan, the three of us came with master's order, we are here to discuss a trade with you." As the leader of this trip, Bing Yuan spoke.

Chai clan's immortals were in serious and heavy moods.

It was not only because of Fang Yuan's reputation, but because of these three variant human Gu Immortals' auras.

Be they Bing Yuan or Golden Fur Immortal Monarch or Shi Zong, they were all at rank eight!

"What does Fang Yuan want? Could my Chai clan have something of interest to him?" Chai clan's first supreme elder asked.

"No need to be modest, Lord Chai Gan." Bing Yuan smiled, "My master is willing to purchase your noble clan's human path results, including the killer move congregated human talent, the human path mountain Human Smoke Mountain, as well as many mortals raised by your clan."

"What?!" The expressions of Chai clan's immortals changed.

"Fang Yuan is going too far!"

"He is trying to dig up our Chai clan's foundation."

"The main thing is, if we cooperate with this demon Fang Yuan, what reputation would our grand righteous path Chai clan still have?"

Chai clan immortals criticized softly.

The expression of Chai clan's first supreme elder was unsightly, he muttered for a while before asking: "My Chai clan does nurture the most mortals, these people live good and content lives in Human Smoke Mountain and do not cause trouble for anyone. I wonder what Fang Yuan wants to buy them for?"

Shi Zong sneered: "Of course, to kill them all."

Golden Fur Immortal Monarch had a crazed expression: "These humans your Chai clan is nurturing have abundant human qi, this is extremely good. Master's Human Sea is only lacking the final step. With these people, it can finally be completed."

Chai clan immortals were shaken.

"Disregarding lives so casually, this demon deserves death!!!" One female immortal, Chai Ke Qing, shouted furiously.

Chapter 2138: Shaken Chai Clan

Thousands of years ago.

Southern Border, Human Smoke Mountain.

A cave at the peak of the mountain opened quietly, and an old man walked out of it.

He had an ashen expression.

In the past, he could not find lifespan Gu and could only use other lifespan extension methods. His lifespan was at its end right now, even if he found lifespan Gu or other methods, it would be of no use.

"I, the grand Chai Fu, cultivated to rank eight as a lone cultivator, but in the end, I still lost to lifespan. How sorrowful, how hateful!"

Chai Fu was filled with anger and sadness that was deep as the sea.

He walked down the mountain numbly, but a village at the base of the mountain gave him a surprise.

"Before I went into closed cultivation, there had been no humans inhabiting this place. But in just several years, this place became so lively?"

"I, the grand rank eight Gu Immortal Chai Fu whose name is spread throughout the Southern Border Gu Immortal world, won't live for long, but you mortals are living so well!"

Looking at the men and women in the village doing labor work and children playing around, Chai Fu's anger and hatred surged so much that he was about to slaughter all these villagers.

But at the next moment, he forcibly closed his eyes, his body trembled for a while before he gradually calmed down.

Chai Fu restrained the evil intentions in his heart as he smiled bitterly: "I, Chai Fu, might not be a good person, but I have never targeted people who have not offended me, and have never slaughtered innocents."

"Sigh, so be it if I die. What else can I do?"

"Even the ten venerables were unable to escape death."

"It is easy for Gu Immortals to live long, but how hard is eternal life!"

Chai Fu had looked back over his whole life when he was in closed cultivation. He had no regrets in his life, he had a clean record and was without lingering concerns.

With nothing else to do, Chai Fu disguised as a passing old Gu Master and entered the village.

"Is he a traveling doctor?" The villagers misunderstood Chai Fu's identity.

Chai Fu went with the flow and used that identity, receiving warm welcomes from the villagers.

There were Gu Masters in the village, but the highest was only at rank three, and they were not specialized in healing.

Many villagers asked for help from Chai Fu, and with Chai Fu's ability, it was a small matter for him to treat their illnesses.

Chai Fu was even more revered because of this, and at the same time, he also learned of this village's origin.

"So these people are actually my descendants from over a hundred years ago!"

This discovery made Chai Fu feel some lingering fear and thankfulness. Fortunately, he did not make a move earlier and slaughter them.

Shortly after, Chai Fu began to think about the meaning of life: "Maybe this arrangement of fate is for me to leave behind something."

Chai Fu had already thought of leaving behind his inheritance, and now his thought had solidified.

"It just so happens that I got an inspiration during my closed cultivation and thought of a human path killer move. Looks like fate is never aimless, it wants me to use this move here."

This killer move was congregated human talent!

Chai Fu had been conceptualizing a lifespan extension method, but he did not expect the final result to be this.

Congregated human talent was a human path killer move that could concentrate the aptitude of many people into a small group.

Chai Fu used this move as the foundation and the favorable location of Human Smoke Mountain to establish his super force, Chai clan.

Since the establishment of Chai clan, they had gathered and nurtured outsiders. They then used the killer move congregated human talent to transfer the aptitude of countless outsiders to Chai clansmen.

Thus, geniuses always emerged in Chai clan.

And those outsiders had mediocre aptitude, they could not cause any problems.

Chai clan had this huge advantage and could rise continually, aspiring for the position of number one super force of Southern Border. However, there were Ba clan and Xia clan near Chai clan.

The three clans were near each other and had always been in dispute. Whenever one clan was more powerful, it would be jointly attacked by the other two clans.

Adding on that Chai clan had previously been near the five regional walls and had small territory, it lacked in resources, even though they had a large number of geniuses, they did not have sufficient cultivation resources.

After the five regional walls disappeared, Chai clan became extremely excited. Because they could march towards Central Continent.

However, not long after the regional walls disappeared, qi tides engulfed the world. After the qi tides, inheritances appeared everywhere. All the super forces in five regions, even lone and demonic immortals, were scrambling everywhere for these inheritances.

In fact, even if this wave calmed down, Chai clan would still be in an awkward situation.

Would they dare to attack Central Continent?

Central Continent had the ten great ancient sects, and in terms of strength, they were stronger than Southern Border. Even more terrifying was that Central Continent's ten great ancient sects had the same superior — Heavenly Court!

Central Continent's ten great ancient sects fought each other, but if foreign enemies appeared, they would unite like one body.

And now, Chai clan encountered the greatest danger over the recent years —

Gu Yue Fang Yuan!

Fang Yuan sent three rank eight variant humans to discuss a trade with Chai clan, but their terms were excessive.

Fang Yuan directly asked for congregated human talent, Human Smoke Mountain, as well as the countless outsider mortals that Chai clan was nurturing.

This was directly excavating Chai clan's core foundation that established their status!

It was no wonder everyone in Chai clan looked unsightly, Chai clan's Gu Immortal Chai Ke Qing even shouted in anger: Fang Yuan deserved death!

"Impudent! You dare to curse my master. Looks like your Chai clan is asking for extermination." Shi Zong shouted.

"No need to report to master, us three will attack and exterminate Chai clan now!" Golden Fur Immortal Monarch directly took out his two large hammers with surging killing intent.

The expressions of Chai clan immortals changed intensely, they activated defensive killer moves and rose to the air.

A large chaotic battle seemed to be imminent.

"All of you, stop right now." Bing Yuan stopped the fight with a dark expression.

"Bing Yuan, this..." Shi Zong and Golden Fur Immortal Monarch looked at Bing Yuan.

Bing Yuan was the last to advance to rank eight among the three. Naturally, she had safely passed her tribulation with Fang Yuan's help.

But Bing Yuan was Xue Er's grandmother, and Xue Er had an extremely terrifying identity that made countless Gu Immortals wary.

She was Fang Yuan's fiancée!

Thus, Shi Zong and Golden Fur Immortal Monarch had no questions about Bing Yuan's leadership position among them, and they were obedient too.

"Restrain your aggression first." Bing Yuan spoke.

Shi Zong snorted as he restrained his aura. Golden Fur Immortal Monarch reluctantly put away his hammers while staring at these Chai clan Gu Immortals.

Chai clan's first supreme elder let out a sigh of relief, and under his lead, Chai clan Gu Immortals also returned to ground as a show of sincerity.

Bing Yuan's expression was solemn as she said to the Chai clan immortals: "We did not come here to make enemies out of Chai clan, we indeed came to do a trade."

"My master is a benevolent lord, his demon title is only a misunderstanding by the outside world."

"It is just that those people who misunderstood master did not have a good ending. But what can my master do? Are you going to show your neck and wait for death when others come to kill you? There is no such logic in this world."

"I believe you can understand it and won't add to master's problems."

Bing Yuan's words not only contained threat, she even distorted reality with her words.

Chai Gan did not want to refute, he cupped his fists and said: "I apologize for my clansman's careless remark. But if we agree to your condition, it will be akin to losing the foundation of our clan. Back then, when fate Gu still existed, it was Heavenly Court's foundation. Does this mean Lord Fang Yuan would request to buy fate Gu from Heavenly Court? Would Heavenly Court sell it? Trying to buy a super force's foundation out of nowhere, there is no such logic in this world, isn't that so?"

Bing Yuan smiled coldly: "Chai clan, that is your own problem. Don't try to take advantage of us variant humans, and don't try to take advantage of our master. Our master is benevolent, but besides a fair transaction, do you still want master to help you think of a way to maintain your foundation?"

Golden Fur Immortal Monarch snickered: "Isn't it simple if you want to keep your foundation? Just surrender to our master."

Shi Zong immediately added with sincerity: "Yes. If you become our master's subordinates, your future will be bright. If you keep on living like this, there are no prospects for you."

The three rank eight variant humans revealed proud looks.

They were deeply aware of this over the recent period of time.

Chai clan was silent.

They were using this tactful way to express their refusal.

The three variant human Gu Immortals did not persuade much, let alone elaborate on it. They would rather have fewer competitors.

Bing Yuan continued to urge: "You are all aware in your hearts, if master wants to forcefully demand the resources, he will personally make a move. Why would he send us three to negotiate? Isn't this an unnecessary move? You can rest assure of master's sincerity, take a look."

Bing Yuan opened her hand, revealing a rank eight Immortal Gu.

The Chai clan immortals were stunned and astonished, they transmitted their voices to each other and discussed.

"Fang Yuan is really willing to pay a price?"

"I thought that he was going to demand those things forcefully."

"Be careful, this Gu may be fake. Fang Yuan is crafty and sinister, we cannot be deceived by him!"

After the rapid conversation, Chai Gan shook his head: "It is a good Gu, we can see Lord Fang Yuan's sincerity. But I am ashamed to say that even though I am Chai clan's first supreme elder, my cultivation is only at rank seven, how can I be worthy of a rank eight Immortal Gu?"

Bing Yuan smiled: "Don't be in a hurry to refuse, take a look."

Bing Yuan opened another hand, revealing another Gu.

It was another rank eight Immortal Gu!

This time, many Chai clan Gu Immortals were moved.

Bing Yuan observed their expressions and said with a confident smile: "That's right, you did not see it wrongly. This Immortal Gu is perfect for your Chai clan, this Gu is what your Immortal Gu House lacks. If you add it, your Immortal Gu House will become a rank eight Immortal Gu House."

Chai Gan's grave expression was also somewhat swayed.

If Chai clan had a rank eight Immortal Gu House, they could fight against rank eight Gu Immortals, and even participate in the peak battle between pseudo venerable level existences.

Their power and authority would rise to another level!

It was a qualitative breakthrough!

But at this time, Chai Ke Qing yelled: "Fellow supreme elders, don't be deceived by the demon Fang Yuan and these variant human Gu Immortals. Even if these Immortal Gu are real, our Chai clan belongs to the grand righteous path, how could we lose our identity and honor for benefits! We must never collude with these demons. If we agree to this trade, what difference is there between us and the demonic immortals that we despise? If Ancestor Chai Fu were still alive, he would definitely berate us furiously!"

Chapter 2139: Righteous Speech

"Hahaha." Golden Fur Immortal Monarch laughed, "You are wrong, little girl."

Shi Zong added: "It doesn't hurt to tell you. Your Southern Alliance's leader, Wu Yong, has already traded with us several times. He purchased a rank nine wind path immortal material from us, and also handed rank seven fan wind Gu to us to raise it to rank eight."

"What?" Chai clan's Gu Immortals were shaken.

Bing Yuan smiled: "Demonic path, righteous path, what's the difference? If my master converts to righteous path, who will dare to not accept him? In fact, not only Wu clan, Western Desert's Fang clan is also secretly working with us. Currently, Fang clan is using all their strength to develop green ghost desert and is supplying countless soul cores to master."

There was another round of disturbance among the Chai clan immortals.

They had heard of Western Desert's Fang clan and also knew of their recent movements. What impacted them even more was that Wu clan was secretly cooperating with Fang Yuan.

"How can that be?" Chai Ke Qing called out, "At least try to make a better lie. Lord Wu Yong is our Southern Alliance's leader, how can he reach agreement with you? Everyone, you should not listen to these variant humans' nonsense, they are just making lies to deceive us!"

But this time, Chai clan immortals were silent.

Chai Ke Qing had undergone immortal ascension just recently and had done so through relationships. Although she had talent, she had always been taken care of by Gu Immortal seniors and was not aware of how the world worked.

Her understanding of the Gu Immortal world was even less than Shang Xin Ci.

Since these variant human Gu Immortals said this, Chai clan's immortals believed that it was likely to be true!

Because they only needed to investigate it and would be able to find clues.

Since the variant human Gu Immortals had said it, they were not afraid of being verified, they could even provide direct evidence.

Chai Ke Qing did not believe Wu Yong would do such things, but Chai clan's immortals were people who were experienced and aware of worldly affairs. Not long ago, they themselves had reached an agreement with Lu Wei Yin secretly to leave a way out.

Bing Yuan continued: "My master is determined to create the secluded domain of heaven and earth — Human Sea. I think you all know about master's nature. Even if all the people in the world oppose him, he will do it, he will not give up because someone obstructs him!"

"You can also inquire about the recent events in Eastern Sea."

"We variant human Gu Immortals moved all around in Eastern Sea and slaughtered humans, it was to gather resources to complete Human Sea."

"Did any Eastern Sea righteous path super force oppose us openly?"

"Hehehe. The righteous Qi Alliance even has Qi Sea Ancestor, a pseudo venerable, but he pretended not to see it. Let alone your Southern Alliance."

The will of Chai clan's immortals were shaken, they started conversing secretly.

"There are indeed many tragedies happening in Eastern Sea Gu Immortal world."

"Yes, these variant human Gu Immortals might be detestable, but their words are not without logic."

"Eastern Sea's Righteous Qi Alliance has the pseudo venerable Qi Sea Ancestor, but it still ended up like this. Not to mention our Southern Alliance which doesn't even have such an expert."

"The worst thing is, Wu Yong secretly collaborated with Fang Yuan."

"Fang Yuan's influence is truly terrifying!"

"The enemy is strong while we are weak, it will be sensible to preserve our strength for the future."

No matter how much they hated to admit it, Chai clan knew they were not Fang Yuan's match, they were not even the match of these three rank eight variant humans in front of them. What made them even more hopeless was that even if they retaliated, the Southern Alliance would not provide them any protection. Even if the Southern Alliance provided protection, they would not be able to protect them.

Chai clan's Human Smoke Mountain had countless humans.

If they really fought, these people were Chai clan's weaknesses and Chai clan would not be able to protect them.

In history, when Ba clan and Xia clan caused troubles for Chai clan, they relied on this point, as long as they made a threatening move towards Human Smoke Mountain, Chai clan had to act carefully.

By now, Chai clan was already inclined towards cooperating with Fang Yuan.

There was nothing that could be done about it.

The enemy was strong while they were weaker by a huge degree!

Only Chai Ke Qing was still continuing: "Everyone, listen to me..."

"Shut up!" Chai Gan could not endure it anymore, he waved his hand and sealed Chai Ke Qing, making her unable to even budge.

Chai Ke Qing was shocked, she had never expected her first supreme elder to do this!

This method surprised the three variant human immortals.

When Chai Gan used this move, not even a slight aura leaked out from the start to finish.

Without being able to sense the aura, the three variant human Gu Immortals were unable to judge what path this killer move belonged to.

Chai clan was a Southern Border super force after all, it had some foundation.

Chai Gan's expression was cold as he stared at a Chai clan Gu Immortal: "Chai Dui Shan, control your own descendant."

"Yes." Chai Dui Shan immediately walked towards Chai Ke Qing and placed his hand on her shoulder.

Instantly, the seal on Chai Ke Qing was strengthened further.

Chai Ke Qing's mind shook intensely, her expression was one of incredulity. Her eyes moved towards the side and reddened as she looked at the ancestor that had once been so tall and grand in her heart.

Seeing this, the three variant human Gu Immortals had a similar thought —

The outcome was set!

A day later.

While Chai clan's headquarters were empty, Human Smoke Mountain was attacked by the biggest beast calamity of the past hundred years. An earth path immemorial desolate beast dug out from the ground.

At that time, Chai clan's immortals had gone out to fight for blessed lands, inheritances, and so on, and only a few rank six Gu Immortals were left to guard the headquarters.

In order to protect the common people, the Gu Immortals left behind, with Chai Ke Qing as the head, used killer moves without caring for losses to Chai clan.

This move inflicted damage on both enemies and oneself, although the immemorial desolate beast was killed, Human Smoke Mountain was heavily damaged and was almost turned into a crater.

Fortunately, they were able to protect some clansmen.

"Although there is a difference between immortals and mortals, Chai clan holds no such differentiation."

"Human life is most important, mortal lives are as precious as Gu Immortal lives! Even if we have to sacrifice our lives, it is worth it if we can save more lives."

"This is my Chai clan's principle, it is our integrity as part of the righteous path!"

Chai clan's first supreme elder Chai Gan proclaimed his words that were full of righteousness to Southern Border's Gu Immortal world after the event.

The three variant human immortals set off on a journey back in secret.

Human Smoke Mountain was naturally attacked by them.

According to the agreement between the three variant human immortals and Chai clan, Chai clan sold Human Smoke Mountain as well as most of the mortals on Human Smoke Mountain, only keeping their own clansmen. They also kept some random outsiders to put up a show.

Chai clan Gu Immortals did not make a move, the three variant human immortals dug up Human Smoke Mountain and slaughtered countless mortals.

Lastly, the three immortals took away Chai clan's human path results, while leaving a fire path true inheritance and three rank eight Immortal Gu to Chai clan.

"Hahaha, master's bottom line was five rank eight Immortal Gu for this mission, I did not think we would complete this mission with just three." Shi Zong laughed.

"Even if Chai clan is a super clan and has been in Southern Border for a long time, they are truly inept. Just three rank eight Immortal Gu were enough to blow them away." Golden Fur Immortal Monarch also showed his disdain.

At present, there were over twenty rank eight Immortal Gu listed on the sovereign immortal aperture's exchange list!

These rank eight Immortal Gu were of various paths and could be exchanged for using contribution points!

Fang Yuan had been helping many Gu Immortals undergo tribulation, which spiked the number of rank eight Gu Immortals in the sovereign immortal aperture. Because of this, Fang Yuan put some rank eight Immortal Gu on the exchange list.

This move stimulated all the rank eight Gu Immortals, they were excited to the point of madness.

Even though many Gu Immortals knew clearly: Fang Yuan was dangling a carrot in front of them so that they would work for him like a mule.

But this carrot was too large and too glossy, it really made them salivate!

How hard was it to obtain a rank eight Immortal Gu, how hard was it to refine it?

The Gu Immortals simply could not resist this temptation!

"Congratulations, Bing Yuan, for saving two rank eight Immortal Gu for master. When we return, you will definitely be rewarded with lots of bonus contribution points." Golden Fur Immortal Monarch flattered.

Fang Yuan's task rewards were not fixed, they could change according to the change in situation.

Bing Yuan laughed reservedly: "Actually, I don't care much about contribution points. I saved the two rank eight Immortal Gu not for contribution points, but to help my family. You know that my Xue Er is Lord Fang Yuan's fiancée after all."

"This again."

"Bing Yuan is showing off her relationship with master again!"

Shi Zong and Golden Fur Immortal Monarch looked at each other secretly, seeing the complex emotions in each other's eyes.

They had heard of Bing Yuan mentioning this relationship so many times that they started feeling nauseous. But even so, every time they heard it, Shi Zong and Golden Fur Immortal Monarch could not help but feel envious.

Not willing for Bing Yuan to stay on this topic, Shi Zong said: "Our side is clearly so strong, why do you think master still used such a huge price to trade with Chai clan?"

Golden Fur Immortal Monarch immediately replied: "In my opinion, master traded with Wu clan, Chai clan, and Fang clan, probably because he wants to convert to righteous path."

Shi Zong heaved a sigh: "If I had status and strength like master's, I would run wild, who can stop me? Hehehe, a mere Chai clan will be turned to ashes with just a flick of my finger. Will I still talk business with these people?"

Bing Yuan snorted coldly: "Which is why you will never become an existence like master. Master's considerations are always far-sighted, how can we reckon what he is thinking? If we make guesses, it is no different than ants trying to estimate the sun and moon."

"Yes, yes." Golden Fur Immortal Monarch quickly added, "Actually, even if we turn to righteous path, our lives will be pretty good. Just look at those Chai clan Gu Immortals holding back their anger, it was really refreshing. I, a hairy man, finally get to experience the taste of equality."

The three immortals looked at each other and saw smiles on the others' faces.

Bing Yuan said: "Whether master walks the righteous path or demonic path, we only need to know one thing. That is, we follow master's decision. If master wants to negotiate and do business, then we will do business. If master wants to kill someone, we will go kill that unlucky fellow."

"Naturally!" Golden Fur Immortal Monarch patted his chest strongly.

Shi Zong also nodded, saying with emotions: "In the history of humanity, besides Ren Zu, I only respect master!"

Over this recent period of time, Fang Yuan's subordinates had a huge transformation.

The transformation on the surface was the rapid increase in their cultivation level and strength. And the internal mental transformation was that their loyalty towards Fang Yuan was increasing rapidly.

The authority of the supreme demon, harsh agreements, and terrifying battle achievements made these Gu Immortals feel dread and not dare to rebel. On this basis, Fang Yuan only needed to give some benefits and these Gu Immortals would feel deeply grateful to him!

And currently, Fang Yuan's treatment towards them was something the other forces simply could not match.

Such huge benefits made these Gu Immortals gather tightly around Fang Yuan.

Chapter 2140: Establishing Dao Veins

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

A huge butterfly was fluttering in the air.

This butterfly was pure-white and let out graceful cloud light. Its speed was sometimes fast, sometimes slow; when it was fast, it was almost like teleportation, and when it was slow, it moved leisurely like fluttering leaves.

This was a totem killer move — Cloud Light Butterfly.

The totem killer moves Zhan Bu Du brought from Myriad Beast Fusion Color Heaven had extremely high value.

Based on their grades, these totem killer moves were divided into: basic totems, unique totems, and super totems.

There were thousands of basic totems, including dark capital strength tiger, golden bell totem, rain eagle totem and so on.

After the cultivators of Myriad Beast Fusion Color Heaven refined a basic totem, they continued to develop the totem, making it a totem unique to them.

These totems were different for different Gu Immortals.

For instance, Zhan Bu Du combined rain eagle and thunder fish into kunpeng totem, which was his unique totem. It could not be copied by others because this totem was closely related to the distribution and scale of Zhan Bu Du's dao marks.

Above unique totems were super totems.

There were extremely few of these totems and they were rare to the point of being only rumors and legends.

Zhan Bu Du only heard of them and had not seen any.

Many Gu cultivators of Myriad Beast Fusion Color Heaven also were doubtful regarding this grade of totem.

But in Fang Yuan's opinion, they should exist.

"According to legends, super totems can leave the Gu cultivator and exist by themselves, they possess the ability to cultivate and can act by themselves. Isn't this speaking of Qing Chou?"

Qing Chou was originally a killer move, but through Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's arrangements, it turned into an immemorial desolate beast.

Even the grand Spectral Soul went down because of Qing Chou.

All the myriad paths reached the same point in the end.

When totem killer moves were cultivated to the limit, they would be like Qing Chou, transforming from a dead killer move to a certain living form.

From another angle, Gu refinement was also the same.

Gu cultivators refined many dead Gu materials into a living Gu worm.

And Gu worms and killer moves were the same in essence.

Life, Gu worms, killer moves, and others, they were just a manifestation of 'Dao'.

"Unfortunately, I still cannot improve totem killer moves into compound killer moves at the moment." Fang Yuan sighed inwardly.

When totem killer moves were used to deal with the enemies, they had to leave the sovereign immortal body and would no longer be under the protection of unrestrained heavenly marks.

"Maybe in the future, when my heaven path attainment increases, I can use heaven path dao marks with totem killer moves to create compound totem killer moves."

Fang Yuan already made some estimations.

His heaven path attainment level needed to increase.

In fact, his heaven path attainment had been rising all along.

He was continuously refining heaven path dao marks into unrestrained heavenly marks, and was using heaven path Gu like heaven's envy Immortal Gu, these experiences gave him insights towards heaven path.

But his heaven path was still far from reaching master level.

Master level heaven path attainment was the starting point for qualitative change.

Fang Yuan continued to cultivate totem killer moves.

So far, he was accumulating totem killer moves.

Fang Yuan carefully selected these totem killer moves from the basic totems, and after perfecting them, they were at rank eight killer move level.

A message appeared that disturbed Fang Yuan's cultivation.

Fang Yuan stopped his cultivation and inspected this message.

This message came from Lu Wei Yin.

The letter focused on the method of artificially creating earth veins.

"My thought of modifying the sovereign immortal aperture is possible after all." Fang Yuan thought with some joy.

Over this period of time, Fang Yuan had published the exchange list and invested greatly to nurture his subordinate Gu Immortals. Because of this, Fang Yuan's subordinates had a huge increase in their strength, they became extremely active and took the initiative to do missions everywhere.

The sovereign immortal aperture's situation had already stabilized.

Fang Yuan estimated he could annex three more grotto-heavens before the ecosystem started breaking down again.

But Fang Yuan was not satisfied with this.

It was best if he could devour all the grotto-heavens and increase his strength to the limit before the battle in Crazed Demon Cave.

When he goes to Crazed Demon Cave in the future and faces off against venerables, he would have a much easier time.

However, even if Fang Yuan placed all the variant human alliance Gu Immortals inside the sovereign immortal aperture, including Qi Sea Ancestor to overlook the whole situation, he could not annex all the two heavens' grotto-heavens.

Even if he could do so, Fang Yuan would not do it.

If he did it, the sovereign immortal aperture's ecosystem would turn completely chaotic, and with just a little carelessness, it would break apart.

Currently, Fang Yuan was in a secure environment and there was already this threat. When he fights with venerables and they discover this weakness, they may have some special methods to exploit this weakness.

In fact, Fang Yuan's silver luck pillar was loose and not condensed, it was hinting to Fang Yuan that this obvious weakness was very likely to be used by venerables.

Just relying on manpower did not work, Fang Yuan racked his brains and finally thought of another method.

That was to construct veins!

Heaven had heaven veins, earth had earth veins, and humans had human veins.

The so-called vein was extraordinary and special, not only was it an agglomeration of dao marks, but it also contained the characteristics of movement.

Heaven veins might be formless, but they contained abundant heaven path dao marks. At the same time, these heaven path dao marks were not constantly unchanging, they circulated and transformed continuously.

So when qi tides swept the world, there were qi harvest fruits every time they dissipated. And in the two heavens, because almost all the grotto-heavens were placed on a heaven vein node, the qi harvest fruits' emergence became even more obvious, turning into a calamity.

Earth veins were similar.

After the pursuit battle against Fang Yuan, earth veins appeared and spread throughout the five regions. Fang Yuan, Lu Wei Yin, and others used the characteristic of the earth vein movement to escape smoothly.

Why were there abnormal situations occurring in Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture?

What was the truth and source of it?

Where was the crux of the issue?

When Fang Yuan researched it, the answer he got was very thought-provoking.

The answer was — the non-conflicting dao marks of the sovereign immortal aperture!

By right, there should be conflict between different dao marks. But there was none of it in the sovereign immortal aperture, dao marks of all paths were harmonious.

Excessive harmony was not a good thing.

There was no absolute good or bad in the world!

Just like when Ni clan encountered the meteor calamity.

This meteor calamity was extremely destructive and Fang Yuan had to personally make a move to resolve it.

The source of this meteor calamity was just a spurt of fire rain in Mini Red Heaven.

After Fang Yuan annexed Fire Plain grotto-heaven, his fire path dao marks had a massive surge which caused frequent fire rain in Mini Red Heaven.

And among all the fire rain, one spell continued to grow and happened to shoot through a charcoal lake.

The fire rain's dao marks and charcoal lake's dao marks merged together, forming rank six level killer move meteor rain.

As the meteor rain entered Mini Orange Heaven, it combined with the dao marks on its way and its strength increased to rank seven level.

As it entered Mini Yellow Heaven, it combined with metal path dao marks and its might increased to rank eight.

When it was above the Ni clan army, the scale of these meteors was already dense enough to fill the sky, reaching tens of thousands!

The smallest were only the size of a small field, while some were as large as a mountain.

If there was the presence of conflicting dao marks, this calamity would have not occurred. It was very likely that when the fire rain shot through the charcoal lake, it would be restrained by the earth path dao marks in the charcoal lake, its might would fall sharply and it would end there.

But because of the harmony between dao marks in the sovereign immortal aperture, after the fire rain went through the charcoal lake, it became meteor fire rain.

After Fang Yuan realized this crucial point, he understood how to end the issues in the sovereign immortal aperture.

It was simple, that was to make the dao marks in the sovereign immortal aperture conflict!

Once there were conflicting dao marks, the sovereign immortal aperture's biggest issue would be solved easily, it would be stable like the outside world's five regions.

Lu Wei Yin's letter also confirmed Fang Yuan's idea.

He mentioned: When Shadow Sect refined sovereign immortal fetus Gu, Mushroomman Paradise had also secretly helped.

Spectral Soul might or might not have realized this issue.

But that was not important.

Spectral Soul and Paradise Earth might oppose each other, but they reached a tacit agreement through Red Lotus Demon Venerable because of fate Gu.

Lu Wei Yin analyzed: the fundamental reason for sovereign immortal fetus Gu being rank nine was non-conflicting dao marks. But if it were to be taken a step further and raised to rank ten, the dao marks had to conflict.

This conflict was not taking a step back, but instead, to make the sovereign immortal body's dao marks follow the master's intention, it could either be non-conflicting or conflicting dao marks at will!

Making the dao marks conflict could resolve the sovereign immortal body's greatest flaw — strong attack, weak defense!

However, Fang Yuan clearly did not have enough capability to accomplish this.

Even Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was unable to do this.

After all, that would not be rank nine sovereign immortal fetus Gu, but rank ten!

Rank nine Immortal Gu were already rare and mighty, rank ten was only a rumor of legends.

Fang Yuan had lived for hundreds of years but had only heard rumors of two rank ten Immortal Gu.

One was destiny Gu, one of the main materials for refining rank ten destiny Gu was rank nine fate Gu.

Another was eternal Gu. This legend originated from \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

Currently, from Lu Wei Yin's letter, Fang Yuan learned of the possible third rank ten Immortal Gu — sovereign immortal fetus Gu!

Fang Yuan could not accomplish conflicting dao marks, then what should he do?

Easy!

Since he could not create conflicting dao marks, Fang Yuan went to the extreme, to make dao marks even more harmonious and condense them.

But this cohesion and harmony was selective, and would be under Fang Yuan's control.

What was the solution?

Fang Yuan did not need to think much before the method of vein construction emerged in his mind.

There were many kinds of dao veins.

Heaven vein, earth vein, human vein, fire vein, water vein, and so on.

In Eastern Sea, undercurrents interwove under the sea, forming a natural route for transportation of goods. Many of Eastern Sea's caravans made use of Gu worms to go deep under the sea and used the undercurrents to move rapidly, in a short time, they could travel for ten thousand li, or even a hundred thousand li, to engage in trade.

This was actually one of the forms of water veins.

Southern Border's Paradise Earth true inheritance naturally contained the way to construct artificial earth vein. But Fang Yuan still wanted to consult Lu Wei Yin regarding the specific way to put it into practice.

Regarding him and Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, Fang Yuan was always on guard.

For instance, Fang Yuan had never let Lu Wei Yin enter the sovereign immortal aperture. Or for example, Fang Yuan preserved Paradise Earth's dream realms and Mushroomman Paradise, he did not make a move on them without deep consideration.

"Adding in Lu Wei Yin's suggestion, I can modify my previous idea and get an overall mature way to implement it. I can let those Gu Immortals finish the early steps."

"Or maybe, I should let Meng Qiu Zhen explore Paradise Earth's dream realms first and raise my earth path attainment, which would make it much more convenient for constructing the earth vein."

Chapter 2141: Fang Huan's Revival

Central Continent.

In the depths of an Earth Trench.

Inside a pitch-black cave, two cold rays of light shone suddenly.

This was Bai Ning Bing's gaze.

As she ended this closed cultivation session, she had not only created an ice path killer move, but also gained some insight towards ice path.

"I can clearly feel my understanding of ice and snow deepening by a little, I am not far from grandmaster level." Bai Ning Bing mumbled.

"Such a pity that after I converted to dragonman, my comprehension speed of ice and snow path fell sharply. My current master level is mostly the accumulation from before."

Previously, Bai Ning Bing possessed Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique and had an extremely high innate advantage when cultivating ice path and soul path. Her attainment levels in those paths could increase rapidly.

But after converting her body, it influenced this aspect.

Dragonman was specialized in enslavement path, if Bai Ning Bing were to change to cultivating enslavement path, she would have an advantage in it. But the level of this advantage could not compare to the help the Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique provided in cultivating ice path and soul path.

Man was the spirit of all living beings, the talent of the ten extreme physiques was far superior to the talents of the variant human races.

Bai Ning Bing cautiously walked out of the cave.

This cave was formed naturally and was at the side of a cliff in the Earth Trench.

Bai Ning Bing activated breath concealment ice pearl, shortly after, an ice thread-like thin line appeared on her slender and fair neck, circling around it.

This move was created by Bai Ning Bing and was not from Bai Xiang's true inheritance.

The killer move did not let out any aura when activated. Because the aura was stored as tiny ice pearls on the ice thread.

The disadvantage of this move was that it sacrificed some of its power, and once there were too many ice pearls, they would combine into one and turn into a noose that would strangle Bai Ning Bing, causing serious injuries or even death.

"I must conceal my aura when exploring this deep into the Earth Trench." Bai Ning Bing's expression was calm as she quietly activated an investigative killer move to scout her surroundings.

After she left the Earth Treasury, she started cultivating in the depths of the Earth Trench. She was chased down by wild beast groups and suffered a lot.

Fortunately, with the killer move Bai Xiang, as long as a fragment of her body remained, Bai Ning Bing was undying, otherwise, she would not have survived until now.

"There are three immemorial desolate beasts within a hundred li radius, as well as an ancient desolate beast group." Bai Ning Bing quickly understood her surroundings.

She only had rank seven cultivation, it was extremely dangerous for her to live in this environment. Even ordinary rank eight Gu Immortals found it difficult to explore this place.

With huge risks came huge rewards.

The cultivation resources here were at rank eight level. Even if Bai Ning Bing could not use them, she could sell them in treasure yellow heaven and buy the resources she needed.

Bai Ning Bing liked taking risks, most people would be on tenterhooks about this kind of life, but she immersed in it and enjoyed the thrill of being at the brink of life and death.

"Although it is dangerous to cultivate here, there is still a chance of survival. But in the five regions and two heavens, it is even more dangerous, be they Fang Yuan, Shadow Sect, or Heavenly Court, they will all hunt me down."

Bai Ning Bing had a clear judgment of her situation.

"Hmm?" Bai Ning Bing had just walked out of the cave when her expression changed slightly.

She sensed that most of the wild beasts suddenly acted like cats that had smelled fish, beginning to rush towards one direction.

Some beasts and beast groups were unmoved, but they were soon engulfed by the will of the majority of the beasts and rushed forward as well.

Thereupon, a massive beast tide formed rapidly under Bai Ning Bing's gaze.

"What's going on? These beasts seem to be attracted to something, they gave up on their fights and territories to go after it. What could it be?"

Bai Ning Bing could not help but feel curious.

Without any hesitation, she immediately activated a movement killer move as she joined the beast tide.

The beast tide started gathering together, countless ancient desolate beasts and some conspicuous immemorial desolate beasts were surrounding an area.

This area was also on the precipice of the Earth Trench, it protruded slowly like a burial mound. At this moment, it was letting out yellowish-brown and red light.

The light was like water as it moved around dazzlingly.

On the peak of the burial mound, there was a tombstone! The tombstone seemed to have writings but they were obstructed by the light. They could not be seen even by using investigative killer moves.

Bai Ning Bing had already transformed into Bai Xiang state and joined with the beast groups.

"What place is this? There is such a dense earth path and fire path aura here. What is hiding here? Immortal materials? Or Immortal Gu?"

"But why is there a tombstone? The tombstone seems to have some characters written on it. Is it made by someone? Who is buried there?"

Bai Ning Bing looked at the surrounding beasts.

She had a trace of understanding: "Most of these beasts are earth path and fire path beasts, no wonder they were attracted here. There are only beasts of other paths here and they were forcefully pulled in by the beast tide."

Boom!

Right at this time, the two lights over the burial mound suddenly shot towards the sky, turning into a giant yellow-red pillar of light.

The beasts roared in excitement.

Some beasts began to charge towards the pillar as if trying to get the top spot, but they were soon knocked down and trampled by the beasts behind them.

The beast groups fell into chaos and madness, fighting and killing each other as they charged towards the pillar of light.

But even if some beasts reached the front and collided with the pillar, they did not get what they wanted. The pillar of light remained unmoving, it was like a large mountain that refused to budge an inch.

Bai Ning Bing was a Gu Immortal and had intelligence far above the beasts. She hid outside the chaotic battle, and although she was still implicated, she mainly observed the changes.

As time passed, there were heavy casualties among the beast groups with corpses scattered everywhere. The yellow-red pillar of light also started to shrink, seemingly converging into the burial mound.

The beasts became even more frantic, their bloodthirsty, pained, and chewing noises filled Bai Ning Bing's ears.

"This vast world is truly profound without limits and it has endless mysteries to explore. Let me see what is going on." Bai Ning Bing began to move closer towards the mound.

When the beasts had killed each other and the survivors were riddled with injuries, the yellow-red light was completely absorbed by the mound.

The tombstone on the mound also dug into the earth.

The mound seemed to have reached the point of qualitative change as it suddenly split apart.

Crack crack.

Thin cracks spread all over the mound.

Shortly after, the mound burst open from the inside and a Gu Immortal's aura leaked towards the surroundings.

A naked male immortal opened his eyes and looked at his surroundings in a daze: "Who... who am I?"

But at the next moment, he started becoming clear-headed as he recalled many things.

"I, I remember, I am Fang Huan." The male immortal's eyes shrunk in amazement and shock.

Roar—!

Beast groups roared and pounced towards the naked immortal agitatedly.

The male immortal opened his eyes wide and flew to the air: "I am alive again! I am Fang Huan, I am — Lava Demon Lord!"

Bam!

A huge sound erupted as red light waves spread from the male immortal's body.

The light waves surged like a tsunami, drowning its surroundings.

Everywhere they passed by, the red light waves burned everything; most of the beast groups were burned to death instantly, and some of the surviving beasts were even more injured. Some were lying on the ground on the verge of death, while a small portion of the beasts went berserk as they charged towards the male immortal.

The male immortal Fang Huan's expression turned solemn as he let out the red light waves again.

The red light swept the whole battlefield, causing a large number of casualties, but there were still several immemorial desolate beasts that managed to reach Fang Huan.

Fang Huan could not keep his composure anymore as he shouted towards Bai Ning Bing: "Lend me a hand. I will reward you heavily after this!"

"Okay." Bai Ning Bing agreed without hesitation and attacked directly.

Within a short period of time, she easily killed those several immemorial desolate beasts.

It was because they were already heavily injured.

"Many thanks, friend! Fortunately, with your help, I could... ahh!" Fang Huan was suddenly cut into two at the waist.

Bai Ning Bing grabbed his head, holding his upper body as she smiled cruelly: "I thought about it, it is still more convenient to soul search directly."

Fang Huan stared at Bai Ning Bing with wide eyes.

This female immortal had light-blue vertical dragon pupils and had a pair of spiral dragon horns. Her glistening silver hair was shiny like crystal, extending to her waist. Her skin was snow-white, and on her peerlessly beautiful face, there was a hint of crazed indifference.

"Such a beautiful woman..." Fang Huan died with his eyes wide open

Bai Ning Bing searched Fang Huan's soul but was unable to obtain any valuable information. Although Fang Huan revived in the mound, he was still muddle-headed and did not know many things.

Bai Ning Bing landed on the broken mound and searched carefully.

There were still no gains.

"This area had such a large scale of earth path and fire path dao marks, but they have disappeared completely, and it is no different from ordinary ground now."

But Bai Ning Bing looked at Fang Huan's body: "No, to be more accurate, these dao marks condensed into the immortal body."

"Wonderful, truly amazing." Bai Ning Bing praised repeatedly.

Through soul search, she knew this Fang Huan was from a previous generation. He cultivated earth path, but later inherited heart fire true inheritance, so cultivated fire path as well. He did fire monster business and had been one of the tycoons of this business in treasure yellow heaven.

He had died long ago, but for some reason, he actually revived!

"This grave-like mound seems to have the same effect as Heavenly Court's immortal graveyard, it can let Gu Immortals revive?!" Bai Ning Bing was excited about this discovery.

She had made a huge gain this time.

Not only did she discover the mysterious mound, she also captured Fang Huan's soul and obtained his inheritance as well as cultivation insights.

The even bigger battle spoils were the beast corpses that filled the battlefield.

There were many rank eight immortal materials here! Rank seven immortal materials were even higher in number.

Sovereign immortal aperture, Mini Southern Border.

Rumble!

With a loud sound, a mountain landed on the ground like a large stamp.

The famous mountain was red and squarish. This mountain did not have even a trace of soil, it was completely formed from all kinds of copper. It was Copper Seal mountain.

Previously, Copper Seal mountain was targeted by the tribulation of the three thousand heaven path dao marks, half of it was split by the lightning, giving out dense smoke and sparks. The entire mountain had turned into a molten state and emitted a terrible smell.

But now, after Fang Yuan issued the corresponding missions, Copper Seal mountain was repaired by many Gu Immortals. It was not only restored to its former state, it was even larger now.

Chapter 2142: Ideas About Resources

"Alright, we have finally moved this Copper Seal mountain now." The exhausted Gu Immortals let out breaths of relief.

One rockman Gu Immortal did not rest and began to prepare.

After a long while, he activated an earth path killer move.

Under the effect of this killer move, Copper Seal mountain seemed to shake slightly. The base of the mountain started emitting a thin earthen-yellow radiance.

The threads of light gathered and formed a translucent, golden earth path mountain root.

The mountain root pierced the ground and began to spread quickly.

The rockman Gu Immortal continued to maintain the killer move, he had an expression of difficulty, his immortal essence was consumed rapidly.

Finally, he could no longer continue and stopped the killer move.

The mountain root stopped spreading rapidly and paused. It had entered deep underground and began to grow with normal speed.

In the coming years, this mountain root would join with the surrounding dao marks, maintaining and helping to stabilize Copper Seal mountain.

Trees had tree roots, while mountains had mountain roots. If they were casually moved, the roots could be broken and result in their destruction.

Therefore, moving famous trees and mountains required special wood path and earth path methods, otherwise, there were more disadvantages than advantages in moving them forcefully.

The rockman Gu Immortal sat cross-legged on the ground and started to recover.

He was extremely tired, his immortal essence expenditure was also the highest among the immortals. Naturally, after the mission completion, his contribution points would be that much higher as well.

As for the other Gu Immortals, they had finished resting and started to carry out the final inspection.

After a while, the immortals gathered once again.

"That will do, this Copper Seal mountain's state is good."

"The mountain root's situation is also pretty good. Such a famous mountain and mountain root can completely bear the task of being an earth vein node."

"Master is truly majestic and bold. He is actually constructing an earth vein in the entire mini five regions. This plan is really too grand and will need at least ten years to complete. It really makes me admire him endlessly."

The immortals nodded, they had the same feeling.

"Alright, let's leave. We need to relocate the next famous mountain."

"There are not many Gu Immortals who can relocate mountains, but there will be fewer tasks like this as we continue finishing them, the contribution points are also abundant. Let's work hard and try to finish some more."

"Yes, yes. Recently, if someone cannot continue, they will make a trip to the liver life formation. No one wants to give up on those contribution points!"

"I already went before this."

"Haha, is that so? I also went there!"

The immortals left Copper Seal mountain while conversing.

If the mini five regions were looked from high above, one would see about ten groups of people working hard to relocate mountains.

Of course, it was not just famous mountains.

Besides famous mountains, there were also the ten earths that could act as earth vein nodes.

There was a detailed description regarding ten earths in Southern Border's Paradise Earth true inheritance.

The ten earths were: Earth Abyss, Earth Trench, Earth Tunnel, Earth Cave, Earth Prison, Production Earth, Flying Earth, Formation Earth, Treasure Earth, and Tomb Earth.

These ten earths could bear the task of being earth vein nodes.

The first step in Fang Yuan's artificial earth vein construction was to arrange all kinds of earth vein nodes in the mini five regions. He would then use earth path methods to connect the nodes. Lastly, he would make adjustments.

Currently, Fang Yuan could only create half of the ten earths: Earth Abyss, Earth Trench, Earth Tunnel, Production Earth, and Formation Earth.

The other five earths were beyond his ability.

For example: Tomb Earth.

The formation of this earth was shrouded in mystery, even Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable could not see through it.

Gu Immortals could revive in this area.

Tomb Earth's tombstone was also extremely mysterious, possessing the ability of information path. It seemed to be able to extract and condense all the information of the Gu Immortal's life from the River of Time.

The greater the reputation of the Gu Immortal, the more detailed the writings on the tombstone, which seemed to provide more help towards the Gu Immortal's revival.

The specific relation between them had to be verified.

At present, Fang Yuan's subordinates were all moving mountains.

Mountains usually acted as earth vein nodes and not the ten earths.

These mountains needed to be at least of famous mountain level.

"There are not many famous mountains in the sovereign immortal aperture. I estimate they can only cover thirty percent of the earth vein nodes in the first step of the plan."

The artificial earth vein project was extremely large and needed the most investment. Fang Yuan had annexed a large number of grotto-heavens and obtained an inestimable amount of cultivation resources, but now, he was starting to see the limits.

Fang Yuan still had a famous mountain which he did not use.

That was the recently obtained Human Smoke Mountain!

"It is better to keep this mountain. My intuition is telling me that if I continue to use Chai clan's human path research results, I will be able to condense the essence of Human Smoke Mountain and form an incomplete Human Mountain!"

Fang Yuan was a human path grandmaster, his intuition regarding human path was much more accurate than human path masters.

After killing many mortals raised by Chai clan, Human Sea was complete, but Human Mountain had yet to form.

The combination of Human Mountain and Human Sea would definitely be extremely powerful. Even in five hundred years of his previous life, Fang Yuan had not seen it.

But this was a long-term project.

The investment in constructing a secluded domain of heaven and earth was extremely big, much bigger than the investment in an artificial earth vein!

The reason the incomplete Human Sea could be completed was because there were the painstaking accumulations of Eastern Sea's Xia clan.

It was at its final stage and required human path resources.

Eastern Sea's Xia clan suffered from their righteous path identity and could only collect the resources secretly. How could they dare to be like Fang Yuan, killing and massacring openly!

Firstly, Fang Yuan chose the targets of slaughter cleverly, he did not cross the limits of the Righteous Qi Alliance, they ignored it.

Later, he paid attention to Chai clan's mortals.

Fang Yuan decisively gave up on a portion of the benefits to negotiate forcefully. Even a super clan like Chai clan finally submitted to Fang Yuan's demonic might, lowering their head to cooperate.

"I am starting to lack resources." Fang Yuan frowned slightly.

The plan of constructing Human Mountain was definitely far away in the future.

In fact, the incomplete Refinement Sea was also on the verge of being consumed.

Fang Yuan had invested too much in this recent period of time.

In fact, he had looted countless cultivation resources. These resources mostly came from two heavens' grotto-heavens, which had a long history spanning several hundreds of thousands of years, and even a million years.

But it would not last long!

Fang Yuan had been refining rank eight Immortal Gu on a large scale, at the same time, he used rank six and rank seven cultivation resources to nurture his subordinates.

Fang Yuan had too many Gu Immortals under him!

Just Lang Ya Sect alone had many hairy man Gu Immortals, the variant human alliance had even more Gu Immortals. There was also the group of variant human Gu Immortals like Bing Yuan, Shi Zong and Mo Tan Sang.

Beast Calamity grotto-heaven's human Gu Immortals were close to ten, including Combat Beast King.

And there was also Lady White Rabbit, Fairy Miao Yin, as well as Fang Yuan's clones Wu Shuai, Zhan Bu Du, and others.

Not long ago, mushroomman Gu Immortals joined him. Among them, the strongest was Ke Xin Hong.

The size of Fang Yuan's subordinate Gu Immortals far surpassed normal super forces. Even Longevity Heaven could not compare to him, that was to say, only the former Shadow Sect that had Zombie Alliance, and Heavenly Court that had the ten great ancient sects under it, could compare to him.

Were Wu clan to possess this many Gu Immortals, Wu Yong might be laughing happily even in his dreams. A formidable character like Wu Yong did not care about the difference in races, he only cared if they were usable or not. Naturally, it would be better if they were all human Gu Immortals.

Fang Yuan was expanding so much that no amount of cultivation resources would be enough for him to use.

Fortunately, his foundation was extremely robust and could last for this long.

But now, it was beginning to show signs of exhaustion.

"Looks like I need to plunder resources again." Although his accumulations were still there, Fang Yuan was preparing for the future.

"I have already looted the resources of the variant human alliance. Only a portion of the grotto-heavens remain now."

"Mushroomman Paradise's situation is also the same. Almost all the mushroommen have moved over, let alone the resources accumulated there."

Fang Yuan analyzed.

He had placed his hopes on Myriad Beast Fusion Color Heaven, but from the information Zhan Bu Du brought, Fang Yuan knew Longevity Heaven had placed its forces in Myriad Beast Fusion Color Heaven.

Myriad Beast Fusion Color Heaven itself was very powerful and was difficult to conquer. There were definitely forces eyeing it other than Longevity Heaven.

So, although that place had plenty of resources, Fang Yuan did not want to target it at the moment.

Eastern Sea's blue dragon whale also had abundant resources.

But it was also not possible.

Ever since the last time he left, Fang Yuan had not been able to find any traces of the blue dragon whale.

He had used the killer move heaven and earth travel to try to enter the blue dragon whale's immortal aperture, but failed mysteriously every time.

"There is still a group of two heavens' grotto-heavens who submitted to Qi Sea Ancestor, they are all humans. These grotto-heavens also have plenty of cultivation resources. Maybe, I can cooperate with Qi Sea clone."

For the moment, Fang Yuan did not want to invade super forces like Chai clan and Wu clan.

That would expend his own luck.

Any super force possessed enormous luck and had a few tricks up their sleeves.

There might not be many benefits and the risks were definitely huge. More importantly, even if he invaded super forces, Fang Yuan did not want to take over too much of the outside world's territories.

It was much better to develop the sovereign immortal aperture, both his territories and himself were in one body, it was extremely flexible and convenient.

Other Gu Immortals did not have the sovereign immortal aperture, so it was more beneficial for them to occupy territories. If they possessed the sovereign immortal aperture, they might also make the same choice as Fang Yuan.

A strong wind suddenly blew over from Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool and charged towards the skies before dissipating.

He Chun Qiu brought good news, Wu clan's fan wind Gu was advanced successfully, though it failed two times in the process.

Rank eight fan wind Gu!

In recent times, Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool had gone through some adjustments and its ability was much stronger now.

Including fan wind Gu, Fang Yuan had already refined over fifty rank eight Immortal Gu with Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool.

"I can sell true inheritances on a large scale in treasure yellow heaven and exchange for cultivation resources. The profits from doing Gu refinement business are also quite amazing." Fang Yuan thought of two ways to gather resources.

According to Fang Yuan's current refinement path strength, he was only unable to refine rank nine and rank ten Immortal Gu, as well as some specific rank eight Immortal Gu.

For instance, Fang Yuan lacked sufficient rank eight luck path immortal materials for fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu.

Chapter 2143: Tiger Poison Gu

"You have only seven days left to live!"

Meng Qiu Zhen entered Paradise Earth's dream realm, what welcomed him was this sentence.

"What?" Meng Qiu Zhen blurted out in astonishment.

In front of him was an old mushroomman granny.

She sighed and said in a guilty tone: "Little Mi, your grandmother is too useless, I really have no way to treat your illness."

Using this short time, Meng Qiu Zhen quickly scanned his surroundings. He found that not only was there a mushroomman in front of him, he himself was also a mushroomman.

And right now, they were in a hut that was specific to mushroomman culture.

This hut had deep-green walls, it was constructed with special grass and mud. The roof of the hut was made with straws.

The furnishings inside the hut were simple and revealed this was a doctor's home.

"Grandma, is it really hopeless? Is there really no other way?" Meng Qiu Zhen pretended to be in disbelief while trying hard to find clues regarding this dream realm.

The mushroomman granny hesitated for a moment before saying: "There is a way."

Meng Qiu Zhen immediately asked: "What way?"

The mushroomman granny shook her head and walked towards a table.

There were medicine pots all over the table; some were white, some were gray, but most were black.

Some of these medicine pots were opened, they were filled with dried medicinal herbs or pitch-black medicinal liquid. Whereas some medicine pots were covered tightly with lids.

The old granny seemed to be in a complicated mood, she subconsciously moved these medicine pots before gradually calming down.

With her back towards Meng Qiu Zhen, she said: "The one thing I can think of that can possibly save you is not a method, but a person."

"A person?" Meng Qiu Zhen got near to the old granny, he saw these medicine pots actually contained Gu worms.

The old granny sighed: "Sigh, you know her too."

Meng Qiu Zhen had no idea who she meant, but he had plenty of experience and developed quite a glib tongue, he said: "Could it be her?"

"Indeed, her. My tribe's previous witch, Huang Wan," said the old granny.

Every mushroomman tribe had a witch. Different from the merman tribe's saintess, witches did not hold authority, but they usually had high reputation.

Because witches were the most capable female doctors in the mushroomman tribe.

Without the witch's support and blessing, the mushroomman's next tribe leader would face questioning and might even be unable to take the position.

"You only have hope of survival by looking for the previous witch, Huang Wan." The old granny emphasized.

Meng Qiu Zhen immediately asked: "Then, where is she?"

"Whip Mountain." The old granny looked at Meng Qiu Zhen: "Little Mi, you are a good child, I have watched you grow up. The plague is terrorizing the tribe but you should not have been infected, it was because you helped me treat others of your own accord that you got infected. You also know a thing or two about Huang Wan's matter. Although she is extremely strong, she betrayed the tribe, so you can only go look for her personally. The tribe won't help you."

Meng Qiu Zhen nodded, he keenly sensed that the old granny had some hidden meaning behind her words.

He suddenly had a flash of inspiration and asked: "But grandma, I simply cannot reach there with my strength. I must see Huang Wan to obtain her help. Not only to keep my life, but more than that, I want to bring back a way to treat the illness!"

"Good child, good child." The old granny was relieved, "That is what I want you to do. Rest assured, you are taking the risk to go to Whip Mountain, your journey will be filled with dangers and Whip Mountain is moreover a human territory. How can I, your grandmother, let you go like that?"

The old granny turned sideways and opened all of the medicine pots on the table: "You can take three of the Gu worms here. They will provide a huge help to you."

"Many thanks, grandma!" Meng Qiu Zhen said while thinking: It was like this indeed.

He had plenty of experiences in exploring dream realms. With just this conversation, he had already probed the key of this dream realm stage.

"The crucial hidden point of this stage of the dream realm is the selection of Gu."

"If I did not sense the old granny's hidden meaning and mentioned it, I might not have gotten the chance to select Gu."

"Choosing three Gu worms will definitely lower the difficulty of the dream realm."

"But which three would be better for me?"

Meng Qiu Zhen carefully observed the Gu worms while secretly activating dream butterfly Immortal Gu.

With the help of dream butterfly Immortal Gu, Meng Qiu Zhen soon found various clues of the second stage.

"Choose quickly, stop wasting time needlessly. You need to treasure every breath of time you have." The old granny urged.

Meng Qiu Zhen said through clenched teeth: "Grandma, let me consider for a bit longer."

The old granny said with a cold face: "Hmph, you are already in this situation, you must be decisive. Choose three Gu worms immediately, then leave the valley through this secret passage. If this time passes, that passage will be closed for seven days. Choose quickly!"

Meng Qiu Zhen was not able to put it off any longer, but fortunately, he had already gotten much information in this short period of time.

"I choose these three." Meng Qiu Zhen quickly chose three Gu from the tens of medicine pots.

"Good. You chose well. Huang Xiao Mi, time is pressing, I can only help you till here, leave now!" The old granny's voice had just ended when Meng Qiu Zhen's sight turned dark.

The dream realm entered the second stage.

He had rank three cultivation, and using his Gu worms as well as the three new Gu, he traveled rapidly through the mountains, although it was arduous.

He walked through the dangerous man-eating forest, passed the high fog, and crossed the death marsh. He was now facing his final obstacle, a thousand beast king level black bear.

Meng Qiu Zhen fought a long and bitter battle with the black bear.

Finally, the black bear collapsed on the ground.

Its thick body shrank within a few breaths of time like a balloon that was poked.

In just a short while, its blood, flesh, and organs turned into purple poison which flowed out of its wounds and orifices.

Meng Qiu Zhen carefully squatted and took out tiger poison Gu.

This rank three tiger poison Gu was one of the three Gu he chose in the first stage of the dream realm. Once activated, it could emit tiger poison.

Tiger poison Gu was like a black scorpion, but its head had golden markings that resembled the character for 'king'.

It came out of the white silver aperture and started absorbing the poison that was all over the ground.

Soon, the poison was completely absorbed by it, and its body was slightly enlarged.

With a shift of Meng Qiu Zhen's will, tiger poison Gu obediently flew back into his aperture.

"The first stage had many poison Gu. Like snake poison Gu, dove poison Gu, bee poison Gu, and so on. Against the thousand beast king level black bear, bee poison Gu, which is restrained by bear physique, should never be selected. Snake poison Gu and dove poison Gu have rather slow effects. Only tiger poison Gu is specialized in dealing with this kind of large beast and its effect takes place quickly as well. Moreover, when used with poison liquid Gu, tiger poison can change form and become extremely practical in battle."

In the fight with the black bear king, Meng Qiu Zhen used poison liquid Gu and tiger poison Gu to form a poison liquid tiger.

The poison liquid tiger was able to fight the black bear king head on, it greatly made up for Meng Qiu Zhen's weakness in direct combat. Meng Qiu Zhen stayed at the back and continuously used poison path Gu worms to help the poison liquid tiger and claimed victory in the end.

Naturally, tiger poison Gu also had its disadvantage.

The disadvantage was quite big as well.

There was a common saying that even tigers would not hurt their cubs, tiger poison Gu had no effect towards infantile targets.

According to dream butterfly Immortal Gu's information, Meng Qiu Zhen had already known in the first stage that the black bear was the final obstacle and also the most difficult one.

He acted according to the conditions and selected the most crucial tiger poison Gu.

"Tiger poison Gu's toxicity and venom quantity has fallen greatly, even though I gathered the remaining poison after the battle."

"Tiger poison Gu needs time to recuperate, my overall power has decreased quite a bit. Fortunately, this is the final obstacle, and this is a dream realm, not the real wilderness."

"Huh? What happened?"

Meng Qiu Zhen's expression changed slightly.

The second stage of the dream realm was still stable and did not disappear like he expected.

"Is there still another obstacle? It can't be. Dream butterfly Immortal Gu already scouted everything."

"Wait a moment, in the search before, there was also a mortal."

This mortal did not have Gu Master cultivation, so Meng Qiu Zhen did not think much of it. Maybe, if tiger poison Gu was not selected, the mortal would provide some help to the Gu cultivator exploring the dream realm.

But now, Meng Qiu Zhen realized this mortal seemed to be a crucial factor.

According to the gathered information, Meng Qiu Zhen naturally knew of this mortal's location.

He immediately moved towards the location.

Halfway on his journey, his strength started decreasing rapidly.

"What's going on?" Meng Qiu Zhen immediately inspected himself and turned pale, "The plague has erupted! There were clearly about two more days left. Could it be, the battle with the black bear expended too much of my energy, and my body is unable to bear it so the plague erupted earlier?"

This plague was specific to mushroommen, once it erupted, mushrooms would grow all over the body.

The bigger the mushrooms grew, the more vitality they would extract from the mushroommen.

The plague broke out so violently that when Meng Qiu Zhen discovered it, he was already sapped of his strength and collapsed on the ground.

"Is this dream realm exploration going to end here?"

"I haven't even seen Paradise Earth's face."

To help the main body's plan of constructing earth vein, Meng Qiu Zhen started the exploration of Paradise Earth's dream realm ahead of time.

"No, I still have hope."

"Persevere, I must persevere, this place is not that far from that mortal's location."

Although Meng Qiu Zhen was powerless and could only lie on the ground, it had not reached the worst situation yet. At least, he had strength to breath and could use the Gu worms in his aperture.

He immediately activated a healing Gu worm and started delaying for time.

The healing Gu could not cure the root problem and only lessened the threat of the plague. But its effect was minimal like a child trying to stop a car.

"Damn it, the battle with the black bear king expended over half of my primeval essence. My primeval essence will be used up soon."

Meng Qiu Zhen was forced into a predicament again.

But right at this time, he heard rustling noises.

"It's that mortal's footsteps. Good!" Meng Qiu Zhen's eyes shone as he used all his strength to shout: "Help... help..."

Chapter 2144: Pulling Mushrooms

Even though he used all his strength to shout, Meng Qiu Zhen's voice was still faint.

"Who is asking for help?" A mortal girl pushed aside the brambles and came to the place.

"Here, look below..." Meng Qiu Zhen spoke, his voice so faint that it was like a whisper.

The mortal girl did not hear him, mumbling: "Did I hear wrongly? Sigh, it is getting late, I need to quickly gather mushrooms and sell them in Tu clan village. Eh? There are so many mushrooms here!"

The mortal girl saw Meng Qiu Zhen.

But right now, Meng Qiu Zhen's body was already covered with mushrooms.

The mortal girl squatted and started picking the mushrooms on Meng Qiu Zhen's body.

Every mushroom she picked, the cause of Meng Qiu Zhen's falling vitality would decrease by one.

His illness was alleviated rapidly and his strength slowly recovered.

"That's right, there are still two days before my illness truly breaks out. For now at least, my life should be safe!"

Meng Qiu Zhen quickly realized.

He then spoke: "Girl, the mushrooms on my body are delicious, it doesn't matter if you pluck them all."

The mortal girl jumped from shock.

"Don't be afraid, I am also a person. It was me who asked for help earlier, thank you for saving me, kind girl."

"But I did not do anything."

Meng Qiu Zhen gave a forced smile: "Pluck all the mushrooms from my body and that will be saving me. These mushrooms are harmful to us mushroommen, but they are harmless and even beneficial to other races."

The girl was shocked before smiling: "So you are a mushroomman, I have heard rumors about you guys since I was a child, the rumors said you were gentle and never harmed people. I had never seen a living mushroomman before I met you."

Meng Qiu Zhen quickly said: "Pick the mushrooms quickly, I can't last much longer."

The girl's hands were nimble, she rapidly picked the mushrooms from Meng Qiu Zhen's body.

He was out of the hopeless situation and rescued from the brink of failure.

"There is still one last mushroom!" The girl said seriously.

"Wait." Meng Qiu Zhen's expression changed, "You don't need to pick that mushroom — ahhh!"

The girl blinked her pure eyes and her face reddened slightly: "I can't pull it out, does it hurt?"

Meng Qiu Zhen was pale as he took a sharp breath: "Don't pull it."

But the girl shook her head, saying stubbornly: "That won't do, mushroomman big brother, you said it earlier, I need to pick all the mushrooms from your body for you to be cured."

"Don't, don't, don't... ahhh!"

The girl pulled up her sleeves, showing an extremely serious and cute expression: "Hmph, I don't believe I can't pull it out!"

Meng Qiu Zhen: "Ahhughhh—!"

...

Amidst the miserable cries of Meng Qiu Zhen, the second stage was finally passed.

His sight changed from a chaotic whirlpool of colors to gradually clearing up.

This was a bustling and busy market with people walking everywhere.

"This is Tu clan village?" Behind Meng Qiu Zhen, the mushroomman Huang Xiao Mi, who was covered tightly, said in a low voice.

Meng Qiu Zhen's mind shook slightly.

In the previous two stages, he had played the role of Huang Xiao Mi, but in this third stage, his identity was actually changed.

This situation was not common.

Meng Qiu Zhen quickly inspected himself.

"Huh, I became that human girl." Meng Qiu Zhen sighed inwardly.

Huang Xiao Mi's strength was barely enough, and now, Meng Qiu Zhen was a mortal, a young girl at that.

The change in identity caused Meng Qiu Zhen to feel some doubts.

What was the main mission in this Paradise Earth dream realm?

In the previous two stages, he had Huang Xiao Mi's identity and had estimated the dream realm's main mission was to save the mushroomman tribe by curing the plague.

But now that his identity changed, Meng Qiu Zhen immediately felt his speculation wavering intensely.

"No matter what, since Huang Xiao Mi followed the human girl into Tu clan village, I should still try to help Huang Xiao Mi to find the mushroomman witch."

Meng Qiu Zhen decided to continue following the previous trail.

"Fang Tu, you came? Quick, the position beside me is very good, take it quickly. The evening market is not like the morning market, it only lasts for a short period of time." A middle-aged uncle waved at Meng Qiu Zhen.

"Thank you, uncle." Meng Qiu Zhen thought for a bit and placed her basket filled with mushrooms at the space beside the uncle.

Huang Xiao Mi silently helped Meng Qiu Zhen set up the mushrooms.

The middle-aged uncle took a glance and exclaimed: "These mushrooms are really fresh."

"Naturally." Huang Xiao Mi said proudly.

The middle-aged uncle's gaze moved towards him: "This is?"

"This is my distant relative, he came to help me." Meng Qiu Zhen quickly replied.

The middle-aged uncle did not ask anymore, the evening market had already started, crowds of people were moving around and everyone was busy.

Some were busy buying, some were busy selling.

The traded goods were all mortal materials like mushrooms, vegetables, bean cakes, and so on. This was a mortal market and had daily necessities. There were no transactions of Gu worms, unless a merchant caravan passed through Tu clan village.

After about five minutes, the crowd began to grow sparse.

At this time, sounds of disturbance came from ahead.

"Step aside, step aside!"

"Move aside, can't you see Lord Green Beast is here?"

A young man shouted, five to six people were pushing through the narrow pavement.

Everywhere they went, pedestrians made way in fear and nervousness, while some even showed disdain and hatred inwardly.

"Fang Tu, hide quickly. Don't let that 'beast' see you." The middle-aged uncle quickly reminded.

"Ah?" Meng Qiu Zhen was dazed.

"Lady Fang Tu!" At the next moment, the leader of the group, the bald youngster, shouted. His eyes let out a sneaky light as he noticed Meng Qiu Zhen from far away.

"What's going on?" Meng Qiu Zhen narrowed his eyes as he saw the bald youngster walking towards him with quick steps.

The bald youngster had thick brows and large eyes but had not even a single hair on his head; instead, there was a tattoo of a green beast on his head.

The bald youngster rubbed his green beast tattoo and smiled widely: "Lady Fang Tu, you are selling mushrooms again. I want to buy them."

"Oh?" Meng Qiu Zhen was inwardly vigilant while asking, "How much do you want to buy?"

The bald youngster raised a finger: "I want to buy one kilogram. Help me pick the big and good ones."

Meng Qiu Zhen began to pick the mushrooms.

"This is good, hmm, that one is also good, I want them." The bald youngster nicknamed 'Green Beast' pointed here and there.

"Eh, I told you, I want this one and that one!" The bald youngster said.

"Which ones do you want?" Meng Qiu Zhen frowned, sensing that the young man seemed to be toying with him.

The bald youngster grinned: "Forget it, Sister Fang, let me help you, we will choose together."

The bald youngster acted immediately.

"Soft, so soft." He chose several mushrooms and said.

Meng Qiu Zhen replied: "These are all fresh, I picked them just today."

"Smooth, so smooth." The bald youngster praised again.

Meng Qiu Zhen slowly looked up and said with a frown: "You are touching my hand!"

"Ah, sorry, sorry." The bald youngster laughed.

Meng Qiu Zhen opened his eyes wide: "You are still touching?!"

"Accident, it was an accident!"

Meng Qiu Zhen was speechless, he was actually being molested!

"Pfft, shameless guy, actually molesting an innocent girl in broad daylight!" Huang Xiao Mi could not endure it anymore, he shouted.

"Who are you? Why are you standing beside my Lady Fang!" The bald youngster was immediately provoked and stared at Huang Xiao Mi.

The two started arguing, sparks seemed to be flying in the air.

"This is the limit of dream butterfly Immortal Gu." Meng Qiu Zhen sighed inwardly.

Dream butterfly Immortal Gu could inspect the details of the next event of the dream realm, but it could not inspect what the owner of Dream Butterfly would encounter.

Because the changes in the dream realm would occur when the Gu cultivator entered and interacted with the dream realm.

Meng Qiu Zhen had already inspected the bald youngster and this Tu clan village's market in the previous stage. But he was unable to know what he would encounter specifically in advance.

The two argued in front of Meng Qiu Zhen, their argument got increasingly heated to the point of nearly exchanging blows.

Meng Qiu Zhen was just about to persuade them to stop when a flash of inspiration hit him, and he kept quiet.

"Ugh, I am getting angry! Brat, you are looking for a beating!!" The bald youngster suddenly rubbed his head and attacked.

"Hmph, who is afraid of you!" Huang Xiao Mi did not show weakness, attacking immediately.

The two started fighting.

"Don't fight, don't fight." Meng Qiu Zhen called out while retreating. He was in a mortal body now, and had no ability to interfere in a Gu Master's battle.

But fortunately, be it Huang Xiao Mi or the bald youngster, they both cared about Meng Qiu Zhen.

When Meng Qiu Zhen retreated to a safe distance, they started using Gu cultivator methods.

After several rounds, Huang Xiao Mi was clearly at a disadvantage and was not the bald youngster's match.

"This ruffian is really strong!" Meng Qiu Zhen was slightly surprised. He was well aware of Huang Xiao Mi's strength, after he acted as the latter in the first and second stage of the dream realm.

But he did not expect the bald youngster to be so strong, he had already suppressed Huang Xiao Mi.

"Wait a second, you are not a human, you are a variant human." The bald youngster suddenly called out.

In the heat of the battle, Huang Xiao Mi's identity was exposed.

"Amazing, you spy, what are you trying to do by entering my Tu clan village? You definitely have bad intentions! Hahaha, I am going to make a great contribution!"

The bald youngster continued to shout: "Attack him together, he is a mushroomman, we don't have to uphold the moral of humanity against such a person!"

"Despicable! If you are a man, fight me alone!" Huang Xiao Mi was heavily outnumbered and captured, but he was still shouting indignantly.

"Hahaha. I will be Tu clan's hero by catching you!" The bald youngster laughed, kicking the bound Huang Xiao Mi, "Just lie still, you variant human."

After saying this, the bald youngster ran towards Meng Qiu Zhen and asked in concern: "Sister Fang, are you alright? You definitely had no idea or were forced by this mushroomman. Haha, how will you thank me now?"

Chapter 2145: Being a Bystander

Meng Qiu Zhen shook his head, saying in an impatient tone: "Brother Mi is a good person..."

The bald youngster interrupted him, shouting hurriedly: "As expected, the scheming mushroomman threatened Lady Fang. Let's go and report to the elders. Move!"

Under everyone's gaze, Meng Qiu Zhen went with the flow and entered Tu clan village with the bald youngster, Huang Xiao Mi, and the rest.

On the way, the bald youngster reminded Meng Qiu Zhen softly: "Sister Fang, you need to report properly, otherwise you might be implicated as well. Variant humans like this mushroomman are vicious things, he is already sure to die!"

Meng Qiu Zhen did not respond.

The tied Huang Xiao Mi shouted: "That's right, I deceived Fang Tu and threatened her. You are creating a huge trouble for your Tu clan by capturing me! Someone will definitely come to save me."

Huang Xiao Mi was saved by Fang Tu, he clearly did not want to implicate his benefactor, thus saying this intentionally.

The bald youngster led Huang Xiao Mi to Tu clan village's prison, and received praises from Tu clan village's elders.

After everyone left, the bald youngster invited Meng Qiu Zhen to his home: "It is already late, Sister Fang, come to my home to have dinner and stay for the night. Back when we were neighbors, we used to play together. My mother will also be very happy if she sees you!"

"So this 'Green Beast' had this kind of relationship with Fang Tu?" Meng Qiu Zhen nodded and let the plot develop.

Soon, Meng Qiu Zhen followed the bald youngster to his home.

This was an ordinary two-storied bamboo building.

Only the bald youngster and his mother lived here.

The bald youngster opened the door to the kitchen and said loudly: "Mother, look who I brought?"

"Ahh, Little Fang. I haven't seen you for many days. Are your parents okay?" The bald youngster's mother was very enthusiastic.

"They are both fine, thank you, auntie." Meng Qiu Zhen said half-heartedly.

The bald youngster's mother nodded, smiling: "Little Fang is here as a guest, take a seat, I will prepare some dishes."

The bald youngster said impatiently: "Mother, you should prepare more delicious food. This meal will be your son's celebration feast as well."

"You brat, what have you done this time?" The bald youngster's mother frowned.

The bald youngster patted his chest: "Mother, your son made a huge contribution this time! I arrested a mushroomman and locked him in prison."

"What?" The bald youngster's mother paused.

The bald youngster quickly narrated the event.

The bald youngster's mother frowned as she looked at Meng Qiu Zhen: "Little Fang, this brat likes to talk nonsense, is what he said true?"

"Yes." Meng Qiu Zhen nodded before adding: "But big brother Huang Xiao Mi is a good person. I..."

Before he finished speaking, he was once again interrupted by the bald youngster: "Alright, Sister Fang, I have warned you several times. You can say this at home, but don't talk about it outside."

"Okay, okay." The bald youngster's mother waved her hand, "Brat, there is no more soy sauce left. Go to the nearby shop and get some soy sauce."

"Ah?"

"Hurry up and go, how can I make food without soy sauce?"

"Oh, alright, alright."

After the bald youngster left, his mother walked towards Meng Qiu Zhen: "Come, Little Fang, tell auntie what is going on?"

The dream realm's third stage passed like this.

Fourth stage.

Deep in the night, underground prison.

"My identity changed again?" When Meng Qiu Zhen came to his senses, he immediately realized this.

He had left the mortal Fang Tu's identity and become a Gu Master again; moreover, his cultivation was rank four!

"I am actually the bald youngster's mother now?" Meng Qiu Zhen shortly discovered that the bald youngster's mother was actually a mushroomman.

Meng Qiu Zhen immediately had a guess: "My current identity is probably that Huang Wan."

This dream realm originated from Paradise Earth, what was special about it was the identities in the different stages of the dream realm were not fixed.

"I might even play the role of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable in the next dream realm." Meng Qiu Zhen smiled.

Till now, he had not seen even the shadow of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable.

In the first stage of the dream realm, Meng Qiu Zhen learned that Huang Xiao Mi's mushroomman tribe had a former witch - Huang Wan. She had great strength and was the only doctor that might be able to cure the plague.

However, he knew from the old granny that this former witch Huang Wan was expelled from the tribe for some reason.

"This mushroomman Huang Wan concealed her identity and lived in Tu clan village, a human territory. She even adopted a human child to perfectly conceal her identity. If that bald youngster knew his 'mother' was actually a mushroomman, I wonder what expression he would show?"

Meng Qiu Zhen laughed.

He used a very short period of time to get familiar with the Gu worms on him.

The Gu worms were comprehensive, covering attack, defense, movement, healing, and other aspects. Meng Qiu Zhen intuitively sensed some of these Gu worms could combine to form a mortal killer move.

Unfortunately, the situation now did not allow Meng Qiu Zhen to test the killer move or its possible combination.

"The third stage already gave obvious clues. Although this mushroomman Huang Wan was expelled from the tribe, her heart is with the tribe. She immediately moved during the night to save Huang Xiao Mi."

"I must move quickly!"

Meng Qiu Zhen immediately went deeper into the underground prison.

The structure of the underground prison was simple and clear.

Very soon, he saw Huang Xiao Mi, who was tied to the wall in the deepest part of the prison.

Meng Qiu Zhen used his Gu worms, silently melting the lock on the prison door.

"Huang Xiao Mi, wake up." Meng Qiu Zhen walked towards Huang Xiao Mi and was about to inspect his condition.

Suddenly, 'Huang Xiao Mi' detonated, turning into ash that covered Meng Qiu Zhen.

Shortly after, alarm bells rang and guards started shouting.

The whole prison started emitting dark-yellow light. The concealed Gu formation was activated.

"Oh no, it is a trap!" Meng Qiu Zhen helplessly discovered that 'Huang Xiao Mi' had completely disappeared.

He hurriedly retreated, using poison Gu to corrode the Gu formation but it showed little effect.

"Such guts! Breaking into my Tu clan's jail!"

"It is indeed like that captive said, someone came to save him. Hmph! Surrender quietly and we might spare your life!"

Two elders with similar faces like they were twins were transported by the Gu formation and arrived in front of Meng Qiu Zhen.

Meng Qiu Zhen sneered as he started the fight.

The battle lasted for sixty rounds before he was defeated and captured by the two elders.

The dream realm dissipated.

"I failed." Meng Qiu Zhen's soul returned to his body as he sighed.

Paradise Earth's dream realm was not easy to explore, but Meng Qiu Zhen had plenty of experience, he reached the fourth stage before failing.

His soul was quite injured, Meng Qiu Zhen began to think about the events while healing his soul.

"Those two elders are really strong! They both have rank four cultivation, and they have extremely good teamwork when fighting, like they are one person."

"Not only do I have to fight those two elders, I also have to deal with the Gu formation. It is quite straining."

"Naturally, there is another important reason, I am not familiar with poison path Gu worms. I should use this time to deduce the hidden poison path killer moves."

"Hmm, there is another reason as well..."

Meng Qiu Zhen reflected on himself and realized he had been fretful in the dream realm.

Although that fake Huang Xiao Mi deceived his initial detection methods, if he was in his normal mental state, he would not have rashly entered the prison, and would have used Gu worms to inspect the situation once again.

"At that time, Huang Wan's mood was extremely anxious and I was unknowingly affected by it, clouding my judgment."

There were emotional disturbances in the previous three stages as well, but they were all suppressed by Meng Qiu Zhen.

At the fourth stage, the dream realm's emotions would naturally be deeper than the third stage.

This was also one of the difficulties of exploring dream realms.

Using this time, Meng Qiu Zhen deduced five poison path killer moves which were mostly based on bee poison Gu.

Entering the dream realm again, Meng Qiu Zhen inspected patiently this time.

He made an astonishing discovery: Not only was Huang Xiao Mi fake, the whole underground prison was also fake.

"This is a fake prison, the real prison is still below. The Gu formation's main body is also below!"

Meng Qiu Zhen carefully entered the real underground prison.

Tu clan village's real underground prison was unexpectedly complicated and extensive!

The underground prison was like an ant nest, it was filled with thousands of paths intersecting each other, Meng Qiu Zhen felt like he had entered a maze.

"The whole mountain seems to have been dug and made into a prison."

"This Tu clan village is clearly an ordinary force, but it was actually able to do this?"

"No, there is a trace of Earth Tunnel here!"

Meng Qiu Zhen was probing carefully and soon discovered traces of one of the ten earths, Earth Tunnel.

"This mountain must be of famous mountain level, it contains a natural Earth Tunnel. Tu clan village just slightly developed the Earth Tunnel and was able to gain a large amount of resources. No wonder they were able to nurture two rank four elders."

Meng Qiu Zhen was moving everywhere in the prison.

The underground prison was mostly empty, and there were more beasts than mortals locked up in it.

Meng Qiu Zhen was still unable to find any clues even after some time. The dream realm had exhausted a large amount of his soul foundation by now.

"Those two Gu Masters!" Meng Qiu Zhen suddenly heard the sounds of Gu cultivators traveling through the Earth Tunnel from ahead.

He quickly moved aside and hid.

Swish, swish.

The two Gu Masters slipped out from the Earth Tunnel.

"The two rank four elders." Meng Qiu Zhen was observing secretly, and immediately recognized them.

They were all along in the underground prison, so they were able to reach the fake prison immediately in the previous situation.

The two elders talked while moving.

"This mushroomman is quite tight-lipped, he actually endured such cruel torture!"

"Even if he does not say it, we are already aware that a mushroomman tribe has been hiding in the surroundings of Tu clan village. It is just that we don't know the specific location."

"Right, we must obtain the specific location of the mushroomman tribe from this captive and eliminate them!"

"In a few days, we will be able to remove the defensive methods on his soul. At that time, we will know everything by searching his soul."

[0] The title is literally translated as buying soy sauce.

Chapter 2146: Prison Break

The two elders gradually stopped, entering another tunnel as they moved along instead.

The two of them rapidly left the place.

Meng Qiu Zhen's eyes twitched.

The scene in front of him reminded him of certain memories in his mind.

"In the five hundred years of the main body's previous life, during the five regions chaotic war, a super clan known as Tu clan emerged in Southern Border. Their Gu Immortals were most skilled at digging tunnels and using them to launch sneak attacks in battle. Does this have anything to do with this Tu village?"

There were several possibilities regarding this.

Firstly, Tu village's inheritance was excavated by someone. Secondly, Tu village's bloodline was spread by descendants, they rose to become immortal during the era of abundant dream realms, or they were simply secluded Gu Immortals. Thirdly, Tu village's members revived in Tomb Earth.

Meng Qiu Zhen successfully found his way to Huang Xiao Mi after following the route of the two rank four elders.

Huang Xiao Mi was curled up in a corner of the cell, having fallen asleep.

This time, Meng Qiu Zhen investigated carefully, after finding out that there were no traps here, he entered the prison cell.

He immediately found that Huang Xiao Mi was in poor shape, at the brink of death.

Huang Xiao Mi had the mushroomman plague to begin with, it was quite fatal. If one had insufficient resistance, they would die.

Today, he first fought against the bald youngster before getting interrogated by the two elders, his entire body was overgrown with mushrooms.

If Meng Qiu Zhen did not arrive in time, he would die in just a few more breaths of time.

Meng Qiu Zhen sighed to himself, it was a close shave, if he came later, this dream realm exploration would have failed entirely.

He immediately tried to save Huang Xiao Mi, thankfully, he was prepared for this.

The mushrooms on Huang Xiao Mi's body continued to shrink until all of them went back into his body.

"Who are you?" Huang Xiao Mi was barely able to open his eyes, his vision was still blurred.

Meng Qiu Zhen answered immediately: "I am Huang Wan, I have already used a killer move to suppress the mushroomman plague in your body. Your situation is dire, your life force is almost depleted. I cannot pull out the mushrooms casually as it will consume your life as well."

Huang Xiao Mi immediately thanked: "Thank you for saving my life, senior."

"Sigh, it is still too early to say that. Let's go out, I need to research on this plague. You don't have much time left." Meng Qiu Zhen said.

He had not created a poison path killer move that could heal Huang Xiao Mi's illness yet.

However, the next scene might request for him to heal this mushroomman plague.

Naturally, that was just his guess.

While searching for Huang Xiao Mi earlier, Meng Qiu Zhen did not have a chance to activate dream butterfly Immortal Gu, thus he did not know what the following scenes would be.

"You need to persevere, let's go." Meng Qiu Zhen helped Huang Xiao Mi to get up as they left together.

But halfway through, they met the bald youngster.

"Stand there! As expected, someone came to save you." The bald youngster shouted.

The two elders were behind him as well, they were furious and shocked.

"Such guts! Vicious thief, you dare to break into the prison!"

"Quickly activate the formation, capture this person as well."

Once he said that, the Gu formation activated, the two elders fought while the bald youngster assisted them.

Meng Qiu Zhen sighed internally as he fought against them.

He had many poison path killer moves, they were evenly matched after fighting for some time.

But soon, the bald youngster saw a weakness and attacked Huang Xiao Mi instead.

Huang Xiao Mi could not resist, he was a huge burden to Meng Qiu Zhen.

Meng Qiu Zhen had to grit his teeth as he helped Huang Xiao Mi time and again. Eventually, he lost the initiative and got suppressed by the two elders.

In the end, Huang Xiao Mi was killed by the bald youngster, dying on the spot.

"All variant human mushroommen deserve to get killed!" The bald youngster shouted with a righteous tone, filled with excitement.

At the next moment, the dream realm shattered.

Meng Qiu Zhen returned to the sovereign immortal aperture, healing himself while collating his insights about the dream.

"I used dream butterfly Immortal Gu earlier to investigate this dream realm but I did not find the bald youngster. To think that after exploring this dream realm to a degree, it would develop on its own and create new characters."

"Why did the bald youngster come to the prison?"

"From his tone, he seemed to have discovered my traces, what method did he use to find me?"

"Unless, he already found out about the secret of his identity, he knows that his 'mother' is a mushroomman variant human? So he went along with the flow?"

After his injuries were healed, Meng Qiu Zhen went back into the dream realm with several questions to answer.

The route did not change, Meng Qiu Zhen arrived at the prison cell in advance.

He lurked at a corner and watched as Huang Xiao Mi was beaten and interrogated by the two elders.

These elders had outstanding strength, more importantly, they had the help of the Gu formation, Meng Qiu Zhen did not want to use brute force.

After two failures and accumulating experience, his own strength already surpassed the original Huang Wan. But his greatest weakness was still Huang Xiao Mi.

His earlier failures already proved that as long as Huang Xiao Mi died, the dream realm would fail.

It seemed that this scene of the dream realm required him to save Huang Xiao Mi successfully.

Meng Qiu Zhen waited patiently, after the two elders left, he immediately went to Huang Xiao Mi's side.

Not waking him up first, Meng Qiu Zhen directly used the poison path killer move to get rid of the mushroomman plague in Huang Xiao Mi's body.

Next, Meng Qiu Zhen woke Huang Xiao Mi up.

Huang Xiao Mi found out that his illness was cured, he was overjoyed: "Thank you senior! Please save the mushroomman tribe, many of our members are afflicted with this plague."

Meng Qiu Zhen nodded, giving Huang Xiao Mi some poison path Gu so that he had some battle strength.

Huang Xiao Mi did not need Meng Qiu Zhen's help, he was barely able to walk on his own as they sneaked out.

But this time, the bald youngster still found them along the way.

"Stand there! As expected, someone came to save you." The bald youngster was very excited.

Meng Qiu Zhen had a peculiar expression as he asked: "I used many methods to conceal my traces, how did you find us?"

The bald youngster chuckled: "I'm not afraid to tell you, with my genius talent, I created a move called earthly underground qi. After I captured this mushroomman, I secretly used this tracing killer move, how can you get rid of it in such a rush?"

"Not bad, even though you are an external member of the clan, you have some talent."

"Very good, all thanks to you, we found this problem today. This is your merit."

The two rank four elders looked at the bald youngster in a renewed light.

"Thank you, lords!" The bald youngster was very excited, he had the demeanor of a lackey: "I will do my best."

Meng Qiu Zhen: "..."

After an intense battle, Huang Xiao Mi still died in battle.

Meng Qiu Zhen failed his third exploration.

After deep analysis and deductions, he went into the fourth exploration.

This time, he sneaked in early and hid in a corner. After the two elders left, he immediately entered the prison cell, healing Huang Xiao Mi's illness and even giving him healing Gu worms.

"Wait here and heal yourself continuously, do not step out of the cell. There is a tracking method on you, if you try to get out, the enemy will find out." Meng Qiu Zhen instructed: "After I kill the crucial Gu Masters, when you see this healing Gu worm fly in the air, get out and escape."

Huang Xiao Mi was very obedient, he nodded: "I will listen to senior's instructions."

Meng Qiu Zhen made the optimal arrangements and left the cell.

At the other side, with the development of the dream realm, the bald youngster appeared.

He was summoned by the two elders and made his way to them but was suddenly attacked by Meng Qiu Zhen.

"Hmm?!" Even though the bald youngster had great strength, he was not Meng Qiu Zhen's match, not to mention that Meng Qiu Zhen had prepared for this assault.

The bald youngster died on the spot.

But Meng Qiu Zhen found that he could not move, an intense feeling of sadness, guilt, and regret overwhelmed his heart, he found that he lost control of his body.

"What is going on?"

"It seems that I cannot kill the bald youngster?"

"Maybe because they lived together for so long, the mushroomman Huang Wan had already treated him as her real son."

The feeling was so intense that even with Meng Qiu Zhen's fortitude, he could not suppress it.

Mushroomman Huang Wan shuddered as tears flowed down her cheeks, it could not be stopped.

Clank clank clank...

Alarm bells suddenly rang, the Gu formation was activated as the two elders found their way to Meng Qiu Zhen.

They must have gotten suspicious after waiting for the bald youngster for so long, they came over to check.

Eventually, Meng Qiu Zhen's exploration failed as well.

"So this guy cannot be killed either?" Meng Qiu Zhen was troubled.

Because he could not unravel and dispel that earthly underground qi killer move.

Even though it was a mortal killer move, Meng Qiu Zhen did not know what Gu worms were used in it. And more importantly, even if he knew, could the Gu worms on him achieve such an effect?

"If only I knew how many Gu worms the bald youngster had. It is a pity I have already lost the opportunity to find out."

In the third scene, Fang Yuan's identity was Fang Tu. If he tried to investigate, with the bald youngster's affection for her, he should have gotten some clues.

Earlier, when Fang Tu sold mushrooms, the bald youngster flirted with her, it was a great opportunity.

But back then, Meng Qiu Zhen had not thought of this.

Because dream butterfly Immortal Gu did not let him see this scene. Back then, the bald youngster did not exist in this scene in the first place, the dream realm changed on its own after saving Huang Xiao Mi, causing the bald youngster to appear.

Now, after reaching this scene, the earlier ones had vanished already.

After deep consideration, Meng Qiu Zhen went into the dream realm again.

This time, he did not enter the cell directly and wait there.

Getting there early was useless.

Meng Qiu Zhen had to wait for the elders to leave before he could try and save Huang Xiao Mi.

Meng Qiu Zhen set up some arrangements on the route that the elders would take instead.

He used create dream Immortal Gu to establish a complicated tunnel along the way.

After making his arrangement, Meng Qiu Zhen came to the prison cell, the two elders had just left.

He immediately saved Huang Xiao Mi but did not leave him in the cell, bringing him away directly.

The two elders were just about to meet up with the bald youngster but they lost their way.

With this crucial gap in time, Meng Qiu Zhen successfully brought Huang Xiao Mi away.

During this period, the bald youngster chased them and wanted to stop them.

But Meng Qiu Zhen did not kill this troublesome guy, instead making him faint on the spot. After stopping Huang Xiao Mi from taking revenge, he successfully passed the scene of the dream realm.

Chapter 2147: War

The Gu Masters reacted and quickly retreated.

Meng Qiu Zhen stomped on the ground with a loud sound, a hole immediately appeared below him.

A Gu Master was caught off guard, he fell into the trap.

"Wanting to restrict me with this method?" He was just about to fly out of the pit, when Meng Qiu Zhen held a huge rock that was the size of a horse carriage and tossed it down.

"Don't...."

Boom!

The huge rock crashed down and sent the Gu Master into the pit, losing all signs of life. From below the rock, bright red blood started to spread into a puddle.

"What are you doing? Are you crazy!"

"You are actually attacking our own clan member, a Tu clansman?"

The remaining two Gu Masters watched this as their hearts jumped intensely.

"Aren't you guys indignant?" Meng Qiu Zhen snickered as he approached.

Even though the bald youngster had limited Gu worms, against Meng Qiu Zhen's combat attainment, how could these mortal Gu Masters resist him?

After a short while, they were all sprawling on the ground.

"Stop it, stop it, we give up!" The Gu Masters pleaded in a hurry.

The sixth scene of the dream realm.

Meng Qiu Zhen became the mushroomman Huang Xiao Mi again.

His injuries had healed already, the mushroomman plague was successfully healed through Huang Wan's secret treatment.

Huang Xiao Mi also obtained some poison path Gu from Huang Wan. Using these Gu to form killer moves, he could completely get rid of the plague that troubled his mushroomman tribe.

Huang Xiao Mi moved stealthily in secret, trying to escape.

The surroundings of Tu clan village had surveying Gu Masters that did patrols regularly.

A group of rank two Gu Masters, with a total of five members, were moving in the forest.

"Stop, we will rest here." The leader suddenly extended his hand, instructing.

The moment the group rested, a colorless and odorless poisonous gas spread towards them.

Boom boom boom.

The five Gu Masters fell on the ground, falling unconscious.

"Huang Wan's poison path killer move might only be effective against rank three and below Gu Masters, but it has no aura at all when used, it is very valuable in realistic situations." Meng Qiu Zhen evaluated as he set off again.

He could not kill these Tu clan Gu Masters, even though they could not resist him now.

Once he killed them, Tu clan village would get alerted, they would chase after him.

But a change happened before Meng Qiu Zhen's very eyes.

The dream realm suddenly changed, a Gu Master group led by the bald youngster met with Meng Qiu Zhen head on.

"Variant human thief, you are still here? Stop there! Where are you trying to escape to?" The bald youngster was slightly stunned before shouting and chasing after him.

"It seems that this happened in history as well." Meng Qiu Zhen was helpless about this.

Dream butterfly Immortal Gu could not detect such sudden changes in advance.

In fact, even if he saw it, Meng Qiu Zhen could not do anything about this.

No matter what route he chose, with the natural development of the dream realm, the bald youngster's group would still meet up with Meng Qiu Zhen regardless.

And looking at it from another perspective, this was a necessary event for this dream realm.

Only by escaping from the bald youngster's pursuit could he successfully pass this scene.

An exciting chase and escape battle erupted between the two sides.

The bald youngster chased while Huang Xiao Mi, who had recovered, did not waste time fighting him, he escaped while setting up traps, killing the rest of his group members.

The bald youngster was the son of Huang Wan, to play safe, Meng Qiu Zhen did not attack him.

Eventually, Meng Qiu Zhen successfully escaped.

The bald youngster stood behind him without any hope of catching up, he shouted: "Mushroomman thief, I will remember you! One day, I will kill you!"

Their grudges intensified.

Seventh scene.

Eighth scene.

Ninth scene...

Meng Qiu Zhen acted as the bald youngster 'Green Beast' at times, while acting as Huang Xiao Mi at other times.

Using the poison path killer move that Huang Xiao Mi brought back, the mushroomman tribe successfully healed from the plague.

But war ensued.

Even though the location of the mushroomman tribe was not discovered, with Tu clan village's rampant searches and investigation, they could not hide for long.

The two sides started to send their Gu Masters to engage in small interactions and battles.

The two sides suffered heavy losses, but because of that, champions appeared.

Tu clan village had the bald youngster, who was Huang Wan's adopted son. The mushroommen had Huang Xiao Mi, the tribesman of Huang Wan.

The two interacted occasionally, fighting against each other frequently.

Because of their contest, their strength grew rapidly, they reached rank four at the same time.

On both sides, their clansmen and tribesmen died terribly at each others' hands.

They became the greatest enemies of each other's lives!

Finally, at the twelfth scene of the dream realm.

Meng Qiu Zhen acted as Huang Xiao Mi, he set up a trap and sowed discord, causing Tu clan village's higher-ups to feel wariness against the bald youngster.

'Green Beast' was not a Tu clansman after all, he was not truly one of them.

The mushroommen set up a trap that did not seem obvious, it seemed to be the true gathering spot of the mushroomman tribe. Tu clan village immediately dispatched the bald youngster to go and probe them out.

Even though the bald youngster knew that something was up, he was uncertain.

After going and investigating, the bald youngster fell into a trap, he was in a life-and-death crisis.

"Green Beast, today, you will die!" Huang Xiao Mi shouted, leading his troops to encircle and attack the humans who were lower in numbers.

"Even if I die, I will drag down ten mushroommen with me to die together!" The bald youngster shouted.

He was bathed in blood and covered in injuries but his morale was high, even the mushroommen attacking him realized that this person was a true warrior!

Eventually, the bald youngster used up all his strength and primeval essence.

He was all alone.

Tens of mushroomman corpses were lying around him.

"You variant humans will not live for long."

"Damn it, damn it!"

"I want to kill my enemies, but I have no way of doing that anymore."

The bald youngster smiled coldly as he knelt on one knee, raising his head up with pride and arrogance.

He shouted at Meng Qiu Zhen: "Huang Xiao Mi, come and kill me! Even if I die at your hands today, I have merely lost to the schemes of those Tu clan elders."

"You understood it after all." Meng Qiu Zhen smiled coldly as he walked forward, ready to deal the final blow, but suddenly a change occurred.

Huang Wan concealed her appearance and appeared suddenly, a wave of white poisonous smoke spread out, she saved the bald youngster successfully.

But at the next moment, a human Gu Master who had rank five cultivation level made his move.

Boom!

With a loud sound, not only was the white smoke dispersed by the human Gu Master, everyone's vision cleared up and he even obstructed Huang Wan from escaping.

Huang Wan held onto the bald youngster as they landed at the periphery of the battlefield.

"Village head!" The bald youngster was overjoyed when he saw the rank five human Gu Master, he also looked at the female Gu Master who saved him.

From this female Gu Master, the bald youngster could sense a familiar yet foreign aura, he asked in curiosity: "Benefactor, who... are you?"

Chapter 2148: Le Tu

At this time, Tu clan village's Gu Masters appeared from all directions, surrounding all the mushroommen as well as Huang Wan and her son.

The mushroommen fell into panic as they got encircled.

Huang Xiao Mi shouted: "Don't panic! I have already requested for help from the tribe, they will arrive shortly. We need to persevere until then!"

The mushroomman Gu Masters forced themselves to calm down.

Tu clan village's leader did not attack directly, he took a few steps forward and stared at Huang Wan with a complex gaze: "Wan Er, as expected, you came."

Huang Wan snorted coldly: "What do you want?"

Once she said that, the bald youngster realized at once, his body and mind shook, gasping: "Mother?!"

Her identity was exposed, Huang Wan got rid of her concealment and returned to her original appearance.

"At this point in time, I can't hide it from you anymore, little rascal." Huang Wan looked at the bald youngster and sighed deeply with a melancholic expression.

The mushroommen were all shocked.

"This is... the previous generation witch?"

"Why did our former witch save the human Gu Master Green Beast?"

"From their conversation, it seems that they are mother and son?"

"So Huang Wan was exiled from the tribe because she had an affair with Tu clan village's head, they even had a son!!"

The truth was unveiled before everyone, they quickly understood the whole situation from start to finish.

"Mother! Are you really my mother? Are they speaking the truth?!" The bald youngster was so shocked he could not control himself.

All along, he had lived as a pure human, to think that he was actually a mixed breed of human and mushroomman.

Huang Wan sighed deeply: "They are all correct, I am sorry for hiding it from you for so long!"

The bald youngster took in a deep breath as he stumbled back for a few steps, looking at Huang Wan with wide opened eyes.

He had never seen his mother's mushroomman form, with the truth of his identity exposed, he could not accept it so easily.

Tu clan village's head looked at the bald youngster deeply before turning his gaze to Huang Wan: "Wan Er, is he really our son? I did not expect that after leaving me back then, you would stay behind and lurk within Tu clan village. You even raised our son all alone, it has really been tough on you."

Huang Wan snorted coldly: "You are Tu clan village head, while I am the witch of the mushroomman tribe, we are destined to be separated. But our child is innocent, I only stayed in the village for a reason. That was because my son, a hybrid, will not be accepted by the tribe. Thus, all these years, I let him grow up in Tu clan village, eventually, I would reveal the truth to you and make you take him in."

Saying so, Huang Wan looked towards the bald youngster, saying gently: "Didn't you ask me who your father was when you were young? Now you know. I had my own plans, but reality is often not under people's control, today's scene was something I did not anticipate. Child, no matter what, regardless of how much you hate me or your father, you need to remember something: People who live in this world, be it humans, variant humans, or mixed breeds, have to be happy and blissful, they should not dwell on grudges or hatred, a big heart will allow you to see a big world, thus, mother named you Le Tu[1]."

Hearing this, Meng Qiu Zhen was shaken internally.

"What, 'Green Beast' is Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable? He actually has mixed blood, but how can a mixed breed become one of the ten human venerables?!"

"No wonder I felt such intense emotions after killing Le Tu as Huang Wan earlier, causing the exploration to fail."

"So it turns out my deductions were wrong, they really are mother and son!"

"Mother, say no more." Le Tu shook his head as he stepped backwards, looking at Huang Wan in disbelief: "How... are you a mushroomman?"

Huang Wan's heart jumped: "Ah Le, you lived among the humans since you were born, I know you cannot accept it immediately, but..."

Boom!

The ground behind Huang Wan cracked open as a Tu clan rank four elder came out and sneak attacked her.

Huang Wan was caught off guard, she was sent flying as she spat out a mouthful of blood while in mid air.

This Tu clan rank four elder did not have strength to chase her after using this move, he had a twisted expression: "Huang Wan! Back then, you saved Huang Xiao Mi, my brother died at your hands. For today, I practiced this cracked soil shattering life killer move for a long time, how does it feel? Hahaha."

"Mother!" Le Tu subconsciously ran towards Huang Wan.

"Lady Huang Wan saved our mushroomman tribe from the plague, quickly save her!" Meng Qiu Zhen shouted too.

"Too late, my fellow Tu clan village members, kill them all!" Tu clan village head shouted as he unleashed a barrage of attacks.

The mushroomman Gu Masters quickly defended against their enemies, they were unable to care for anything else.

"Lord village head!" Le Tu was anxious at the moment, he could not call that person his 'father', he defended Huang Wan as he looked at Tu clan village's leader in disbelief.

Le Tu was not a three year old, he was a veteran in war, he knew about people's hearts. When the situation occurred earlier, Tu clan village's leader had used words to distract Huang Wan, he used Le Tu to draw away her attention and kept the elder hidden so his sneak attack succeeded.

"You made this decision after all!" Huang Wan stared at Tu clan village's head, her former lover, with a cold expression.

The situation was urgent, there was no time for healing. She quickly suppressed her injuries and stood up.

"I am the head of Tu clan village, I am responsible for all the lives of my Tu clan village's members. Moreover, culling variant humans is the righteous duty of all humans!" Tu clan village's leader snorted as he attacked.

"You have such a cruel and wicked heart!" Huang Wan screamed before pushing Le Tu aside, fighting against Tu clan village's leader.

Boom boom boom.

The two fought with a huge commotion, the effects of their attacks spread out, causing unguarded Gu Masters to die continuously.

Thus, the surrounding Gu Masters moved away, creating a huge space for these two to fight in.

"Stop fighting!" Le Tu was anxious, he screamed in his anxiety and helplessness.

His body was in poor condition, he could not join the fight now.

"Ah Le, escape!" Huang Wan shouted.

"Ah Le, you are a mixed blood but you are still my son. I've seen all your achievements so far, quickly come and help the village, these mushroommen deserve death!" Tu clan village's leader shouted.

"Stop fighting, stop fighting!" Le Tu's entire body shook, he was completely lost at the moment.

A dark light flashed in the eyes of Tu clan village's leader as he thought of a plan.

His cultivation level was higher than Huang Wan, with the latter injured from the sneak attack, Tu clan village's leader had the upper hand, he controlled the situation.

Tu clan village's leader purposely forced Huang Wan to approach a certain Gu Master of Tu clan village.

This Tu clan Gu Master unfortunately fell into Huang Wan's attack range, but his cultivation level was only rank two.

Huang Wan did not think much about it, her attack landed on this Tu clan Gu Master and killed him on the spot!

"No!" Le Tu shouted, subconsciously running over.

It turned out that this Tu clan Gu Master was his close ally, they had gone through dangerous situations many times in the past.

"Go away, Ah Le!" Huang Wan saw that Le Tu charged in, she screamed with a pale expression.

Tu clan village's head used the chance to attack thrice, landing three attacks on her as she fainted on the spot.

"Mother!" Le Tu shouted, using his body to block the leader's path, protecting Huang Wan behind him: "Don't harm my mother!"

Tu clan village's leader burst out with killing intent, he was about to attack when he suddenly heard some shouting from afar.

"The mushroomman tribe's reinforcements!"

"Their tribe leader arrived too."

Tu clan village's head squinted as he thought: "We came here stealthily without many people, but they are all elites, it is not worth losing them over these mushroommen. Moreover, so what if we win? As long as we cannot find the mushroomman tribe's hideout, they will not lose against us."

Thinking so, Tu clan village's head ordered: "Retreat."

"What are you thinking of doing?" Seeing Tu clan village's head approach, the bald youngster called out nervously.

Tu clan village head sighed as he showed a gentle expression on his face: "Le Tu, I will not attack you. You are my son after all, but your mother, she is a mushroomman."

"A variant human!" His voice suddenly became sharper and louder.

"Do you want to side with the variant humans?!" Tu clan village's head shouted again.

Le Tu gritted his teeth but did not speak.

"All these years, how many mushroommen have you killed? Do you think they will accept you if you side with them?" Tu clan village's head smiled coldly.

Le Tu snorted coldly, staring at Tu clan village's head fiercely: "I want my mother to live! If you have any ill intentions towards her, I will not let you off."

Tu clan village's head chuckled: "If you continue keeping her in that state, in just a while, she will die from her injuries."

"This..." Le Tu was completely lost at the moment.

Tu clan village's head suddenly attacked, causing Le Tu to faint, he brought both son and mother away.

"Kill!"

"Kill these humans!"

"Bring Huang Wan back, she knows the secret of our tribe's hideout!!"

The mushroomman Gu Masters chased relentlessly.

The Huang Xiao Mi that Meng Qiu Zhen was portraying also shouted among them, but he did not do anything.

Because he had already used dream butterfly Immortal Gu to check the next scene.

After the mushroomman Gu Masters failed in their pursuit, Meng Qiu Zhen arrived at the next scene.

This time, he became Huang Wan again.

His body was bound by chains that pierced through his bones, he had no primeval essence at all, he was completely out of strength.

In the dark prison cell, the door was suddenly opened.

Tu clan village's head walked in.

Meng Qiu Zhen squinted, from the situation of the previous scene, this was clearly an ambitious and formidable person!

Tu clan village's head smiled, he came prepared.

"You know my objective, don't be too rash to reject it. Let me show you this." Tu clan village's head took out an information path Gu worm.

Immediately, a video played itself in the air, the scene within it was vivid and lively.

In a well decorated room, Tu clan village's head opened the door and met with Le Tu.

"I heard from my subordinates that you are awake, I immediately came to meet you, my son." Tu clan village's head had a warm expression.

Le Tu was covered in bandages, the moment he got out of bed, his body wavered as he fell back onto the bed.

"How is my mother now?" Le Tu immediately asked in an urgent tone.

[1] These are the same characters as Paradise Earth, his later venerable title. Back

Chapter 2149: I Confess Everything

Tu clan village head sighed deeply: "Your mother is a noble mother, for your sake, she took a huge risk and stayed within Tu clan village for so many years."

Tu clan village head's tone suddenly changed: "But I cannot let her off, she is a mushroomman, a variant human!"

"You are also clear about these mushroommen. Those of other races will have different motives, the best outcome for these mushroommen is death!"

"But you are different, you are my son. You know that I have no other children, you are my only son!"

"Ah Le, come and help me. Only I can accept you here, this Tu clan village is your home."

"As your father, I owe you a lot, I will do my best to make up to you in the future."

"After this huge battle, you have already accumulated sufficient credits. I know that you want the Tu surname, originally, the village would need to test you, but father will allow it now. From today onwards, you will be a true Tu clansman. With the new surname, you will no longer be Le Tu, you will be called Tu Le!"

"Child, father is proud of you. This is your new life!"

Le Tu laughed loudly, his voice was filled with mockery and sadness.

The goal that he had always pursued was finally achieved, but he felt no sense of accomplishment or happiness.

"I don't want the Tu surname, I want to exchange for my mother's life using all the contributions I've done for Tu clan village over these years!" Le Tu called out.

But Tu clan village's head had an expressionless face, he shook his head with a firm attitude.

Le Tu gritted his teeth, blood flowing out from his teeth as he pointed at Tu clan village head: "If you kill my mother, I will not live alone. In fact, I will stake my life against yours!"

"Ah Le!!" Tu clan village's head shouted coldly.

Le Tu did not speak, he stared at Tu clan village head fixedly.

The atmosphere in the room became immensely tense.

The father and son stared at each other with a deathly gaze, eventually, the expression of Tu clan village's head changed.

He shifted his sight towards the ceiling as he sighed deeply to himself.

His sigh was filled with complex emotions. There was anger, hatred, helplessness, and sadness.

Tu clan village's head looked at Le Tu deeply as he said with deep emotions: "All these years, father did not discover you. I really owe you a lot, my son. If I had taken care of you, things would not have gotten to this stage."

"Never mind!"

"Since it was my fault, I will satisfy your request."

"I will let your mother escape, but I will only let her go secretly."

"However, the mushroomman tribe needs to be eradicated, not a single one of them will be left!"

"This is your father's limit, it is also the greatest compromise I can give you as the head of Tu clan village. Ah Le, you need to understand my difficulties as well."

Le Tu's expression was immediately moved, he gulped: "Village... village head, as long as you let my mother off, I don't care about those mushroomman tribe members!"

All these years, Le Tu had been fighting against the mushroomman tribe, they had immense grudges and mutual hatred.

He only cared about Huang Wan after all.

"Good child!" Tu clan village's head was very excited, he patted Le Tu's shoulders: "But I cannot let your mother go now. You know that even though we have the advantage, as long as we cannot find the mushroomman tribe's location, we cannot obtain true victory."

"But your mother knows the location of the mushroomman tribe, she knows how to find them. Ah Le, I need your help, convince your mother to tell us this secret."

"I promise you, I assure you, as long as we eliminate the mushroomman tribe and get rid of this huge threat, I will let your mother off and she will live in peace for the rest of her life."

"This..." Le Tu hesitated.

Even though he wanted to eliminate the mushroomman tribe, he understood that his mother had deep feelings for her tribe.

Tu clan village's head patted Le Tu's shoulders, saying in a kind tone: "Father will not force you, think about it yourself. You are still injured, you need to recuperate. I will give you enough time to think, I believe in you!"

The video ended here.

Tu clan village's head smiled coldly as he approached Huang Wan: "What do you think? Do you want your own son to come and convince you personally?"

"Think about it, Wan Er."

"You can disregard your own life, but what about your son's life?"

"If our relationship really turns sour, neither of you will have a good ending."

"I may not kill him."

"But I just need to send him to fight on the front lines and kill all of your tribesmen, what do you think?"

Meng Qiu Zhen looked at Tu clan village head with a look of appreciation: "Unscrupulous and shameless, you are quite something."

"Hahaha, a great person would not mind small sacrifices! Have you just found out about it, it is too late now!" Tu clan village head laughed loudly, but he felt that Huang Wan's gaze was not normal.

Meng Qiu Zhen nodded in a serious manner: "Exactly why I appreciate you."

As his laughter stopped abruptly, Tu clan village's head could not believe what he had just heard: "What did you say?"

Meng Qiu Zhen had a straightforward attitude, his gaze flickered: "Actually, you don't have to go through the trouble, don't you want to know the location of the tribe? I'll tell you directly."

"What?" Tu clan village's head was dazed.

Meng Qiu Zhen shrugged.

During this period, he used dream butterfly Immortal Gu to check the next scene, and the following one as well, he obtained crucial information.

In the end, Tu clan village's army attacks the headquarters of the mushroomman tribe, this meant that Tu clan village's head would learn of the location of the mushroomman tribe eventually.

In history, Huang Wan might not have exposed the location even after interrogation and torture, or after Tu clan village's head threatened her using her son.

But this was the dream realm, Huang Wan was not really Huang Wan, she was Meng Qiu Zhen.

"Not only will I tell you the location of the tribe, I'll even tell you that the tribe has a small secretive tunnel. You can send elites to attack it while the main troops are at the front." Meng Qiu Zhen suggested.

Tu clan village's head had a look of deep disbelief and suspicion.

The more cooperative Meng Qiu Zhen was, the less he believed in the words that were said.

Tu clan village's head was silent for a moment before he laughed coldly: "As a captive, you dare to toy with me? Good, very good, to think that you would disregard your own son, you are such a cold blooded person."

"No, listen to me. I am really telling you the truth." Meng Qiu Zhen said sincerely.

But Tu clan village's head shook his head, his voice became even colder: "I won't listen! Do you think I will believe you?"

"You can test out what I just said." Meng Qiu Zhen could not help but roll his eyes.

Tu clan village's head continued his cold snicker: "Do you think I am stupid? In the earlier battle, your mushroomman tribe created a trap. This time, it must be a trap too. You want me to lose my elite members."

Meng Qiu Zhen sighed deeply: "If you do not test it, what will you do now? Without knowing the mushroomman tribe's location, how can you attack?"

Tu clan village's head laughed loudly: "I am prepared for that."

Clap clap clap.

He clapped and said: "Master Wu Xiao, please come out."

"Wu Xiao greets Tu clan village's leader." A Gu Master with a grim expression, having a tall and thin body, was created by the dream realm.

"I'll let you know, this is the famous doctor of Southern Border, Master Wu Xiao. Did you think I came unprepared?" Tu clan village's head introduced.

Meng Qiu Zhen sighed: "What's the point of all this?"

Wu Xiao walked forward and used Gu worms to investigate Meng Qiu Zhen and said: "Reporting to village head, this captive has tight defenses, if we soul search her abruptly, not only will her soul dissipate immediately, it will even cause a backlash on the attacker and cause them to get badly poisoned."

Tu clan village's head nodded: "Precisely so, I asked for you to come here. Master Wu, you cultivate soul path, you can use soul healing methods and are one of the six great doctors of Southern Border. In the current Southern Border, only you can resist the mushroomman poison path methods, while preserving their souls at the same time."

Wu Xiao smiled proudly: "Village head, I am flattered, please watch me as I use my methods now."

Wu Xiao started to use his killer move on Meng Qiu Zhen.

Meng Qiu Zhen grunted, intense pain assaulted him as his body shuddered, cold sweat broke out.

The dream realm intensified at this moment, causing his soul foundation to dwindle.

"Stop it, don't you want to know their location? I'll tell you directly, isn't that enough?" Meng Qiu Zhen shouted.

"Do you think I will believe you? Wan Er, I know you too well, saying such words is an insult to my intelligence!" Tu clan village's head snorted and waved his sleeves in anger.

"Ahhh... ahh..." Meng Qiu Zhen pretended to cry out in agony: "I am telling the truth!"

Tu clan village's head was enraged: "You dare to lie further!"

"Ahhhh..." Meng Qiu Zhen pretended to have broken down: "I can't take it anymore, I'll tell you, I'll tell you everything."

Tu clan village's head waved his hand: "Say no more, I will soul search you either way."

Meng Qiu Zhen shut his mouth at this moment.

He was certain now.

At this juncture, he needed to pass the dream realm's test.

Some dream realms were like this, they could only be passed after expending soul foundation. If one's soul foundation was too low, they would die in this dream realm.

Guh.

Suddenly, Doctor Wu Xiao spat out a mouthful of blood.

He took several steps back, his forehead was covered in sweat, he panted heavily, there was purple blood flowing down his lips.

"Amazing, impressive! A poison within a poison, to think that there is such an amazing method in the world. To think that I was actually hit by it, it seems that I have to use my final method."

Wu Xiao turned his gaze to Tu clan village head, reporting: "But this method has a drawback."

"What drawback?"

"This is considered forceful soul search, the target would go insane, but their insane words are truthful thoughts!"

Tu clan village's head did not even look at Huang Wan, he said without hesitation: "Please go ahead and use your method, there is no need to hold back."

"Yes." Wu Xiao immediately took action.

A few moments later, Huang Wan went insane, she lost her mind completely.

This was the first time Meng Qiu Zhen had encountered such a situation.

This condition directly influenced his thoughts as well.

"Tell me the mushroomman tribe's location." Tu clan village's head asked.

Meng Qiu Zhen wanted to tell him the truth but his words that came out were: "La la la my homeland exists in my heart. Hehehe."

Huang Wan started to smile foolishly.

"How do I get into the mushroomman tribe's headquarters?" Tu clan village's head continued to ask.

"Use your legs to walk in, of course, you can crawl too. Hahaha..." Huang Wan started to laugh madly again.

Chapter 2150: Crazy Mother

Tu clan village head became anxious, he started to fire off questions.

But even though Huang Wan spoke the truth each time, her replies were all nonsensical.

Tu clan village head did not get the answer he wanted, he looked towards Doctor Wu Xiao with an unkind gaze.

Doctor Wu Xiao was shocked too: "Amazing, too amazing! This mushroomman's will is too strong, even though she lost her mind and has fallen into insanity, she became even purer as a result, each of her actions resonate with her true feelings. In her heart, she will definitely not betray her tribe, even if they exiled her. Tu clan village head, there is nothing else I can do."

"You..." Tu clan village head was very angry, he controlled himself: "Then Master Wu Xiao, you can go rest now."

In the jail cell, only Tu clan village head and Huang Wan were left.

Tu clan village head looked at Huang Wan and laughed coldly: "Don't worry, even if you are crazy, I can still make use of you. If I cannot get an answer from you, I will capture more mushroomman higher-ups and ask Master Wu Xiao to take action. I do not believe that I cannot find out the location of your mushroomman tribe!"

Thus, in the next scene, Meng Qiu Zhen turned into Huang Xiao Mi.

The elite Gu Masters of the mushroomman tribe were beside him.

The night was dark, they had already stealthily arrived near Tu clan village.

"Brother Xiao Mi!" Fang Tu secretly went to receive him.

These years, Fang Tu had received the help of Huang Wan and Le Tu, she started her cultivation journey and was now a rank two Gu Master.

She had received immense help from Huang Wan, because of her fortuitous encounter, she bore goodwill towards the mushroommen.

"How is the situation?" Meng Qiu Zhen asked immediately.

Fang Tu answered: "The village head is already prepared, tomorrow morning, Auntie Huang Wan will face the trial publicly, she will be beheaded! On the other hand, I have already found out about the location where Le Tu is kept in."

"Alright, we will split into two groups, one group will head to the execution ground and lay in ambush. The other group will save Le Tu and pass him those Gu worms that we prepared." Meng Qiu Zhen instructed.

The sky gradually lightened up.

Right when Huang Wan was about to be beheaded, Meng Qiu Zhen led the mushroomman Gu Masters to attack the execution ground.

"You came after all." Tu clan village head laughed.

"Everything has gone according to leader's estimations." The elders praised.

"Mother!" On the other hand, Le Tu also arrived with his reinforcements.

Tu clan village head frowned: "You chose the other side after all! Forget it, today, I will slay my kin in the name of justice, I will correct my past mistakes. Kill that pair of mother and son! Try your best to capture all the remaining mushroommen."

A chaotic battle started.

Tu clan village soon gained the upper hand, this was a trap that they had set in the first place.

The mushroomman tribe also predicted this but there was no choice. Huang Wan was the former witch, she knew too many secrets of the tribe, she could not be allowed to stay in Tu clan village.

Huang Xiao Mi and Le Tu fell into tough combat, they were surrounded by strong foes.

"To think that the day would come where we fight on the same side." Le Tu looked at Huang Xiao Mi, smiling bitterly.

Meng Qiu Zhen suddenly laughed heartily: "Don't worry, our reinforcements are here."

At the crucial moment, the dream realm changed once again as a large number of mushroomman Gu Masters joined the fight.

It turned out that the mushroomman tribe leader had gone all-out, he led the entire tribe to attack Tu clan village in a last ditch attempt.

To win or to die trying!

There was no other possible outcome!

Most of Tu clan village's higher-ups were at the execution ground, because of their temporarily weakened defenses, the mushroomman army actually broke in and charged all the way into Tu clan village.

An intense battle erupted.

The village head and tribe leader were both rank five, they fought against each other.

Le Tu and Huang Xiao Mi's alliance became the crucial element that could break this stalemate.

They were too familiar with each other, even though this was their first alliance, they had immense coordination in working together.

Both of them had rank four cultivation level, once they joined hands, their battle strength rose greatly, even Tu clan village's head could not resist them.

In the end, the mushroomman tribe won while Tu clan village suffered a terrible loss.

The remaining Gu Masters escaped into the prison, resisting with all their might, desperately attempting to survive.

Meanwhile, Tu clan village's head was heavily injured, he was on the brink of death, captured by the mushroomman tribe.

"Mother, how are you? What happened to you?"

Le Tu managed to save his mother in this chaotic battle after suffering huge injuries. But he found that Huang Wan had already gone mad.

Huang Wan looked at Huang Xiao Mi: "Son, oh son, you must live in happiness and bliss. That is why I named you Le Tu. Come, smile for mother, show me a smile."

"Oh mother..." Le Tu was covered in tears: "It was my fault, if I had not barged in, you would not have gotten hit by the village head! You would not be in such a state."

At this time, Wu Xiao was brought over.

He begged for mercy: "Don't kill me, don't kill me! I know what happened to your mother."

"Speak!" Le Tu roared.

Tu clan village head who was heavily injured smiled and replied in a cold tone: "Hahaha, your mother cannot be saved, she had gone completely insane. That's right, I caused it, this Doctor Wu Xiao is the direct culprit behind it as well."

"You will all die!!!" Le Tu's expression was distorted, he was about to make a move.

But Huang Wan suddenly stopped him: "Don't kill him, don't kill anyone! That is not good, you must be a kind person, you stupid rascal."

"Mother, you finally recognized me." Le Tu cried.

Slap.

Huang Wan suddenly slapped as Le Tu became stunned.

"Who are you calling mother! My son is right here." She grabbed Huang Xiao Mi, patting the latter's chest: "This is my son."

"Look at my son!" Huang Wan said proudly: "My son is so strong and tall! He is such a wonderful lad."

"Oh son." Huang Wan was smiling earlier but suddenly, she cried: "Mother let you down. I hid your identity from you and shaved your head because I was afraid that your hair might grow into a mushroom cap instead. Will you blame me?"

Le Tu wept in agony as tears flowed like a river.

But Huang Wan paid him no attention, she only looked at Huang Xiao Mi.

For the first time, Le Tu looked at Huang Xiao Mi in a pleading gaze.

Huang Xiao Mi nodded as he acted: "Mother, I won't blame you, you will always be my wonderful mother."

Huang Wan shed tears of joy as she said: "Stupid rascal, I'm glad you forgive me. But don't kill your father, don't kill anyone else. I want you to live in peace and happiness, that is all I want. Let them off, conflict and slaughter only breeds deeper conflict and hatred, it will make you empty, it will torture you, it will make you unhappy."

"If you are not happy, you will not be Ah Le anymore."

The surrounding people were silent.

Even Tu clan village head was the same.

"You want me to spare these people?!" Le Tu's eyes were red, he clenched his fists as his expression became distorted with rage.

"How can I do that?!" He forced that question out through the cracks between his teeth.

Tu clan village head smiled coldly, he had already lost completely, he became disheartened, he had no fear towards death.

But Doctor Wu Xiao suddenly shouted: "There is hope, there is still hope! Your mother still has a chance of regaining her sanity."

Le Tu grabbed Wu Xiao's shoulder and lifted him up: "Tell me, what method is it?"

Wu Xiao quickly answered: "Even though your mother is mad, she still has a bit of her mind left in her. Look at her actions and words, they are pure and sincere, this is her inner heart. As long as you do not go against her wishes, in time, her condition will not aggravate, her mind will grow and recover."

"After that, with my healing, she will definitely be able to recover, there is still hope!"

Wu Xiao shouted for his life, in order to live, he did not give up any opportunities.

Bam.

Le Tu threw Wu Xiao to the ground.

"Ah—!" Le Tu raised his head to the sky and shouted in pain and agony.

His two enemies were right in front of him, they were completely defenseless, but he could not take revenge!

For the sake of his mother, he had to follow her wishes.

"Fine, for my mother's sake, I will spare you two today." Le Tu gritted his teeth, he used so much force that his teeth were bleeding.

The dream realm ended here.

Meng Qiu Zhen's soul returned to his body, he sighed deeply to himself.

"To think that Paradise Earth had such an arduous and difficult life."

"Heroes often experience difficulties beyond an ordinary man."

"No wonder he had no hair in the depiction of his appearance that was left behind in history. But that green beast tattoo is also gone."

"Paradise Earth is actually the mixed blood of human and mushroomman? How did he become venerable?"

"After that, did he manage to save his mother?"

"When he was still young, he had a rash temper and deep killing intent, he was no different from any other person. How did he end up being the person he was?"

The dream realm gave Meng Qiu Zhen many questions.

And they could not be answered for now.

But the fact was that his attainment level had risen.

Fang Yuan's earth path attainment level jumped to great grandmaster!

Not only that, his poison path attainment also rose to great grandmaster.

Before this, Fang Yuan's poison path attainment level was at grandmaster. This dream realm that Paradise Earth left behind contained the true meaning of both earth path and poison path.

Fang Yuan took a risk to raise his dream path clone into an immortal, the gains were quite apparent now.

Not only were food path, poison path, and earth path elevated to great grandmaster, even luck path and ice and snow path were grandmaster now. Space path, metal path, wind path, cloud path, lightning path, information path, light path, and dark path were also at master level.

After passing Paradise Earth's dream realm, he only had a few dream realms left.

Before the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Fang Yuan would definitely be able to use up all of these dream realms.

At this moment, he had basically no weakness in most cultivation paths. However, painting path, weapon path, and pill path were still blank.

This could not be helped.

These paths did not exist in any of Spectral Soul's dream realms.

This might be part of Spectral Soul's plan, or maybe even he did not have attainment in those paths. After all, they were produced after Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's era. Meanwhile, painting path was kept in the hands of Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, he did not let any information leak out, it was even more secretive than Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's luck path inheritance.

Moreover, a portion of Spectral Soul's dream realms were taken by Feng Jin Huang while pursuing Fang Yuan.

But she obtained very few dream realms.

It was not worth it for Fang Yuan to take them back.

After all, Feng Jin Huang had immense luck.

After becoming an earth path great grandmaster, Fang Yuan immediately started to modify the details of his earth vein project, he saved a lot of cost and reduced the time needed for it.

"Looking at the time, Ke Xin Hong should have already arrived in Southern Border's Wu clan and met with Wu Yong?"

Fang Yuan counted and planned.

Chapter 2151: Refining Gu in Exchange for Famous Mountains

Southern Border.

Wu Yi Mountain, Wu clan's headquarters.

In a hall.

Ke Xin Hong had a faint smile as he greeted politely: "Ke Xin Hong pays respects to Wu clan's first supreme elder."

Wu Yong sat and smiled: "Esteemed envoy, no need to be so polite."

Ke Xin Hong spoke openly and straightforwardly: "I came here with fan wind Gu, it has already been refined and raised successfully. Please do examine it now."

Wu Yong could not help but feel surprised: "So quickly? Does Fang Yuan have a method to refine fake Immortal Gu, is he here to scam me?"

He received it and checked thoroughly, there were no flaws at all.

"It is a genuine rank eight Immortal Gu. But how can Fang Yuan refine a rank eight Immortal Gu in such a short period of time?" Thinking of this, Wu Yong was uncertain again.

In his mind, Fang Yuan's main traits were craftiness, viciousness, shamelessness, unscrupulous, and ruthlessness. This number one demon in the world could not be assessed using common sense.

"Envoy, please hold on, our Wu clan Gu Immortal will come and check it." Wu Yong answered.

Wu clan had their own refinement path Gu refinements, but they were not strong.

Wu clan was not specialized in refinement path, they were best at wind path. Not only in Southern Border, even in the five regions, Wu clan was first rate in wind path.

After a few minutes, Wu Yong received information that rank eight fan wind Gu was the real thing, it could not be fake.

Wu Yong had a complex emotion.

Immortal Gu were unique, because rank eight Immortal Gu were too hard to refine, they had an extremely important significance!

Ordinary rank eight Gu Immortals did not even have one rank eight Immortal Gu. For example, Old Ancestor Xue Hu lost everything that he had worked to accumulate for many years on Snowy Mountain blessed land after trying to refine fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu.

Of course, this was because his ambitions clashed with Heavenly Court's and Longevity Heaven's benefits.

"Even though the world has been changing in the last few years, with the movement of earth veins and rampaging of qi tides, a vast amount of immortal materials surfaced, it will likely cause a large increase in rank eight Immortal Gu. But for ordinary rank eight Gu Immortals, especially the lone immortals, they will still face problems getting one rank eight Immortal Gu."

"To think that my Wu clan has gained a new rank eight Immortal Gu."

Wu Yong was happy but also gained increasing wariness regarding Fang Yuan.

"Even though I know that Fang Yuan had annexed Lang Ya Sect, it is still hard to believe that his refinement path ability has become so incredible, it feels like he had an easy time refining a rank eight fan wind Gu with no problems encountered at all."

On the other hand, Ke Xin Hong added: "Since you have checked it, which two Immortal Gu does your clan want to refine next? I can bring them both back next time."

Wu Yong became hesitant.

Should he pass the seven-faced prestige wind Gu to Ke Xin Hong?

If he could refine eight-faced prestige wind Gu, Wu Yong would gain a huge boost in strength. But precisely so, seven-faced prestige wind Gu was extremely important.

If he gave it to Fang Yuan and the latter snatched it, what would he do?

"Come to think of it, there are many options." At this moment, Wu Yong felt that three chances were too few. He would want nothing more than to raise all of Wu clan's Immortal Gu to rank eight!

"To think that you acted so quickly, I am quite spoiled for choice at the moment, I need to think about it carefully. Envoy, why don't you stay here and give me three days to consider?" Wu Yong asked.

Wu Ba Chong heard this and added, urging Ke Xin Hong: "Speaking of which, this is the third time you've come to Wu clan, let us host you and bring you around."

"Alright." Ke Xin Hong smiled lightly: "I do like Wu clan's style a lot, I'll trouble you with my stay. As for first supreme elder's considerations, I understand. In fact, I have been tasked with another mission, I wonder if your clan would like to undergo another transaction with us?"

"What transaction?" Wu Yong became alert.

He thought of the secluded domain of heaven and earth Hu Land, it was akin to a quasi-rank nine Immortal Gu, but Fang Yuan forcefully bought it.

Thinking of this, Wu Yong felt a slight heartache again.

Ke Xin Hong explained the details while Wu Yong fell into contemplation.

Wu Ba Chong shouted in shock: "What? Fang Yuan wants to dig away our Wu clan's famous mountains? In return, he will refine rank eight Immortal Gu for our Wu clan?"

"Precisely." Ke Xin Hong nodded.

Wu Ba Chong snickered: "How can that be? Any famous mountain is a large resource point at least. Most of them are giant resource points, a select few are super resource points, they can produce rank eight immortal materials! Even though you can refine rank eight Immortal Gu, you are still using our Immortal Gu as the foundation to raise their rank, you are not giving us additional Immortal Gu."

"Furthermore, Immortal Gu are hard to feed, rank eight Immortal Gu are too. Even if they are refined, they will expend our resources. Yet, famous mountains are able to produce resources continuously, they will almost never dry out. You want to take our famous mountains, you are trying to cripple our foundation, what intentions do you have, what schemes are you up to?!"

Towards the end, Wu Ba Chong was basically screaming in anger.

But Ke Xin Hong was prepared for this, he spoke calmly: "Not so, not so at all. Elder Wu Ba Chong, you are too pessimistic about this. Think about it carefully, your clan has just gotten many Gu Immortal seeds to undergo immortal ascension recently, but you only gained six new immortals, with most of them being external members."

"Even with more Gu Immortals, Wu clan's territory is too big, you cannot defend it. Since that is the case, you might as well sell some territories. In that case, not only would Wu clan have higher ranked Immortal Gu, you will even have sufficient manpower."

"Furthermore." Ke Xin Hong continued: "Immortal Gu are unique, I am sure Elder Wu Ba Chong knows how priceless rank eight Immortal Gu are. Immortal materials can be sold and bought, but can Immortal Gu be easily bought? They are unique, they can only be traded. Even if treasure yellow heaven is the number one market in the world, let me ask you, how many Immortal Gu have been traded in it over these years?"

"The five regions are now one, the five regions chaotic war cannot be avoided. Gu Immortal battle strength is the most important thing, you can only consider the rest after having sufficient strength to defend yourself. A rank eight Immortal Gu can cause your clan's strength to rise sharply, not only can you protect yourself, you can invade others and gain a huge amount of wealth in war."

"This..." Wu Ba Chong hesitated.

Ke Xin Hong looked at Wu Ba Chong, he cast a secretive glance at Wu Yong without showing any signs, continuing to convince them.

"Human Smoke Mountain is Chai clan's headquarters, they sold it to us recently."

"What? There is such a thing?" Wu Ba Chong was stunned.

Ke Xin Hong did not elaborate further, he took a step back: "If Wu clan does not want this trade, we will not force you. This time, other than bringing back Immortal Gu for refinement, I also need to find other clans and undergo this trade with them."

Wu Ba Chong's expression changed mildly.

If Wu clan did not deal with Fang Yuan but the other clans did, their battle strength would surge instead.

Even if they give up on resources now and lose future potential, what if they decide to expand through invasion?

By then, if Wu clan refuses to work with Fang Yuan, their battle strength would be surpassed by other clans, by then, Wu clan would fall from their throne of the number one Southern Border force, they would be bullied by others.

Wu Yong tapped on the table with his finger as he fell into deep thought.

"Fang Yuan is so domineering even when doing business, he gives others no way of rejecting!"

"However, even though Ke Xin Hong is trying to convince us, he is not wrong about it."

"This trade is sensible, but we need to control the extent of our dealing!"

At almost the same time, in Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

"Gan Ni pays respects to master!" Earth Extremity of the Eight Extremities knelt before Immortal Zombie Giant Sun.

Earth Extremity Gan Ni was a female immortal, she cultivated earth path and refinement path, her refinement path attainment was quite deep.

At this moment, she held four rank eight Immortal Gu and handed them over respectfully.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun inspected them for some time and felt pleased: "Gan Ni, you are our Longevity Heaven's refinement path expert indeed. Since the fate war until now, you received my orders and refined four rank eight Immortal Gu, you have made a huge contribution."

Gan Ni quickly answered: "It was all thanks to master's luck path methods, otherwise, with just my mere talent, we could not have refined so many rank eight Immortal Gu in these few years. But because of that, Longevity Heaven's luck fell greatly..."

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun interrupted her as he waved his hand: "In this world, there are losses where there are gains. To refine these Immortal Gu, luck expenditure was a necessary investment."

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun took one of these four Immortal Gu and observed it carefully in front of him.

This Gu had a peculiar shape, it was cubic and resembled a wooden box.

This was imitation Gu, it was eighth place on the List of Mystical Gu, originating from Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable!

If one placed this Gu with any Immortal Gu in the world together for some time, the Gu cultivator could activate imitation Gu to turn itself into that Immortal Gu.

Immortal Gu were unique, but imitation Gu could bypass this logic to some extent. However, the imitated Gu could not compare to the real one in power.

Back then, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable asked Heavenly Court for human qi Immortal Gu and failed.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable took another path, refining imitation Gu and turning it into human qi Immortal Gu. Next, with this 'human qi Immortal Gu' as the core, he established Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Other than this imitation Gu, the other three rank eight Immortal Gu were all blood path Immortal Gu!

Divine Emperor City.

Light flickered, the ten children of human path came out of the painting world, returning to the real world.

"We... are finally back."

"It is a pity that we did not manage to take down those two new paintings."

"We were nurtured by Heavenly Court but the time is up, we needed to leave."

"What are you worried about? Even though we did not take it down entirely, the situation has been set. There are so many beast tamers in the painting world, even cultivators have appeared. Moreover, with the deep foundation that we created, there is no chance of failure."

"That's true."

After the ten children of human path conversed for some time, their sect's Gu Immortals arrived to bring them back.

Qin Ding Ling and the rest concealed their traces, watching the scene unfold before them.

"These ten people are the human path immortal seeds of our Heavenly Court. Regardless of the results from this Crazed Demon Cave expedition, we need to nurture these people, invest fully in them!" Qin Ding Ling announced.

"Yes, madam." The Gu Immortal in charge listened to Qin Ding Ling's words and engraved it in his mind.

"Let's go." Qin Ding Ling turned around and said to Genesis Lotus' will.

Genesis Lotus' will nodded.

At the next moment, Divine Emperor City moved, the huge city flew up again, heading straight from Central Continent with unparalleled momentum.

The target was Crazed Demon Cave!

Chapter 2152: Earth Vein's Initial Formation

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Several variant human men gathered into a circle, they were busily engaging in an important business.

"Slowly, slowly."

"Guys, relax a little, don't be so anxious."

"Faster, faster, I can't endure it anymore."

Bam.

A loud sound was heard.

A gigantic hill landed on the ground.

This hill was not tall, it did not have clear waters of beautiful vegetation, there were mostly dust rocks and iron cloud stones on the mountain, causing it to look grey in most areas.

And most amazingly, this entire hill was completely silent.

Even though there were many life forms, when Gu Immortals spoke here, no sound could be transmitted unless they used specific methods.

This was silent hill.

It had the same reputation as Western Desert's anti-sound desert, famous in the world. Any sound path killer move used here would be greatly weakened and suppressed.

Silent hill was a famous mountain in Southern Border, but because it produced little resources, it had not been very useful to anyone.

This time, Fang Yuan sent envoys all over the place to negotiate in transactions.

Silent hill was sold to Fang Yuan as a result, these variant human Gu Immortals moved in groups, they were in charge of moving silent hill back into a specific location of the sovereign immortal aperture.

But relocation was just the first step, next, they had to develop its mountain roots.

The one in charge of this was a rockman Gu Immortal.

He activated a method as silent hill's mountain roots began to grow rapidly, stabbing into the surrounding environment.

"Deeper, go deeper!" The leader instructed as he suddenly sighed: "Sigh, why did you stop? Are you finished so quickly?"

The rockman Gu Immortal said impatiently: "Say, leader, can you keep quiet? I want to go deeper too, but I only have rank seven cultivation level. This is a famous mountain, it is very exhausting to influence and manipulate its mountain roots!"

But the leader said: "That's why I said you need to work harder. Your cultivation level is too low, when will you become a rank eight?"

The rockman Gu Immortal rolled his eyes: "Boss, I was still rank six some time ago, I only went to pass the tribulation and reached rank seven because of our master. I also want to reach rank eight, but that is just too difficult."

The other Gu Immortals quickly spoke.

"Leader is right, in our group, you're the only one that can deal with the mountain roots, allowing them to grow thick and long. If you were stronger, we would complete our mission to a greater extent, we would receive better rewards as well."

"You are in charge of the mountain veins, your contribution is the highest among us!"

"I heard that you went to sleep recently?"

"I have not slept in two months, I have been doing mountain relocation missions the entire time."

"Master has such grand ambitions and inspirations, he is managing a project to create artificial earth veins. But this plan will eventually be completed, aren't we grabbing onto this chance when it is available to us? Look at the other groups, the more missions they complete, the fewer we will have for ourselves."

The other Gu Immortals stared at the rockman Gu Immortal, they had a look of expectation and disappointment.

The rockman Gu Immortal was very helpless: "Don't you guys know? We rockmen have no lack of sleep in our lives. Because our bodies are too heavy, it is a huge burden on our soul. We need to sleep to pacify our soul."

"Then use the liver life formation!"

"I already used it."

"On master's contribution board, aren't there soul path methods to raise your soul foundation?"

"But I cultivate earth path, soul path methods are less effective on me. Instead of using my contribution points on them, I might as well raise my earth path attainment instead."

The leader gritted his teeth: "Stop arguing, let's pool our funds and help our little rockman brother. Let's gather some points and raise his soul foundation."

The other Gu Immortals agreed together.

Right now, the rockman Gu Immortal was their group's weakness, if he got stronger, the entire group would benefit from it.

Fang Yuan handed out all sorts of missions, they were created after wisdom path deductions, their contents were simple but they had deep meaning.

Be it the difficulty of the mission or the content itself, Gu Immortals often had to cooperate with others, it was hard to do any mission alone.

This gave the Gu Immortals of various races a chance to work together intimately.

After a long period of cooperation, they naturally developed camaraderie and friendship.

Thus, within the entire sovereign immortal aperture, all the different tribes and races were seamlessly fusing together into one big community.

Humans, rockmen, feathermen, inkmen, snowmen, and others, they were all working together, contributing blood and sweat for the sake of building their wonderful homeland.

"Excellent, silent hill has been relocated already. All the famous mountains are distributed around the mini five regions, the most basic requirement has been met, we can now start developing the earth vein."

Fang Yuan had been paying huge attention to the famous mountain relocation plan.

After seeing the situation over at silent hill, he started to take action personally.

In order to construct the earth vein, he had already created many immortal formations in the important areas of the mini five regions.

At this moment, Fang Yuan willed as immortal essence was expended, the immortal formations started to activate on their own.

The ground of the mini five regions was shaking with greater intensity as time passed.

The variant humans living in the various areas were lost and confused, while some showed expressions of joy.

"What is happening? Is there another earthquake?" Most of the mortal Gu Masters did not understand the situation.

"Master has started to take action. Oh heavens, he is affecting the entire mini five regions in one go, this is truly a huge project!" The Gu Immortals sensed the situation, they all felt intense joy and also deeper admiration towards Fang Yuan.

Rumble...

The ground continued to rumble but the extent was not too severe, there was not much loss from this.

An earth vein started to form in a chain due to the effect of the Gu formations in various areas, using the famous mountains as its various nodes.

This earth vein crossed through the mini five regions, it was present in Mini Eastern Sea, Mini Central Continent, Mini Northern Plains, Mini Southern Border, and Mini Western Desert.

If one looked from above, this earth vein would resemble an irregular geometric shape, the lines were very clear and simple, it barely covered the area of half the mini five regions.

The earth vein was successfully constructed, the ground returned to normal.

The immortal formations of various places came to a halt, they were basically fueled by immortal materials that were almost completely expended, the formations were now incomplete and could not be used again.

Fang Yuan started to carefully assess the outcome.

He was very patient and thorough, after some time, he nodded in satisfaction.

It had gone according to plan, the entire earth vein was created perfectly, no flaws could be observed.

Of course, this had to do with the simple design of the artificial earth vein, it was simply too crude.

The truth was, the hardest part of the artificial earth vein project was not the creation of the earth vein. The problem was the way to gather enough famous mountains to use as the nodes of the various regions' earth vein.

The second hardest thing was the method to create an artificial earth vein.

"The earth vein is completed in its initial state, it is quite crude now and does not have an immediate impact on the entire sovereign immortal aperture. In fact, it might even cause problems to occur frequently during this initial period, but after some time when things go back to normal, the sovereign immortal aperture will become more stable than before!"

Fang Yuan estimated in his mind, he withdrew his attention from the sovereign immortal aperture and used Cooking Luck Pot to inspect his luck again.

With one glance, Fang Yuan's eyes shined, joy was expressed in his gaze.

The creation of his artificial earth vein had a huge effect on his luck.

His luck was originally a grand pillar of silver light, but it was quite loose like cloud soil, it could scatter with one touch.

Now, even though the silver pillar was smaller, it became more condensed.

This was quite an assuring development.

"But the luck of the other venerables has also grown stronger." Fang Yuan frowned to himself.

At the top of the silver light pillar, three clouds were looming over it, they represented Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, and Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Star Constellation's cloud was still in control of the first level, it had expanded slightly.

Spectral Soul was at the second level, while Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was at the third.

But there was an odd scene now, Star Constellation's cloud seemed to be devouring Spectral Soul's cloud.

This scene was quite confusing to Fang Yuan, he had many guesses in his mind but he was not certain about anything.

There was also another transformation.

At the bottom of the silver light pillar, yellow-brown dust started to spin around it again. This earthy dust moved around the silver light pillar, seemingly stabilizing it.

Through luck inspection, Fang Yuan confirmed that the artificial earth vein plan was very useful to himself, he became even more resolved to continue this plan.

"But after getting an earth vein, I can no longer use myriad beings assimilation transformation." Fang Yuan reminded himself.

Myriad beings assimilation transformation killer move was the ultimate method of Beast Calamity Immortal, it contained the highest profundity of transformation path, able to turn dao marks of all other paths into transformation path dao marks. It could even influence heaven path dao marks, thus all sorts of tribulations could turn into beast calamities.

Fang Yuan's main body could not use it anymore.

This move that transformed dao marks had a huge effect on the sovereign immortal aperture's habitat.

Fang Yuan had a terrifying number of dao marks now, ignoring anything else, just refinement path dao marks alone amounted to over six million. If these six million dao marks suddenly turned into another path's dao marks, the sovereign immortal aperture would not be able to adapt to the change.

By then, a huge issue would occur in the environment, the terrifying tribulation that occurs would have unimaginable consequences!

For example, it was like a fish swimming in water but the water turned into lava, it was easy to guess the outcome of the fish.

In the past, when Fang Yuan used myriad beings assimilation transformation, the sovereign immortal aperture's development was still quite low, there were very few life forms inside. At that time, he also had far fewer dao marks.

If he used myriad beings assimilation transformation now, there would be too many dao marks transformed, it could not be done. But if he transformed fewer dao marks instead, against venerables, it would not have any purpose in combat.

Immortal killer move — Heaven and Earth Travel!

At the next moment, Fang Yuan's main body went from Eastern Sea to Southern Border.

A tall mountain peered into the clouds, frost energy emanated from it, its mountain roots were cut already, Fang Yuan was here to retrieve it after the preparations were done.

This was Frosty Peak.

Back then, Fang Yuan disguised as Wu Yi Hai and sneaked into Wu clan, he had gotten into conflict with Xia clan over this mountain.

Frosty Peak was a famous mountain of course, it produced ice and snow path resources. However, the originally white and beautiful Frosty Peak was now littered with holes all over as a result of excessive excavation, not only was it ugly, the production of resources was also affected.

Thus, this Frosty Peak was sold to Fang Yuan by Wu clan.

At this moment, there were many Gu Immortals surrounding Frosty Peak.

Other than the variant human Gu Immortals that Fang Yuan dispatched, Wu clan's Gu Immortals were here as well, Wu Yong was among them.

"Fang Yuan, have you been well?" Wu Yong took the initiative to greet him, showing a complex expression at the same time.

Chapter 2153: Lord Fang Yuan, Time to Get Going!

Wu Yong wanted to meet Fang Yuan personally.

If the pursuit of Fang Yuan had just ended, Wu Yong would not dare to get close to him at all.

Fang Yuan was the number one demon in the world, Wu Yong would not dare to approach him, there was a threat of getting killed.

It was too dangerous!

But now was different.

Fang Yuan had an entire series of methods for foreign affairs, he engaged in transactions with many major forces without using brute strength.

The initial effect might be small but after so long, super forces like Wu clan, Fang clan, and Chai clan could see that Fang Yuan was someone who could work with principles and rules.

After these super forces reassessed Fang Yuan, they decided to work with him.

It was not easy to reach this stage.

Would a rabbit have the guts to make transactions with a wolf?

"But this man in front of me achieved this feat." Wu Yong looked at Fang Yuan while feeling complicated internally.

Wu Yong was a current generation hero, his talent and aptitude were top rate even among rank eight Gu Immortals. Seeing Fang Yuan's actions these days, even Wu Yong sighed to himself as he developed feelings of admiration.

Having strength but not abusing it or bullying the weak casually, this was not something easy to achieve. On the surface, this seemed like the demeanor of someone with self-control and an understanding that one could not abuse their advantage or they would eventually falter. But the truth was, he was unaffected by greed or ambition, his logic had always suppressed other emotions.

In the current world, no, throughout time, throughout the history of mankind, how many people could reach this stage?

Fang Yuan could even make these weaker forces undergo transactions with him without worries. Initially, there was only Wu clan, but Wu Yong soon found that almost all super forces were transacting with him, they sold some useless famous mountains in exchange for the chance to refine rank eight Immortal Gu.

This was not easy.

It showed that Fang Yuan had incredible interpersonal skills.

Be it through threatening or temptation, even if he used other methods, the result was that he succeeded.

"Fang Yuan is truly an incredible person! Even though he started from the demonic path, his mannerism and mindset has never been restrained by shallow ideas like factions."

"He can be righteous or demonic, he can either help the world or cause chaos in the world, everything depends on the methods he adopt. Even throughout history, such a demon is truly the most terrifying."

"Being born in the same generation as this person is also my blessing."

Wu Yong was wary of Fang Yuan, he had felt disappointment and rage because of Fang Yuan, but he had also gained morale and inspiration, he even saw the beauty of life because of Fang Yuan.

Because from Fang Yuan, he saw himself, it was a testament to his own ideals.

He had too many similarities with Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's series of actions during this period allowed Wu Yong to see Fang Yuan's vision, he knew that Fang Yuan was someone who saw ten steps ahead of each action.

"Since everyone's opinions and actions have changed because of Fang Yuan, why can't I try to cooperate even more deeply with him?" After losing Hu Land, Wu Yong developed this thought.

What to do with an enemy you could not beat?

The best way was to cooperate with them, to turn from enemies to allies!

Cooperating with Fang Yuan had huge potential for gains, it was very helpful to Wu clan.

Wu Yong was someone with high restraint, but he also had the honor of the righteous path.

Except that the honor of an ambitionist like him was worth less than a piece of paper. As long as the benefits were high enough, Wu Yong could tear this paper into pieces with no second thought.

Thus, Wu Yong took the initiative to come and meet with Fang Yuan personally, he wanted to talk and try to see if he could deepen their cooperation!

Seeing Wu Yong, Fang Yuan also revealed a faint smile.

Wu Yong had once chased after his life, but so what?

If you can kill me, that is testament to your strength! This is a world where the strongest survive, if I die because of you, that is because I am weak, it is my own lack of capability, it is my fault!

The weak were devoured by the strong, was this not a natural thing?

Thus, in Fang Yuan's heart, he had never felt any pointless hatred or grudge.

Wu Yong came here of his own accord, his intention to cooperate was obvious, then let's cooperate!

For Fang Yuan, working with Wu clan had benefits and gains too.

Wu Yong was the leader of the Southern Alliance, while Wu clan was the number one super force in Southern Border. They would become a role model for other forces if they chose to cooperate.

Like how Fang Yuan traded with other forces for famous mountains, he had used Wu clan's transaction records to tempt them.

But just when Fang Yuan was about to talk with Wu Yong, a Gu Immortal flew over in the sky.

This Gu Immortal was dressed in a grey hemp garment and conical hat, he had a muscular body and a chin that was wide and thick, it was Lu Wei Yin.

He had always been calm and composed, but now, he showed an anxious expression.

Lu Wei Yin saw Fang Yuan and shouted from afar: "Lord Fang Yuan, I finally found you!"

"What's the matter?" Fang Yuan smiled.

Lu Wei Yin flew towards Fang Yuan, casting a glance at Wu Yong but not greeting him.

Wu Yong became quite curious, he had never seen Lu Wei Yin in such a frantic state.

Lu Wei Yin spoke directly in front of Fang Yuan: "Lord Fang Yuan, do you know that yesterday, Divine Emperor City brought Heavenly Court's immortals from Central Continent straight towards Northern Plains' Crazed Demon Cave!"

"Oh?" Fang Yuan's expression moved slightly.

Lu Wei Yin continued: "Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has likely revived, if she joins up with Heavenly Court, they will be able to work together, Crazed Demon Cave's situation will be very dangerous. There is no time, we need to head there immediately and take control of the situation!"

"What?" Wu Yong heard this and felt incredibly shocked.

What in the world was going on?

Why were Heavenly Court and Crazed Demon Cave involved in something?

Wu Yong was very perceptive, he immediately realized that this was an incredibly important fight. Regardless of the result, it would definitely affect the entire Gu Immortal world, as well as the five regions and two heavens!

But Fang Yuan was not anxious, he consoled Lu Wei Yin: "Your information network is really broad. But don't worry, don't be anxious, I still have matters to settle."

Saying this, Fang Yuan used a method to put Frosty Peak into the sovereign immortal aperture.

"How can I not be anxious?" Lu Wei Yin took off his hat as he stared with wide eyes, urging: "We are going against Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven, the location is also Limitless Demon Venerable's Crazed Demon Cave, as well as that secluded domain of heaven and earth, Primordial Domain. Lord Fang Yuan, we cannot lose our initiative in this fight."

"What? What? Heavenly Court, Longevity Heaven... Limitless Demon Venerable... and Primordial Domain? The secluded domain of heaven and earth recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>?" Wu Yong had more and more questions in his mind, he felt more anxious as well.

He wanted to know everything.

Fang Yuan had a solemn expression: "I know that you want to make contributions, I've already promised you. If Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable wants to revive, I will help you. But I have my own judgment towards the situation, if I do not use my time to strengthen myself, how can I go up against the venerables? There is no need to rush me any further."

"This..." Lu Wei Yin pondered without speaking further.

Fang Yuan turned to Wu Yong as he smiled again: "Wu Yong, regarding the sale of famous mountains, I think we can expand the scale of transactions. For example, Moon Bowl, Corpse Mountain, Phoenix Peak, or Corpse Emperor Yu Ding Tian, and others."

Wu Yong showed a difficult expression: "These famous mountains have higher value than Frosty Peak. The true value of Phoenix Peak is that phoenixes will gather every year to lay eggs. If you take the mountain, it might not have great value anymore."

"As for Corpse Emperor Yu Ding Tian or Corpse Mountain, they are things that Wu clan needs. Not long ago, we obtained the enslavement path true inheritance of the Corpse Emperor, we are trying to develop and use it, these two mountains are not for sale."

"As for Moon Bowl, as long as the price is reasonable, we can consider selling it."

Wu Yong spoke with a sincere tone but his mind was wandering elsewhere.

He had been anticipating this conversation for a long time. But because of Lu Wei Yin's words earlier, Wu Yong's attention was drawn away to the issue instead.

Fang Yuan negotiated with Wu Yong for some time, Lu Wei Yin was left unattended beside them.

Fang Yuan truly needed more famous mountains now.

Even though the earlier transactions were helpful, they were mostly useless mountains. But if Wu clan led the transaction, this huge deal between Fang Yuan and Southern Border's super forces could go one step further.

After the discussion, Fang Yuan waved his sleeves: "Alright, I'll see you both another time."

Lu Wei Yin stretched out his hand: "Lord Fang Yuan..."

Before leaving, Fang Yuan cast a cold glance at him: "I have other matters to attend to."

Lu Wei Yin could not speak any of the words that he had bottled up inside.

At the next moment, heaven and earth travel was activated, Fang Yuan vanished on the spot.

He really had things to do.

This time, he went to Rotten Mud Mountain and took the mountain.

"Sigh!" Lu Wei Yin sighed deeply to himself.

Wu Yong smiled: "We have not met for some time. Why don't we..."

Lu Wei Yin waved his hand: "Wu Yong, I have matters to attend to, when I am free, I will definitely visit Wu Yi Mountain."

Saying so, Lu Wei Yin left.

He did not have the mood to explain things to Wu Yong.

Wu Yong also had a bunch of bottled up questions, he felt horrible internally.

He immediately turned his gaze towards the variant human Gu Immortals that were present.

His smile did not change, he asked these people.

But what did these variant human Gu Immortals know?

The leader replied calmly: "Without master's permission, how can us subordinates speak out of line? Please do not blame us, Lord Wu Yong, we need to continue moving the mountains."

Wu Yong was helpless as he watched these people leave.

Even though he spoke to Fang Yuan and achieved his original goal, Wu Yong could not be happy.

He sensed acutely that he was starting to get left behind by Fang Yuan and others. He had no idea what was going on in Crazed Demon Cave, for example.

"No wonder Fang Yuan is trying to work with the major forces... Star Constellation Immortal Venerable revived? One can only imagine the pressure he is facing."

"Maybe I should use this to haggle for more conditions with Fang Yuan?"

After understanding Fang Yuan's difficulties, Wu Yong started to develop some thoughts.

"Wait." His eyes burst with bright light: "Lu Wei Yin could have transmitted those words to Fang Yuan, why did he speak in front of me purposely? It is likely that I can gain more information by asking him. He rejected me earlier to try to raise his status and get a higher price."

Wu Yong smiled bitterly internally.

He knew that if he contacted Lu Wei Yin now, he would be extorted by the latter.

But if he did not ask for information, how could he know if there was a chance to benefit from this situation?

Chapter 2154: Looting Everything

Immemorial white heaven.

Intense winds blew, Fang Yuan's hair fluttered in the wind as a result.

After preparation, he activated his killer move.

A rank eight earth path grotto-heaven was devoured by the sovereign immortal aperture under Fang Yuan's method.

Like what he did earlier, Fang Yuan did not annex this grotto-heaven wholly, he chose to split it into different portions and placed them into the sovereign immortal aperture's various areas.

Of course, because this was a rockman earth path grotto-heaven, most of it landed in the mini five regions, only a small portion ended up in the mini nine heavens.

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

As profound light faded, a mountain range appeared in Mini Central Continent out of nowhere.

"It's here, it's here, our tribe's Myriad Ravine Mountain Range!" Shi San Bai was incredibly excited.

"Yes, this is our former Sacred Mountain, but now that it is inside the sovereign immortal aperture, it has become quite ordinary." Shi Gua Bi had a complex expression, he felt dejected but also happy.

These few rockman Gu Immortals gathered together for this moment.

They were the Gu Immortals of this former grotto-heaven, but they were sent into Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture in advance.

During this period of time, their cultivation levels rose rapidly, they also gained many Immortal Gu. They were simply on a whole new level than before.

"Let's go, let's go in." The rockman Gu Immortals flew into Myriad Ravine Mountain Range.

"Greetings to supreme ancestor!"

"The ancestors have finally returned!!!"

Myriad Ravine Mountain Range still had a large number of rockman Gu Masters, after seeing the rockman Gu Immortals, they cheered loudly.

"Indeed, this is our new home."

"We have a bright future living here."

After the rockman Gu Immortals gave them a speech, they started to take action.

They had missions to do.

This Myriad Ravine Mountain Range was a famous mountain too, it was going to be one of the cores of an earth vein.

Fang Yuan spent several hours annexing this earth path grotto-heaven, during the process, certain changes developed in various places across the sovereign immortal aperture.

In Star Collection City, Combat Beast King held the fort as he observed the commotions in the sovereign immortal aperture along with other Gu Immortals.

"During this period of time, master annexed several grotto-heavens and caused the dao marks to rise in number. It can be expected that the various areas of the sovereign immortal aperture will have increasing commotion over time, with rising intensity."

"Isn't this good? The more incidents there are, the more missions we have to do."

"Sigh, when will our tribe's grotto-heaven be annexed by master?"

The Gu Immortals talked among themselves, feeling expectant towards their future prospects.

Their mindsets had already changed drastically.

In the past, they were against Fang Yuan annexing their grotto-heavens, but now the situation was different, they looked forward to it. It was as if they could not gain their master's acknowledgement if their grotto-heaven had not been annexed. Many Gu Immortals who had their immortal apertures annexed felt that they were a true part of the sovereign immortal aperture, they felt superior to the Gu Immortals of the two heavens.

"Lord Fang Yuan, Lord Fang Yuan!" Lu Wei Yin shouted.

He flew over from afar.

Fang Yuan turned around and smiled: "It has been tough on you, you came all the way here to immemorial white heaven."

Lu Wei Yin smiled bitterly, he said in an urgent tone: "Lord Fang Yuan, you must know why I came here. Let's set off now, do you know that yesterday, a rank eight Immortal Gu House flew from immemorial black heaven to Crazed Demon Cave."

Fang Yuan nodded: "Many people saw that, the Immortal Gu House should be the one that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable left behind, Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace, right?"

"Indeed." Lu Wei Yin nodded continuously, staring at Fang Yuan: "Right now, Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court have moved. If we still do not start taking action, we are going to lose this prime opportunity."

Fang Yuan nodded: "Fine, let's go."

"Really?" Lu Wei Yin heard the answer he wanted, but he could not believe it.

These last days, he had used information path methods to urge Fang Yuan to go, but he kept on refusing it.

To think that Fang Yuan was actually going to move now.

"Can I confirm when Lord Fang Yuan will go?" Lu Wei Yin was still in disbelief.

Fang Yuan smiled: "How about now?"

Lu Wei Yin was overjoyed: "Lord Fang Yuan is truly resolute, that is the best answer, let's go, let's go!"

The truth was, Fang Yuan had already decided to go to Crazed Demon Cave now.

He had already used up all of the dream realms, his attainment levels rose accordingly.

Quasi-supreme grandmaster: refinement path, time path, enslavement path.

Great grandmaster: theft path, transformation path, rule path, qi path, fire path, wisdom path, water path, earth path, poison path.

Grandmaster: blood path, strength path, star path, dark path, formation path, soul path, sword path, human path, wood path, food path, phantom path, luck path, ice and snow path.

Master: dream path, space path, metal path, wind path, cloud path, lightning path, information path, light path, sound path.

As for the remaining paths like bone path, they were not at master level yet, but he still had some progress. Heaven path was the same.

Even though he did not reach Spectral Soul's level, Fang Yuan's attainment levels were already top rate in the current world. Be it breadth or depth, he could be considered the number one person in the world!

After all, Spectral Soul lost his attainment levels after leaving behind the dream realms, while Star Constellation and Giant Sun would not retain their supreme grandmaster attainment levels even if they revived now.

Of course, he still had insufficiencies.

For example, painting path, weapon path, and others, they were completely blank.

These paths were just too rare, painting path was intentionally concealed by Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, while weapon path was crudely created by Heavenly Court's Gu Immortal Che Wei recently.

With the rise of attainment level, Fang Yuan could annex more grotto-heavens, the sovereign immortal aperture reached its limit once again.

If there was some time to digest the new gains, the sovereign immortal aperture would become more stable.

But there was neither time nor opportunity.

Through luck inspection, Fang Yuan found that the situation had worsened again, even though there was still leeway, it had clearly gotten quite severe.

With a resolute decision, Fang Yuan immediately went to Northern Plains with Lu Wei Yin.

Ever since that pursuit battle over Fang Yuan ended, he had already used all his time to the limit, recuperating and raising his strength as much as he could.

Now, it was time to face the venerables head on!

Years had passed, Fang Yuan returned to Crazed Demon Cave again.

Initially, when he first came here, he only had rank seven cultivation level and was restricted by an alliance agreement.

Now, he looked down towards Crazed Demon Cave, ready to engage in battle with venerables.

The first layer of Crazed Demon Cave was a huge land of yellow soil.

This was a huge cave, it was almost circular at the entrance, spanning hundreds of kilometers, it looked extremely grand.

Inside the cave, there was a lush rain forest, filled with the colors yellow and green. Desolate beasts formed into groups, vines and trees tangled together, growling could be heard everywhere, it was a primitive sight.

"We will go down from there." Lu Wei Yin said.

"No rush." Fang Yuan raised his hand: "These immortal materials are useful to me."

He opened his immortal aperture's entrance, many variant human Gu Immortals were let out.

These Gu Immortals were talking among themselves, they went down in groups, causing chaos in the entire first layer.

"Quick, there is a desolate plant here!"

"Dig it up, bring it back."

"Oh oh, there's a group of desolate beast monkeys here, let's work together."

"Squeak squeak..." The monkey group cried out together.

"These rocks are immortal materials, bring them back, bring them all back."

"These are all contribution points!!"

The Gu Immortals worked enthusiastically, they were like a group of bandits that entered a mortal village.

Even though the first layer of Crazed Demon Cave had wild beasts and plants, Fang Yuan's subordinates were superior in numbers, there were also many rank eight Gu Immortals among them that possessed rank eight Immortal Gu and rank eight killer moves.

The first layer of Crazed Demon Cave was completely looted!

Lu Wei Yin watched with a dazed expression.

In just this short period of time, how did Fang Yuan's subordinates become so strong, didn't their strength rise too absurdly?

"I have too many people under me, our resource expenditure is very high, especially when I made the artificial earth vein recently. This is really embarrassing." Fang Yuan smiled.

Lu Wei Yin quickly waved his hand: "Of course not, I feel admiration towards you instead. In the current world, only Lord Fang Yuan is capable of making use of these chaotic immortal materials."

Because Crazed Demon Cave had demonic sounds at set intervals, dao marks would become chaotic and all the immortal materials would be useless. Living beings would rampage and lose their senses, even rank eight Gu Immortals became lunatics in such an environment.

A while later, the first layer that was filled with vitality became a barren land.

The variant human Gu Immortals were still not satisfied as they brought the vast amount of resources back into the sovereign immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan and Lu Wei Yin went into the second layer after that.

Crazed Demon Cave's second layer was an incredibly hot land of burning rocks. A large amount of rocks were piled up together, big and small, the large ones were like huge elephants, the small ones were like pebbles.

These Gu materials also had chaotic dao marks, but they were mostly made of fire path and earth path dao marks.

"Take them all." Fang Yuan ordered, the variant human Gu Immortals moved again.

They swept the area like a locust swarm, emptying the entire second layer.

After that, Fang Yuan and Lu Wei Yin went into the third layer.

The third layer was covered in dense fog, it had a vast number of fog worms and cloud bamboos. These life forms were also senseless and chaotic, they were all taken down or chopped down and collected by the variant human Gu Immortals.

There was even a Fog City here.

A ghost city of dead people.

The Gu Immortals who died in Crazed Demon Cave gathered together with vengeance and created this Fog City.

When Fang Yuan came here before, he avoided it as he had rank seven cultivation level, if he entered it, he would definitely die, there was no way to escape.

But it was different now.

Fog City?

Mine.

Take it away!

After looting everything in his path, Fang Yuan arrived at the seventh layer of Crazed Demon Cave.

He spent much less time compared to his previous expedition.

Back then, Fang Yuan was led by Not Immortal, they kept taking detours. The deeper they went, the more turns they had to make, sometimes, the straight distance seemed to be short, but they had to make a long detour. With their strength back then, detours actually saved them more time than taking a straight path.

But now, Fang Yuan moved unhindered.

No matter what obstacles he met along the way, he placed them all into the sovereign immortal aperture.

The seventh layer of Crazed Demon Cave was filled with bright colors. The rocks, grass, soil, and trees were all shining in bright lights.

Every piece of soil or rock here was a quasi-rank nine immortal material.

But the dao marks were chaotic, they could not be used at all.

Of course, that was the case for most Gu Immortals in the world.

Chapter 2155: Paradise Earth's Sacred Tomb

Fang Yuan was the exception, of course.

As demonic sounds rang, Fang Yuan had already prepared himself. Back then, he was able to deal with the demonic sounds, now, it was simply too easy.

Under the demonic sounds' influence, dao marks of the same path in the seventh layer gathered together and formed large areas of beautiful rainbow lights, they were no longer as scattered and random as before.

"Such an incredible sight!" Lu Wei Yin sighed in amazement: "Eh..."

At the next moment, he saw Fang Yuan taking out Immortal Gu House Thieves Den.

Steal dao killer move activated!

Large numbers of dao marks were stolen, forming into corresponding rank nine immortal materials within Thieves Den.

These rank nine immortal materials were very pure, they only had one path's dao marks, they had immense value.

Lu Wei Yin watched, he became tongue-tied.

He estimated that in just over ten breaths of time, Fang Yuan obtained at least three rank nine immortal materials!

Rank nine immortal materials!

Wasn't he obtaining them simply too easily?

Fang Yuan and Lu Wei Yin moved together, everywhere they went, large areas of dao marks vanished.

The beautiful sight turned into something that resembled cheese gnawed by rats, everywhere Fang Yuan went, there were large pieces of black and white spots.

Lu Wei Yin watched, his eyes turned slightly red.

Fang Yuan's gains were too huge, the benefits were large enough for him to feel envy internally.

"Such wealth, he's earned a fortune! This is the first time I've seen anyone gain a vast number of rank nine immortal materials so easily!!" Lu Wei Yin shouted internally to himself.

He could no longer guess how many rank nine immortal materials Fang Yuan had obtained.

The only thing he was knew, his gains were huge, enormous, unthinkable.

Continuing to move forward, they finally arrived at the entrance of the eighth layer.

Fang Yuan's expression was slightly pale, the burden of using Thieves Den and the killer move steal dao along the way was not small, especially in terms of immortal essence expenditure.

Lu Wei Yin became slightly worried: "Lord Fang Yuan, do pay attention to your immortal essence storage."

"No need to worry." Fang Yuan smiled mildly: "I have rank eight Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus."

Lu Wei Yin heard this and his expression froze before replying: "Impressive, impressive, as befitting of Lord Fang Yuan."

At the entrance, Fang Yuan saw three paths ahead again.

One path was filled with golden light, luck surged around it. It was the luck path left behind by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

One path was dark and horrifying, killing intent filled it. It was the soul path left behind by Spectral Soul when he entered the eighth layer.

One path was humble and plain, giving a virtuous aura. It was Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's path.

Because Lu Wei Yin had methods prepared beforehand, he could enter Paradise Earth's path.

But Fang Yuan waved his hand, Thieves Den activated, the three paths were completely devoured, they disappeared.

A large number of rank nine immortal materials were produced as a result.

Lu Wei Yin moved his lips but he did not manage to say anything, he followed Fang Yuan into the eighth layer wordlessly.

Nothingness!

This was a boundless void that resembled a huge ocean with no shore in sight.

Fang Yuan and Lu Wei Yin who entered were like two bugs in the ocean, extremely minuscule and insignificant.

Fang Yuan had once come here, he had a deep impression of the place.

In this boundless void, countless worlds were created and destroyed, deriving brand new heaven path dao marks.

He had once tried to enter the ninth layer but he did not succeed.

This void was evidently the profundity of phantom path, but Fang Yuan did not have phantom path attainment back then, he could not deduce the location of the ninth layer's entrance.

This time, he came prepared.

His phantom path attainment level had reached grandmaster.

Immediately, Fang Yuan used his phantom path method.

"Hmm?" At the next moment, Fang Yuan raised his brows: "The void here is different from the one I experienced last time."

But Fang Yuan could not point out the exact difference.

Even though he made huge progress in phantom path, he was still very far from understanding or breaking Limitless Demon Venerable's eighth layer arrangements.

"Please follow me." Lu Wei Yin activated a certain killer move and found his direction, leading the way.

Fang Yuan followed after Lu Wei Yin.

Along the way, he saw worlds created and destroyed, it was truly an extraordinary sight.

But different from before, these worlds were moving along the void, no matter which world it was, they went in the same direction.

Fang Yuan's deductions finally had some results.

He was evidently moved: "I understand now, this void is contracting. At the final moment, all of the worlds and heaven path dao marks will be squeezed together, they will be completely fused into one. Is this Limitless Demon Venerable's plan?"

Lu Wei Yin shook his head: "I only know the location of Yellow Earth Great World, we need to hurry and head there."

The two immortals flew for a few more hours before finally seeing their destination.

"This is?!" Lu Wei Yin expressed shock on his face, because he did not just see Yellow Earth Great World, he also saw the worlds that Reckless Savage and Genesis Lotus left behind.

Fang Yuan squinted: "The three great worlds are fusing into one, not just that, there are also many small worlds following beside them."

These worlds were motionless within the void.

Each world was like a bubble, the three great worlds were the largest bubbles, being green, yellow, and red respectively. The three worlds were joint together at the center, the periphery was filled with smaller bubbles that were linked to the surface of the three great world bubbles.

"Oh no, lord, please look!" Lu Wei Yin pointed at the yellow bubble and said anxiously.

Fang Yuan turned his gaze and saw that Yellow Earth Great World was currently attacked by the joint efforts of the other two great worlds.

Even though the view outside the bubble was quite vague, Fang Yuan and Lu Wei Yin could still sense the intensity of the battle inside. Especially when the connecting area of the three worlds was filled with corpses, it was the most intense area of the battle.

"Lord, with my method, Yellow Earth Great World will not resist us. Let's go and reinforce them!" Lu Wei Yin charged in like a falling meteor.

Fang Yuan followed after him, his body was also shrouded in a yellow light.

It was this yellow light that allowed them to easily pass through the bubble and enter Yellow Earth Great World.

Looking at the great world, the thing that attracted Fang Yuan's gaze the most was that huge mound at the center.

This mound resembled a mountain, the mountain itself was quite flat, it looked man-made.

But Fang Yuan could see the true essence of the mountain at first glance: "This is Tomb Earth of the Ten Earths? This is such a huge tomb."

This unprecedented tomb had a tombstone on it.

The tombstone had six words written on it — Tomb of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable!

Seemingly sensing Lu Wei Yin and Fang Yuan, the tomb suddenly emitted a grand pillar of light.

It rose up into the skies, resembling a pillar that held up heaven itself, the entire battlefield froze, everyone's eyes were attracted to it.

"The Sacred Tomb is shining, heaven and earth can bear testament to it. Our sage has arrived!" After a few breaths of time, a huge roar erupted in Yellow Earth Great World, it was like a huge tsunami.

The people of Yellow Earth Great World became energized and surged with morale, they started to counterattack.

Green Lotus Great World.

This was the Dao field of Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, look at it, forests and vegetation were abundant, it was filled with greenery and vitality, giving off an unfathomable aura.

In this densely green world, there was a black and white mountain.

At the peak of the mountain, there were rows of chairs that extended downwards.

The top two chairs were unoccupied, while Qin Ding Ling sat at the fourth seat!

"Fang Yuan and Lu Wei Yin arrived after all!" After receiving the information, Qin Ding Ling snorted coldly.

During the pursuit battle against Fang Yuan, Lu Wei Yin took the initiative to help Fang Yuan, not only did he help to kill Spectral Soul, he even helped Fang Yuan escape.

Lu Wei Yin was Southern Border's Paradise Earth inheritor, after that, Paradise Earth's intention to cooperate with Fang Yuan became obvious.

The Paradise Earth Sacred Tomb at the center of Yellow Earth Great World was also openly seen to everyone, the Gu Immortals of the three worlds knew of it.

Thus, there was nothing strange about Lu Wei Yin and Fang Yuan showing up here.

Qin Ding Ling gritted her teeth as she said: "Currently, we need to split up into two groups, one group will advance and attack Yellow Earth Great World, the other will aid Demon Judgment Board in suppressing and resisting Savage Wilderness Great World as well as restraining Longevity Heaven. As for the other Gu Immortals, you can go conquer the small worlds in groups."

"Originally, our side was cooperating with Longevity Heaven to devour Yellow Earth Great World, but now that Fang Yuan and Lu Wei Yin showed up, Yellow Earth Great World is no longer meat on the chopping block, we can suffer losses if we are careless."

Saying so, Qin Ding Ling stood up and bowed to the Gu Immortal on the third seat: "Lady Ming Hao, please allow this subordinate to use Divine Emperor City and personally lead the group invading Yellow Earth Great World to resist Fang Yuan."

Qin Ding Ling was originally the leader of Heavenly Court, but here, she was only fourth place, she had to obey the three fairies at the top.

Currently, the first and second fairies were not around, only the third Fairy Ming Hao was here to control the situation.

This Fairy Ming Hao had the appearance of a three to four year old girl, she was cute and delicate, her large eyes shined with sparkling starlight specks.

She blinked her large and shiny eyes, she pondered before replying with a childish voice: "I've heard of Fang Yuan, but do you need to deal with him personally? Let them go instead."

Saying so, her tiny arm waved as a Gu worm flew out.

This information path Gu worm flew to the middle of the mountain and landed in front of two Gu Immortals.

These were neither human nor variant human Gu Immortals.

One was an old tree with a thin and dry trunk, it had countless branches of different length but had no leaves on them. It had thin and long roots that number to a hundred. The tree's name was Mu Cha Lang.

The other was a long bamboo that was green like jade, its name was Qing Hao Zi.

Qing Hao Zi floated in the air, casually and peacefully sleeping.

Mu Cha Lang was lying on the mountain rock that seemed like a chair, its branches wrapped around a small rock like a person resting his legs on a stool, it was very relaxed.

After seeing the information path Gu worm, Mu Cha Lang stood up immediately.

It extended its branches to nudge Qing Hao Zi: "Stop sleeping, stop sleeping, the sage has sent an order."

Qing Hao Zi waved back and forth because of the nudge but it did not land on the ground.

After getting awakened, it straightened its body and remained in the air: "To think that we are going to move out so quickly."

Next, the two immortals left the mountain, leading their troops to the front lines.

Chapter 2156: Heaven Extremity Gai Mei

Savage Wilderness Great World.

A grand and ancient dark gold palace floated in the sky.

It was Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

Within the palace, Bing Sai Chuan sat on a cushion with one information path Immortal Gu on the tiny table in front of him.

Several Gu Immortals were standing towards his left and right.

Bing Sai Chuan stared at the information path Immortal Gu, he frowned slightly.

Fang Yuan and Lu Wei Yin came together, it created a huge uncertainty in the battle of the three great worlds. What should Longevity Heaven, which occupied Savage Wilderness Great World, do?

Should they retreat first or send more people to probe Fang Yuan's strength?

Bing Sai Chuan could not decide immediately.

He thought for a while and cast his gaze towards the first person on his left.

A fatty was sitting there.

The fatty was lying down on the table, fast asleep, there was even saliva flowing out of his mouth, onto his sleeves and the table below.

Bam bam bam!

Bing Sai Chuan knocked on the table with his knuckle several times.

The fatty was woken up by this noise, he opened his sleepy eyes and asked in a daze: "What happened?"

Bing Sai Chuan withheld his anger: "Gai Mei, you are the Heaven Extremity, you cultivate wisdom path. The newest information is here, I want you to deduce what our following actions should be."

Saying this, the information path Immortal Gu flew and landed on the fatty's head.

The fatty did not use his hand to touch it, he looked into the Immortal Gu directly, his pupils shrank immediately.

"What? That demon Fang Yuan is here?" The fatty shrugged: "See, weren't my previous deductions correct?"

Bing Sai Chuan knocked on the table again: "I want you to deduce what action our side should take for this situation. Originally, Yellow Earth Great World was weak, with our control over Savage Wilderness Great World, and Heavenly Court's control over Green Lotus Great World, we could invade Yellow Earth Great World and strengthen ourselves before deciding the victor between us. But now that Lu Wei Yin and Fang Yuan appeared in Yellow Earth Great World, if we attack it by force, they might counterattack and expend our strength instead."

Bing Sai Chuan was not afraid of Fang Yuan's counterattack, he was worried about the impact on the overall situation instead.

After all, the current situation was more complex than before, the three worlds were resisting each other. If any two forces went ahead and fought too intensely, the third force would benefit.

"Then let me deduce it." The fatty Gu Immortal, Heaven Extremity Gai Mei, waved his loose sleeves and stretched out five fat fingers, he pretended to make a deduction.

"Oh, I deduced it, let's follow our original pan." Gai Mei said.

Bing Sai Chuan watched with a dumbfounded expression: "Can you use your Immortal Gu to activate a killer move and make a proper deduction?!"

Gai Mei blinked innocently: "What? How did you know I was pretending? You actually found out, you are so smart! You must be the wisdom path cultivator instead, right?"

Veins bulged on Bing Sai Chuan's forehead: "Do you think you are Southern Border's Wu Yong? You have no methods to conceal your aura, hurry up and make a deduction!"

Gai Mei waved his wide sleeves again, exposing his five fat fingers, he was about to make a deduction when he suddenly sighed: "Sigh! Forget it, the killer move is too tiring to activate. Why don't we just ask our lord ancestor instead?"

Bing Sai Chuan was livid with anger, he shouted: "Absolutely not! Our lord is working with Earth Extremity, Black Extremity, and Space Extremity to deduce Limitless Demon Venerable's plot, how can we disturb him?"

"Currently, Heavenly Court already has the initiative, they obtained Book Mountain. We are relying on our lord to have any hope of catching up to Heavenly Court. Heaven Extremity, can't you see the big picture?"

Gai Mei pouted unhappily: "Stop calling me Heaven Extremity all the time, I didn't even want to be Heaven Extremity, you guys forced it on me."

Yellow Extremity Jiao Huo who was sitting beside Gai Mei tried to convince him: "Brother Gai, just help out and make the deductions. This is not just about the strength of Yellow Earth Great World, it also concerns Fang Yuan's possible actions."

"This demon Fang Yuan has no regard for his identity as a human. I am more worried that he might relocate the local Gu Immortals of Yellow Earth Great World and the ones he captures from our forces into the sovereign immortal aperture. Look at what he did in the five regions, he recruited the variant humans to become his subordinates and almost rejected nobody. In my opinion, it is likely he would do this."

"In that case, it might foil our lord's plans."

Jiao Huo spoke, trying his best to convince Gai Mei, but he still shook his head, smiling instead: "Actually, you guys don't have to be so worried. Isn't Heavenly Court just as worried as us? Let's see what Heavenly Court is doing now, wouldn't that do? They are guarded by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, she is the number one wisdom path expert in history, she is definitely better than me at deductions."

Jiao Huo's expression froze: "Even so, if Heavenly Court deduces first, they will gain the initiative. If we join them in their plan, we will fall behind them."

"Regardless, I am not going to work!" Gai Mei rolled his eyes as he went back to sleep on the table.

Jiao Huo and Bing Sai Chuan stared at him angrily, but he completely ignored them.

"Charge, charge with me!"

"Force back all of these enemies."

"Charge—!"

Thousands of Gu Masters engaged in battle on the ground, the front lines looked disorderly, blood flowed everywhere.

The sky was the battlefield for Gu Immortals as they fought, more than ten Gu Immortals engaged in a chaotic battle at once.

On the ground, Yellow Earth Great World's Gu Master army launched a powerful counterattack, while in the sky, Yellow Earth Great World's Gu Immortals were suppressed.

Yellow Earth Great World's sage had already descended, the Gu Masters were spirited and motivated, but in the battle between Gu Immortals, morale alone could not make up for their difference in strength.

After all, Yellow Earth Great World had fewer Gu Immortals than Green Lotus Great World.

This could not be helped.

The three great worlds were made one after another, Savage Wilderness Great World had the longest history, but it had a lot of internal conflict over the years. Green Lotus Great World was second while Yellow Earth Great World was the most recent. After all, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable was the most recent venerable.

Yellow Earth Great World had very few Gu Immortals to begin with, it was even attacked by the joint force of two other worlds, they had fewer and fewer Gu Immortals gradually, the situation was dire.

"Our sages have arrived, there is still hope."

"I will defend Yellow Earth Great World, I will defend my homeland!"

The Gu Immortals of Yellow Earth Great World shouted together, raising their morale.

Green Lotus' side laughed coldly.

"Even if your sages arrive, they cannot stop us from killing you guys."

"You have sages but so do we. The result of this battle will not change!"

"We don't want to do this too, but we have orders from our sage, we need to kill all of you and devour all the worlds to prevent the apocalypse from happening."

The Green Lotus Gu Immortals continued to attack.

Yellow Earth's Gu Immortals were specialized in defense, even though the situation was dangerous, they were barely able to hold the line, struggling at the brink of defeat.

Right at this time, from the huge tunnel connecting Yellow Earth Great World and Green Lotus Great World, two armies appeared.

They were led by the Gu Immortals Qing Hao Zi and Mu Cha Lang.

Immortal killer move — Spring Upon Withered Tree!

Mu Cha Lang shouted as green leaves appeared all over its entire tree body, the new leaves flew out and landed on the Green Lotus Gu Immortals.

The Green Lotus Gu Immortals were not severely injured to begin with, their large injuries became small while their small injuries healed completely.

The condition of the Green Lotus Gu Immortals improved immediately!

Immortal killer move — Green Life Taker.

Qing Hao Zi flew with extreme speed, creating a green trail in the sky, piercing the body of a Yellow Earth Gu Immortal.

The Yellow Earth Great World's Gu Immortal was a black bear, it grabbed its empty chest.

After gasping, it fell to the ground.

The Yellow Earth Gu Immortals were anguished.

After dealing the fatal blow, Qing Hao Zi looked at these Gu Immortals arrogant and said: "The Sacred Mountain gave orders, you will all die."

Mu Cha Lang laughed loudly: "So what if your sage is here? The eventual victor will only be our Green Lotus Great World!"

At the same time, in another battlefield.

Savage Wilderness Great World's main forces were fighting against another group of Yellow Earth Great World inhabitants.

"Die! Die! Die!"

A six legged black tiger that was as large as a mountain charged around in the sky, it managed to grab a Yellow Earth Great World Gu Immortal.

"I finally caught you!" The six legged black tiger laughed and exerted force with both claws.

Swoosh!

With a soft sound, the giant-like Yellow Earth Gu Immortal was torn into two by the six legged black tiger, dying on the spot.

"Hahaha!" The six legged black tiger laughed loudly, the giant's blood spurted all over its face, the tiger licked and showed a maniacal and bloodthirsty expression.

"Little Rock Monarch was killed by Hei Liu Biao."

"Let's retreat, we are not these people's match."

"Indeed, our sage has already arrived, let's return and ask him to take charge of us."

The Gu Master armies were still fighting on the ground, but in the sky, Yellow Earth Great World's Gu Immortals had lost their fighting spirit, they wanted to retreat.

Suddenly, there was an eagle cry as white light flashed in the sky.

Everyone turned to look, they saw a snow wing eagle pecking a Yellow Earth Gu Immortal and devouring him whole.

"Xue Li Du!"

"He ate another person!!"

The Yellow Earth Gu Immortals were furious and shocked.

Snow wing eagle Xue Li Du said in a shrill voice: "Escape? Don't even think of running!"

The morale of the Yellow Earth Gu Immortals collapsed at once.

At Paradise Earth's Sacred Tomb.

"Kan Ke La greets both sages!"

"Big Rock Monarch greets both sages, we implore you, please save our Yellow Earth Great World!!"

A group of Gu Immortals knelt on the ground.

They were either beasts or plants. Some even had peculiar forms, some seemed like they had been formed from casually molded clay, some were like children's doodles, there were no pure humans.

These Yellow Earth Gu Immortals were all injured, some had severe injuries, on the brink of death.

But because of the commotion that Fang Yuan and Lu Wei Yin caused when they arrived, these sick and injured Gu Immortals came over.

Fang Yuan took a glance at them, seeing a 'familiar person'.

This was a giant grey fish, it resembled a goldfish but had the size of a whale.

When Fang Yuan first entered the eighth layer, he met with this fish and forcefully enslaved it, it was named Little Flower.

Right now, as Little Flower saw Fang Yuan, it was very excited and wanted to say something, but in this situation, it chose to control its emotions as the timing was inappropriate.

Fang Yuan nodded, saying: "I wanted to see the ones behind Green Lotus Dao field as well."

"Lord Fang Yuan, you cannot attack rashly." Lu Wei Yin suddenly transmitted.

Fang Yuan looked at Lu Wei Yin with a peculiar gaze, seemingly saying: 'Didn't you invite me here because of my battle strength?'

Chapter 2157: Rushing Forward Together

Lu Wei Yin secretly transmitted as he explained in detail: "Lord Fang Yuan, you may not know this, because of your high battle strength, it will trigger a retaliative method from Limitless Demon Venerable. After our obvious arrival, why did Heavenly Court send more troops to provoke us? It was to probe our strength and try to lure you into attacking, which would be the best outcome for them."

"What are the details about this?" Fang Yuan asked.

Lu Wei Yin smiled bitterly: "I'm not sure about the exact situation, but I know that Limitless Demon Venerable exerted huge effort to create Crazed Demon Cave back then, it was to make derivations regarding the Heavenly Dao, to find the true path of eternal life. At this point in time, the arrangement is finally about to reveal the result and bear fruit."

"The current eighth layer void is contracting and shrinking now, all the various worlds are lured to the center, fusing into or annexing each other, until only one great world is left in the end."

"And this great world might be the result of Limitless Demon Venerable's derivation, it might contain the answer to eternal life."

"If we attack abruptly and cause a huge commotion in battle, we may disrupt the eventual derivation of Crazed Demon Cave, Limitless Demon Venerable's method will immediately activate to deal with us."

"That will incur an unfavorable loss to our side."

"Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven will be happy to see that happen. If we end up suffering mutual losses with Limitless Demon Venerable's method, we will be less threatening to them while Limitless Demon Venerable's method will also be exposed, they will be able to discern information about it."

Fang Yuan pondered: "In that case, we can only make a move when the final great world is formed? Then why would Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven come here early to take charge of their respective great worlds?"

Lu Wei Yin explained patiently: "More precisely, only people with battle strength like yours cannot make a move. I am still able to take action here."

"If our side can control Yellow Earth Great World and emerge victorious, we will have the upper hand in the final battle. When the final great world is created, the amount of control we have over it will determine our gains. Thus, we need to invade more worlds and devour them to expand our territory."

After his transmission, Fang Yuan finally understood the situation.

Currently, he could not take action.

Once he took action and caused a big commotion, he would disrupt Crazed Demon Cave's final derivation, it would trigger the retaliative method of Limitless Demon Venerable.

Of course, Fang Yuan could suppress his strength to take action.

But there was no need to.

Suppressing his strength would mean that Fang Yuan was about as strong as other Gu Immortals, he might be slightly superior but that would not have an impact on the overall situation. In fact, after making many moves, Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven would gain information about his methods, he would even waste his luck in advance.

Thus, Lu Wei Yin invited Fang Yuan over mainly to deal with the final eventual battle.

Once the final world was formed, Fang Yuan, Star Constellation, and Longevity Heaven might have equal battle strength, they would fight it out for the final fruit in Crazed Demon Cave.

At that time, they would fight for real.

Before that, Lu Wei Yin could still make a move (he was pseudo venerable battle strength only in terms of defense) to try to make Yellow Earth Great World the victor of this war.

This would have significant impact on the final battle.

If Lu Wei Yin could succeed, Fang Yuan would gain the initiative later.

"Even if Yellow Earth Great World cannot win in this battle, we cannot let the other two worlds gain too much of a lead. As long as we defend the Sacred Tomb, during the final battle, Lord Paradise Earth will be able to revive successfully. By then, our battle strength will reign above the other two forces." Lu Wei Yin explained his meticulously crafted plan to Fang Yuan.

The conclusion was to defend now and counterattack later.

Defending their base initially while stirring conflict in secret, to make Savage Wilderness Great World and Green Lotus Great World fight each other and expend their strength, to make sure the three forces were eventually matched in the end.

At the later stage, after Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable revives, he would gain Fang Yuan's support and use their superior battle strength to gain victory over the others.

This was a logical arrangement to bide for time, it suited Lu Wei Yin's nature.

But...

This was not Fang Yuan's style.

Fang Yuan looked at the kneeling Yellow Earth Gu Immortals before turning to Lu Wei Yin, smiling: "Taking hits passively is not how I do things. Since we cannot use our top battle strength easily, it means that Heavenly Court is taking advantage of the fact that we lack subordinates."

"In that case..." Fang Yuan smiled as he looked towards Green Lotus Dao field: "Everyone, come outside."

Saying so, he opened his immortal aperture's entrance.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh.

A large number of Gu Immortals flew out.

"We pay respects to master!" Dozens of Gu Immortals greeted at once.

Their voices were thunderously loud, all of the Gu Immortals had evident excitement on their faces.

"The details are listed on the mission board, go." Fang Yuan waved his hand casually.

Swoosh swoosh!

These Gu Immortals immediately split into two groups, charging towards the two battlefields.

The kneeling Yellow Earth Gu Immortals were dumbfounded.

"How did so many Gu Immortals appear at once!"

"These people seem to be calling that handsome sage master."

"We are saved, Yellow Earth Great World is saved!"

After the Yellow Earth Gu Immortal reacted, they all relaxed and some even wept in joy.

Not just them, even Lu Wei Yin was shocked.

He had seen Fang Yuan dispatching variant human Gu Immortals all over Southern Border to collect mountains, he also knew that Fang Yuan led the variant human alliance, his force was not small.

But after seeing the main force that Fang Yuan sent out, Lu Wei Yin was filled with shock.

"So many Gu Immortals, they number to over fifty!"

"And from their aura, there are eighteen rank eight Gu Immortals, the rest are all rank seven Gu Immortals."

"How can there be so many rank eight Gu Immortals?"

"The rank seven Gu Immortals also have surging auras, they are close to the realm of rank eight already."

"No, there is no way Fang Yuan has zero rank six Gu Immortals, this means that these Gu Immortals are not his entire force?"

"That's right, Fang Yuan's clone Wu Shuai has not showed up either."

As Lu Wei Yin analyzed, the disbelief in his heart intensified.

He also felt worried.

"Did Fang Yuan spend all of his recent time nurturing these subordinates? According to his personality, he should not be this unwise..."

"Also, even though these Gu Immortals are high in number and have high cultivation level, who knows how high their actual battle strength is."

The ones that Lu Wei Yin was confident in were Xiao He Jian and Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch.

Front lines.

"Go and die!" Qing Hao Zi killed another Yellow Earth Gu Immortal.

But its injuries were not light either.

It had to temporarily stop its movement and go to Mu Cha Lang.

After Mu Cha Lang's healing killer move was used, Qing Hao Zi recovered greatly.

"This is all thanks to you, my old friend." Qing Hao Zi was overjoyed.

Mu Cha Lang said in admiration: "This is all I am skilled at, I feel admiration towards your ability to kill so many people. But don't be too rash and forget your defense, the final struggle of these Yellow Earth Gu Immortals will not be simple to heal if you get hit."

"Don't worry." Qing Hao Zi raised its bamboo tail: "I will try to kill four people."

"Hey, you guys should calm down, leave some for me to kill." Qing Hao Zi called out loudly as it entered the battlefield again.

Right at this time, a group of Gu Immortals flew over from the sky.

They were led by rank eight snowman Gu Immortal, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch.

He shouted: "We are the subordinates of Yellow Earth Sage, Gu Yue Fang Yuan, we are here to help and kill the Green Lotus Gu Immortals!"

The Gu Immortals were stunned.

The Yellow Earth Gu Immortals who were in deep peril saw hope, they became overjoyed.

The Green Lotus Gu Immortals started to feel their hearts pounding wildly.

It could not be helped.

Together with Mu Cha Lang and Qing Hao Zi, they only had eight people.

But there were over twenty Gu Immortal reinforcements!

Among them, there were nine rank eight Gu Immortals!

On Green Lotus' side, only Mu Cha Lang, Qing Hao Zi, and Old Forest Moss had rank eight cultivation level.

Weren't their reinforcements simply too large?!

Mu Cha Lang gritted its teeth, shouting: "Don't be scared by numbers, who knows what their actual battle strength is!"

The Green Lotus Gu Immortals regained their morale upon hearing this.

That's right, cultivation level was just part of the battle strength, only by fighting could their true strength be seen.

If they did not even dare to fight and retreated immediately, how would they face the sages on the Sacred Mountain?

The Green Lotus Gu Immortals disregarded the Yellow Earth Gu Immortals, they faced Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's group instead.

Immortal killer move — Snow Avalanche!

Immortal killer move — Crashing Rock Slide!

Immortal killer move — Great Earth Collapse!

Immortal killer move — Refine Life!

Immortal killer move — Multi-layered Five Poisons!

...

Bam Bam Bam Bam...

The Yellow Earth Gu Immortals who were disregarded opened their mouths in shock as they watched.

The moment they fought, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's group erupted with their full strength.

All sorts of killer moves were sent out like fireworks, the commotion was huge, resounding in heaven and earth.

Green Lotus' group also unleashed killer moves but the quantity was lower, their strength was also largely inferior.

Only after just one round, the Green Lotus Gu Immortals faced a terrible loss.

"Retreat, quickly retreat!" Old Forest Moss shouted.

"How can this be? The other side has so many rank eight Immortal Gu!" Qing Hao Zi shouted.

He had become a rank eight Gu Immortal long ago but he had never obtained a rank eight Immortal Gu, in this life, he had not even seen three rank eight Immortal Gu!

But Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch was quite unsatisfied, he scolded: "Don't launch a barrage like this, it is very wasteful, understand? The moves conflicted with each other, half of it was wasted, only thirty percent landed on the enemies! Find your individual targets and don't let them escape!"

Even though the first round had huge commotion, a lot of the moves' strength was wasted.

The outside world was not the sovereign immortal aperture after all.

Thus, the Green Lotus Gu Immortals managed to survive.

But the first round of combat gave them huge gains too.

The Green Lotus Gu Immortals were completely scared and lost their morale, they wanted to retreat now.

But Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's group had advantage in number, they dispersed and encircled the enemies.

Battle resumed.

The Green Lotus Gu Immortals were soon beaten up harshly, they were battered and bruised.

"These Gu Immortals have an absurdly perfect set of Immortal Gu!" Qing Hao Zi shouted.

"We can only focus on one aspect, but all of them have superb healing methods." Mu Cha Lang said bitterly.

"They have too many killer moves, they are all incredible methods!" Other Gu Immortals shouted.

Fang Yuan's refinement path attainment was number one in the world, Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven could only look at him in admiration.

After obtaining a vast number of immortal materials from the various grotto-heavens, compared to other forces, Fang Yuan had the highest number of Immortal Gu in the world.

Chapter 2158: Too Brutal!

Immortal Gu were unique, Immortal Gu were the most fundamental.

After sovereign immortal aperture's Gu Immortals obtained Immortal Gu, they were also able to easily exchange for corresponding killer moves.

Even though they lost some dao marks, these gains were simply too immense, completely negating the flaw of fewer dao marks.

A moment later, the Green Lotus Gu Immortals ran with all their strength.

Only three rank eights escaped, the rest were all killed by Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's group.

"Without a battlefield killer move, we cannot kill Gu Immortals efficiently." Bing Yuan sighed.

"Cannot kill efficiently?" The Yellow Earth Gu Immortals looked at the five corpses on the ground, their hearts beating wildly.

"Too timid, too timid!" Shi Zong sighed in pity: "They actually ran away, they are a disgrace to all rank eights!"

The Yellow Earth Gu Immortals looked at each other and transmitted secretly: "Even if I have rank eight cultivation level, I would have ran away in this situation too?"

"How can we face our master with just these results?" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch gritted his teeth, making a decision: "Chase, we will pursue and kill them!!"

The Yellow Earth Gu Immortal were shocked, they quickly urged: "Everyone, don't be too rash. There are still a number of Green Lotus rank eight Gu Immortals, they did not join the battle."

"Indeed, we barely managed to win this fight, we should go on the defense instead."

"Green Lotus Great World has many Immortal Gu Houses with terrifying strength, many Gu Immortals were killed on the spot because of their rampage."

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch was completely unmoved, he looked at the Yellow Earth Gu Immortals indifferently: "We are the subordinates of Sage Gu Yue Fang Yuan, we only obey his orders. You can all stay and clean up the battlefield."

Be it the Immortal Gu or immortal apertures of these fallen Gu Immortals, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's group did not take any.

That was Fang Yuan's order.

The Gu Immortals and Immortal Gu that belonged here were part of Limitless Demon Venerable's derivation results.

Killing these Gu Immortals would promote the fusion of the great worlds.

At the same time, in another battlefield.

Xiao He Jian and the rest arrived before Hei Liu Biao and Xue Li Du.

"So many reinforcements!"

"Wonderful, we're saved."

There were only two Yellow Earth Gu Immortals left.

"Be careful, these two are powerful rank eight experts from Savage Wilderness Great World, they are very strong!"

"They are specialized in..."

"Noisy!" Xiao He Jian took charge as the leader, he shouted and interrupted the advice of the Yellow Earth Gu Immortals.

This miniman Gu Immortal's eyes seemed to be glowing red, he pointed at the mountain-like six legged black tiger and shouted: "This guy belongs to me, I will fight anyone who contests with me!"

Roar—!

Hei Liu Biao was triggered: "Tiny little bug, you are going to die, I will kill you, no Gu Immortal had ever treated me with such an attitude!!"

Hei Liu Biao charged in a frenzy towards Xiao He Jian.

The Yellow Earth Gu Immortals were deeply scared and shocked.

"Numbers do not determine everything!" Xue Li Du also smiled coldly, charging into the Gu Immortal group.

Bam Bam Bam Bam....

An array of fireworks erupted, it was a beautiful sight.

Bam.

With a loud sound, Hei Liu Biao crashed onto the ground, creating a huge and deep crater.

It stared with wide eyes, struggling to get up.

Boom!

Xiao He Jian flew like a meteor, charging down.

Behind him were five to six rank eight Gu Immortals, they also attacked.

Bam bam bam bam!

The ground shook intensely, dust clouds rose, almost covering the rays of the sun.

With an intense wind that swept by, the dust clouds were dispersed.

The crater was even deeper now.

Hei Liu Biao was lying at the bottom of the crater, holding onto its last breath, its six tiger claws were twitching.

"I told you guys not to interfere!" Xiao He Jian shouted.

"On what basis?"

"Whoever kills it gets the contribution points!"

The other Gu Immortals shouted in retaliation.

Xiao He Jian rolled his eyes: "We all attacked, so who killed him? Who can be sure of it?"

"Easy, we can split up the contribution points. Whoever gets the largest part of the corpse will get the most points."

Nobody knew who was the one who suggested this.

But at the very next moment, the rank eight Gu Immortals flew down into the pit, splitting up the corpse of Hei Liu Biao.

"The leg is mine!"

"Hmph, I only got a tail! Give me back the butt."

"Head, this tiger head, hahaha, it is mine!"

The rank eight Gu Immortals shouted loudly, some were happy while others were dejected.

Those who did not get enough body parts directed their gaze towards snow wing eagle Xue Li Du.

But Xue Li Du had been killed already, it died even earlier than Hei Liu Biao.

The corpse was also completely split up between the Gu Immortals.

The Yellow Earth Gu Immortals watched in a daze.

Too brutal.

Too brutal!

Weren't these Gu Immortals the subordinates of the sage? Why were they so brutal?

Not only did they kill the Gu Immortal, they even dissected the corpse.

And they were so happy when dissecting the corpse?

Too brutal!

Too vicious!

Yellow Earth Great World was created by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, his ideal was to live in harmony and peace, emphasizing on unity and love. Even though Yellow Earth Great World had its own internal conflicts, the main trend had always been the same.

The action of Fang Yuan's subordinates was completely the opposite of Yellow Earth Great World, this was a huge contrast to the expectations of these Yellow Earth Gu Immortals.

"There are some Gu Immortals left." The rank eight Gu Immortals' eyes flashed.

But those rank seven Gu Immortals quickly shouted: "Before coming here, we already decided that the rank sevens belong to us. You rank eights already took the bulk of the gains, shouldn't you leave some to us?"

The rank eight Gu Immortals pouted: "Then hurry up, don't waste time! Otherwise, we will help you out and take a portion of the contribution points..."

"Wishful thinking!" The rank seven Gu Immortals quickly exerted effort and killed all of the Savage Wilderness Great World Gu Immortals in a moment's time.

"Hahaha, these Gu Immortals are so stupid, none of them ran away."

"Indeed, I was afraid that we lacked a battlefield killer move and could not stop them from escaping."

The Gu Immortals started to discuss heatedly.

The two Yellow Earth Gu Immortals looked at each other, they had peculiar expressions.

The Gu Immortals of Savage Wilderness Great World were combat maniacs, their ferocity was always the thing that made Yellow Earth Great World and Green Lotus Great World's Gu Immortals wary. Savage Wilderness Great World's Gu Immortals would rather fight to the death than retreat, they were courageous maniacs who did not care about their own lives when they were in combat.

But in the perspective of the sage's subordinates, they were stupid?

"How much did you snatch?"

"I only got this much."

"Heh, only? You earned a lot!"

"Hehe, it was all thanks to master who handed out such a lucrative mission."

The Gu Immortals collated their gains as they tossed away the corpses in their hands.

Fang Yuan had given specific instructions, be it immortal aperture, body, or Immortal Gu, they were all to be thrown away.

These subordinates did not dare to defy him.

Seeing the scattered corpses, the two Yellow Earth Gu Immortals' eyelids twitched.

If you were going to throw them away, why snatch them with such intensity earlier?

Was it just for fun?

What sort of monsters were these Gu Immortals!

The two Yellow Earth Gu Immortals who had just mustered up courage to express their gratitude instantly lost all motivation to do so.

They breathed in deeply and wanted to speak but suddenly, Xiao He Jian's group's expression changed.

"Master sent orders, we need to gather with the other group and attack Green Lotus Great World."

"Go, let's go! Don't let Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's group gain the initiative."

Swoosh swoosh.

The Gu Immortals left rapidly in a hurry, leaving the two Yellow Earth Gu Immortals who stayed behind with a dazed expression on their faces.

They looked at the Gu Master battlefield that was still fighting (Yellow Earth Gu Masters were already moving forward and pursuing the enemies), they felt completely lost for words.

For some reason, they started to feel pity for the Green Lotus Great World's Gu Immortals.

Fang Yuan watched from afar, capturing the scenes of the two battlefields with his eyes.

After those Gu Immortal corpses landed on the ground, they were quickly absorbed into the world. Immortal apertures disintegrated rapidly, the Gu worms inside faced the same end, there was no winds of assimilation produced, no traces were left at all.

Fang Yuan was not feeling calm internally.

"This is the profundity of refinement path!"

"Except that Limitless Demon Venerable is not refining Immortal Gu, he is refining the entire world."

"If I want to become venerable on the path of refinement, this is an aspect that I lack as well!"

In his later years, Limitless Demon Venerable wanted to break free from Fate and obtain the way to attain eternal life, but he could not find an answer from Heavenly Court of that time.

Thus, he created Crazed Demon Cave, he decided to use his own method and derive the method of eternal life.

After all, fate Gu was still around back then, completely intact.

The unified great world that was formed in the end might be the result of his plan, it might contain the method of eternal life. And now, the fighting and slaughter of these Gu cultivators became the fuel and sacrifice for this derivation.

After understanding this, Fang Yuan would not take the corpses of these Gu Immortals or their Immortal Gu.

This huge battle between worlds was definitely going to have countless dead Gu cultivators, be it mortal or immortal.

As for how many could survive in the end? Would there be thousands, or just one person?

Nobody knew.

But so what if that was the case?

Be it Fang Yuan, Lu Wei Yin, Heavenly Court, and Longevity Heaven, they did not care about that answer.

They had their own objectives.

The Gu Immortals born here obeyed the orders of their sages, they fought and killed, using their lives and wits to resist the others, they were necessary sacrifices that were determined from the start.

Fang Yuan casted his gaze towards Green Lotus Great World, he saw that his army had gathered and invaded Green Lotus Great World.

"If an outsider Gu Immortal died here, what would happen?" Fang Yuan had a calm gaze as he watched with anticipation.

These Gu Immortals were just his pawns after all!

When it was time to sacrifice them, Fang Yuan would not be stingy to do so.

"But I should prevent unnecessary deaths if possible." Thinking so, Fang Yuan said to Lu Wei Yin: "Friend Lu, I would like you to go and help out my subordinates. If the situation turns dangerous, your life is the highest priority, you can ignore the rest if necessary."

Lu Wei Yin nodded and he flew away.

Fang Yuan's subordinates were so ferocious, Lu Wei Yin was quite pleased and surprised.

At the same time, he agreed with Fang Yuan's plan.

They were already behind to begin with, having such a large force, they had to work hard and catch up to the rest, to make up for their difference!

Savage Wilderness Great World.

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

Bing Sai Chuan looked at the information path Immortal Gu on the table with a grim expression: "To think that Fang Yuan's force is so powerful, Hei Liu Biao and Xue Li Du are powerful rank eight experts in Savage Wilderness Great World, they actually died so easily."

"But now, Fang Yuan's two groups have gathered to attack Green Lotus Dao field."

Saying so, Bing Sai Chuan let out a breath of turbid air, feeling emotions of joy and gladness.

He was glad that he did not send reinforcements, because Heavenly Court sent more troops against Fang Yuan, he sent his army to find trouble with them.

Chapter 2159: Fairy Ming Hao

"That's why I said we should continue with our previous plan, my deduction was not wrong." Heaven Extremity Gai Mei drank wine and ate snacks while saying shamelessly.

Bing Sai Chuan could not be bothered to retort him, he looked at the rest: "Fang Yuan has such a huge force, it is very unexpected. If he attacks us, we will land in a passive spot. Even though Savage Wilderness Great World has the most Gu Immortals, most of them have their own intentions, they do not obey orders. If we could unify and rule them, we would have been the number one world long ago, suppressing Heavenly Court."

Heaven Extremity rolled his eyes: "Don't you know the reason? That Yellow Earth Great World was the arrangement of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable to begin with. Green Lotus Great World is also created by Heavenly Court's Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable. Meanwhile, Savage Wilderness Great World was made by Reckless Savage Demon Venerable but our lord obtained it, without a proper relationship, how can we convince them?"

Bing Sai Chuan could not help but tap on the table: "Forget about the reason, let's try to deal with the current problem. Do you guys have any good ideas to recruit those savage Gu Immortals?"

Green Lotus Great World.

Once in a while, an information path Gu worm flew over.

Qin Ding Ling was frowning deeper.

"Fang Yuan's subordinates are so ferocious, in just half a day, not only did they defeat our main troops, they even invaded and broke three of our defense lines!"

"We've already lost close to twenty Gu Immortals, the defeated rank eight Gu Immortals have suffered huge injuries, they came to the mountain to seek an audience with the sage."

"Oh?" The third seat Fairy Ming Hao showed an expression of curiosity: "As expected of Fang Yuan I guess. To think that he is skilled at nurturing subordinates too."

After pausing for a moment, Fairy Ming Hao asked in a child-like voice: "This means to say that Longevity Heaven also sent more troops out?"

"Yes." Qin Ding Ling nodded: "After sensing that Fang Yuan gathered his groups to attack us, Longevity Heaven immediately sent more people to stall Lady Yu Xiu's group, this might be the scene that Fang Yuan wants to see."

Fairy Ming Hao laughed heartily: "Since they want to attack us, let them come. Withdraw our defense lines, let them come and attack us."

"Yes." Qin Ding Ling immediately ordered and reorganized the troops without a hint of questioning.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian moved unhindered, they charged all the way until the center of Green Lotus Great World, below the Sacred Mountain.

Looking at the mountain, they saw that it had a peculiar appearance.

The entire mountain was black and white, all of the mountain rocks looked like they were drawn with black lines and filled with patches of white paper.

All of the life forms on the mountain were also altered.

They were all white paper people that were drawn with black lines.

A tiny white paper person flew down from the mountain, after leaving the area of the Sacred Mountain, she turned back into flesh and blood, looking like a cute and innocent young girl.

Xiao He Jian and Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch looked at each other, feeling that the situation was not simple.

The latter half of their trip was unhindered, that made them uneasy already.

And after reaching the enemy's headquarters, they only sent one rank eight Gu Immortal.

This was Heavenly Court!

No matter how weak they became, they had those rank eight Gu Immortals who escaped earlier at least right?

Why did they send a little girl?

Even though Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian had surging momentum, they were already feeling uneasy internally.

This army was mainly made up of people from the two heavens' grotto-heavens.

They had spent most of their lives hiding in the grotto-heaven, living a life of trepidation and fear, afraid that the five regions' humans would discover them.

If Fang Yuan did not have such demonic might that suppressed them, and also with the huge increase in their strength and confidence during these few fights, they would not dare to attack with such intensity in their previous state.

"What do we do now?"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian transmitted their thoughts, sending out one person to test the enemy's strength.

This Gu Immortal was Ke Xin Hong.

He cultivated poison path and was the strongest expert of the mushroomman Gu Immortals.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian did not choose their own members, they chose him instead.

After all, the mushroommen were the last group that joined Fang Yuan, they did not join the current major factions. Thus, as the seniors, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian worked together to target them.

And truthfully, many people were jealous of Ke Xin Hong recently.

He had the most envoy missions, he was almost the sole beneficiary of these missions that could gain huge rewards by just talking.

Many Gu Immortals were jealous.

Ke Xin Hong took in a deep breath, stepping forward and facing Fairy Ming Hao.

Brilliance shined in his eyes, he had soaring fighting spirit.

On one hand, after many envoy missions, he gained a lot of animosity from the rest, he needed to prove himself through combat. On the other hand, he wanted to use this chance to make a huge contribution, to make sure the mushroomman tribe was the number one faction in Fang Yuan's subordinate force, he would be able to protect his tribesmen in the future.

"Our mushroomman tribe joined master the latest, we are naturally ostracized by the senior members."

"Even though we want to establish a good relationship with Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian, it seems that master does not want to see that."

"Why did master give me envoy missions time and again, he might not have planned this from the start, but as time went on, his intentions became increasingly deep."

"Master has a total of two factions under him, they are the variant humans and the humans. There are fewer humans, forget about them now. There are far more variant humans instead, led by Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian, these two groups are getting larger and more influential, as time passes, they will definitely clash over benefits, because of their large influence, master will not be able to control them easily."

"Thus, from the start, master did not want us mushroommen to join them. The reason why master gave me envoy missions time and again is to help our mushroomman tribe gain power and sow discord between the variant human forces."

Ke Xin Hong sighed internally.

The longer he joined Fang Yuan, the more he felt Fang Yuan's unfathomably deep schemes, as well as his experienced political skills and methods.

Ke Xin Hong had already expected Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian to ostracize him in such situations.

He calmed his mind and collected all his scattered thoughts, he gathered his spirits and looked at the young girl, cupping his fists: "I am Ke Xin Hong, I would like to exchange pointers with you."

The young girl smiled: "I am Fairy Ming Hao, Ke Xin Hong, I know about you, is your poison path method used like this?"

Saying so, Ming Hao moved her tiny arm as poisonous fluid flew out.

Each lump of yellowish brown poisonous fluid flew into the air and turned into a goose.

Soon, an army of poisonous geese danced around in the sky, changing their formation constantly.

Ke Xin Hong was shook internally: "This is my uniquely created method, why can she use it?"

"Is she also a poison path Gu Immortal?"

"But why can she use my unique method?"

Ke Xin Hong stabilized his mind: "Fairy Ming Hao, that is an amazing method, but this move has a variation move, watch."

Saying so, Ke Xin Hong used the same poison path killer move.

After the geese were formed, they cried out as poison seeped out wherever their voices reached.

Ming Hao's eyes shined, she moved her poisonous geese to fight them as she observed carefully.

After a few breaths of time, she smiled and laughed: "So that's how it is, look, is this how the move works?"

Saying so, she activated Ke Xin Hong's variation move and caused her own geese group to cry out as well.

"What?!" This time, not only was Ke Xin Hong shocked, even the other subordinates were shook.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian thought to themselves: "This immortal is very strange, she can mimic other people's killer moves. But she only has rank eight cultivation level, our army is huge, how can we falter to one person?"

The two of them had similar thoughts, they immediately ordered and led the other immortals to get around Ming Hao and attack the Sacred Mountain behind her.

Fairy Ming Hao sighed: "Oh you guys, can't you play along? Why are you in such a rush?"

Saying so, her aura surged as she resonated with the Sacred Mountain behind her.

Next, the Sacred Mountain made of black lines and white paper shot out profound lights that had countless killer moves flying out of them.

Fang Yuan's subordinates were busy resisting the attacks.

Bam bam bam...

After an intense clash of killer moves, Fang Yuan's subordinates' attacks were all dealt with.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian showed expressions of shock.

"What killer move is this? It can actually mimic all of the killer moves that we used earlier?!"

"This mountain is not normal, it is not just a famous mountain, it is a secluded domain of heaven and earth!"

"Is this the legendary Book Mountain recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>?"

Fairy Ming Hao chuckled: "This killer move was casually created by me, it uses humility Gu as the core, it is called humble reciprocation. This move can use the information recorded on Book Mountain to deduce and unleash the killer moves that you use. Every killer move that you use is a present for me. Thank you very much."

"Is that really Book Mountain?"

"Humble reciprocation? That is clearly a human path killer move."

Fang Yuan's subordinates were shook internally, they attacked again.

But Fairy Ming Hao unleashed humble reciprocation killer move again, dealing with all of their offenses.

Fang Yuan had many subordinates but they were all stopped by one person.

"Master often told me that a lack of reciprocation is a lack of proper manners. After receiving so many gifts, I should return the favor. Take these." Fairy Ming Hao raised the intensity of her attacks.

The attacks came in waves, they were hard to block.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian had to use their full strength to defend and retreat.

At the crucial moment, a muddy yellowish light shot out and blocked most of the attacks, helping Fang Yuan's subordinates stabilize their footing.

It was Lu Wei Yin who had helped.

Fairy Ming Hao casted her gaze and smiled: "You are the current generation Paradise Earth's inheritor? You finally showed yourself?"

Lu Wei Yin frowned deeply, bowing at Fairy Ming Hao: "Greetings to Fairy Ming Hao, I wonder what is your relationship with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable?"

Fairy Ming Hao blinked cheekily: "Make a guess?"

Saying so, she stretched out her tiny finger and pointed at Lu Wei Yin.

Boom!

A five pointed starlight speck shot out with intense speed, once it was activated, it arrived before Lu Wei Yin.

Lu Wei Yin's expression did not change, he did not dodge either.

The starlight speck arrived before him and got blocked by a yellowish light wall, turning into nothingness.

Lu Wei Yin sensed something from this as he raised his brows, saying with peculiarity: "Carefree Wisdom Heart?"

Chapter 2160: Book Mountain

"You are quite perceptive." Fairy Ming Hao smiled.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

Around her, starlight specks continued to shoot out towards Lu Wei Yin.

Lu Wei Yin flew up against the attack and started to engage in battle.

Initially, he was able to fight evenly with Fairy Ming Hao. But soon, he started to get suppressed.

Fairy Ming Hao only used the flying stars to attack her enemy.

Initially, she shot out the flying stars one by one, but soon, they started to shoot out in groups of three, five, or even ten at once.

The power of her flying stars did not increase, but Lu Wei Yin faced increased pressure when they landed on him!

"These flying stars are very profound, this seems to be an endless consecutive move! I am going to face greater and greater pressure as time passes." Lu Wei Yin had a grim expression as he felt fatigue in defending himself.

Both sides only fought for some time, Lu Wei Yin had to retreat as he fought, Fairy Ming Hao had the complete advantage.

Each time she waved her hand, a large cloud of fragmented starlight specks flew out.

Each time the stars shot out, their quantity rose, they were already over a hundred in number.

Starlight shined as the stars moved in the air, the sound of air getting pierced was unceasing, it was a dazzling sight.

"This Ming Hao cultivates wisdom path and star path, she definitely has pseudo venerable battle strength. I should retreat for now!" Lu Wei Yin had intentions of retreating.

Fang Yuan also gave out orders to retreat at the appropriate time, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and the rest let out a sigh of relief as they quickly backed out.

Fairy Ming Hao smiled: "You all came here to seek death, why don't you stay here for good?"

Fairy Ming Hao attacked the immortals.

"Don't even think about it!" Lu Wei Yin blocked her.

Fairy Ming Hao chuckled, a mysterious light flashed in her eyes, shooting towards Lu Wei Yin's forehead.

Lu Wei Yin felt an indescribable change in his mind, he only had the capacity to store up half of his original thoughts.

At the same time, when his thoughts moved, they became much faster but each time, they would stop preemptively. It seemed like all of his remaining thoughts became 'rash', they collided impatiently, trying to deduce the results more quickly.

Lu Wei Yin fell into a predicament immediately.

When using killer moves, he needed to mobilize thoughts.

The more killer moves he used or the more complex they were, the more thoughts he would need to use.

But now that he had only half his thoughts left, he could not think as easily as before. More importantly, even when these thoughts collided, they would resolve in advance, he could not get the most useful result that he wanted.

This was quite fatal.

Once Lu Wei Yin's thoughts end preemptively when he activates a killer move, towards the end when he prepares his killer move, it would end up in failure.

With the killer move activation failing, Lu Wei Yin would suffer a heavy backlash himself.

"Such an incredible wisdom path method!!" Lu Wei Yin was helpless, he could only defend himself, he could not care about the rest.

Fairy Ming Hao grasped the absolute advantage, she immediately ordered the rank eight Gu Immortals of the Sacred Mountain to move out and chase after Fang Yuan's subordinates and kill them.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian retreated with huge losses.

Along the way, they lost nine Gu Immortals, among which three were rank eight Gu Immortals.

The immortal apertures of these Gu Immortals landed on the ground and got absorbed by Green Lotus Great World, their Immortal Gu were also quickly dissolved.

When the Gu Immortals died, their obsession was left behind but Fang Yuan did not see the birth of any land spirit or heavenly spirit.

After Fang Yuan's subordinates returned to Yellow Earth Great World, Fairy Ming Hao judged the situation and stopped her advances.

Lu Wei Yin led the immortals to meet Fang Yuan, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian quickly knelt down and sought for forgiveness.

But Fang Yuan consoled them amicably: "This loss is not your fault. I could tell clearly that this Fairy Ming Hao had outstanding strength, she possesses pseudo venerable battle strength. To think that this place could nurture an expert of such a level."

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and the rest were relieved, they started to calm down.

While retreating, they were all worried that Fang Yuan would be enraged and kill them all to vent his anger.

After that, Fang Yuan sent out these Gu Immortals to be stationed at all the various defense lines of Yellow Earth Great World. The emphasis of their defense was on the boundary and connection points of Yellow Earth Great World and the two other great worlds, Green Lotus Great World, and Savage Wilderness Great World.

"I am ashamed. To think that Heavenly Court actually has such a female immortal, she possesses an incredible combat system, I am not her match." Lu Wei Yin said with an expression of guilt.

Fang Yuan also consoled him.

Fang Yuan knew that Lu Wei Yin had already used his full strength at this point.

After all, in the previous fight, he had worked with Lu Wei Yin to fight against Spectral Soul and Heavenly Court, it was a near death situation, during that time, Lu Wei Yin had no way of concealing his strength if he wanted to live.

When fighting against Fairy Ming Hao, Lu Wei Yin had already used all of the methods that Fang Yuan knew he had. Yet, he was still not the enemy's match.

"Since this is war, there will be sacrifices. Maybe in the future, you and I might lose our lives too. This is the world of the Gu Immortals, we do not need to harp on it." Fang Yuan was quite satisfied with this result.

The conclusion was that Fang Yuan's losses were smaller than Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven. This was considered a victory.

Furthermore, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian even forced someone like Fairy Ming Hao to take action, Fang Yuan gained useful information about her.

Fang Yuan nurtured Gu Immortals for the purpose of sacrificing them to begin with.

If these cannon fodder could display their value, it would not be his loss.

"The biggest pity is that Lord Fang Yuan lost many Immortal Gu." Lu Wei Yin added: "But now, Northern Plains' Paradise Earth true inheritance is right before us, lord might have something to gain from it."

Lu Wei Yin was referring to Paradise Earth's Sacred Tomb.

Even without his explanation, when Fang Yuan sent him on this mission, he had already done his investigations.

"The tomb of Paradise Earth contains extraordinary profundity, I have not gotten any useful leads yet." Fang Yuan said frankly before asking: "Do you know anything?"

Lu Wei Yin smiled bitterly: "I am ashamed, I know nothing about it."

Fang Yuan nodded and said: "The wisdom path killer move that hit you earlier was the key that resulted in your loss, what do you think about it?"

This wisdom path killer move was too powerful, since it was exposed already, Fang Yuan wanted to create a counter for it.

Lu Wei Yin thought about it and said with uncertainty: 'It seems that the core Immortal Gu of that move is... pride Gu?"

Fang Yuan nodded again: "That is what I deduced as well."

Lu Wei Yin took in a deep breath of cold air: "Fairy Ming Hao is not a simple person. She possesses the Carefree Wisdom Heart Physique, she also has humility Gu and pride Gu, this reminds me of the description within \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>."

"According to what I know, there is no such person in the history of Heavenly Court, and she seems to have a deep connection with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable."

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, chapter five, section thirty-five states —

Ren Zu and Great Strength True Martial went through great hurdles and finally arrived before Qian Kun Crystal Wall.

Qian Kun Crystal Wall was straight and stood upright in the void, it was like a huge mirror that reflected everything that happened in the world.

Ren Zu and Great Strength True Martial went inside Qian Kun Crystal Wall.

Numerous flowers, birds, fish and insects converged into a colorful dazzling shadow that filled Great Strength True Martial's vision. The sound of the waves, thunder, and birds' singing in his ears rippled together, there was a fresh, sweet, exciting, spicy taste dancing on his tongue. At times, he felt like he was walking on a steep mountain path, at other times he felt like he was swimming in the waves, and at other times he felt as if he was falling from a great height.

"Father, father! Where are you?" Great Strength True Martial shouted.

But Ren Zu could not hear Great Strength True Martial, he could not see Great Strength True Martial, the color of white filled his vision, it was boundless and vast.

"Oh son, where are you?" Ren Zu sprinted, wanting to find Great Strength True Martial.

Ren Zu ran and ran and ran, after a long time, he saw a black dot at the furthest point within his vision.

Initially, he felt happy and thought it was Great Strength True Martial. But when he approached the black dot, he found that it was actually a huge mountain.

This mountain was very special, the mountain rocks and vegetation were made of white paper, the streams and waterfalls were made of black ink.

This was Book Mountain.

At the foot of Book Mountain, there was a village with many inkmen living in it.

Ren Zu went into the village, causing a huge commotion to arise.

"This is really a rare sight." The inkman spoke: "When ordinary lifeforms enter Qian Kun Crystal Wall, they would get lost after a few steps, they cannot resist the allure of the material world or the countless temptations within it, they can never reach here. You are the first person to arrive here."

Ren Zu was confused: "Why so?"

The inkman elder replied: "Oh human, you are only left with a skeleton, you cannot see, hear, taste, smell, or touch, it allowed you to roam Qian Kun Crystal Wall freely without losing your life."

Qian Kun Crystal Wall existed when the world was first created, it reflected everyone and everything, it contained all the secrets of the world's past and present. Once a person enters it, they would face the barrage of endless information, after some time, they would die from information overload.

After Ren Zu heard this, he felt very worried about Great Strength True Martial, he asked the inkman elder about the way to survive, the elder thus brought Ren Zu to ascend the mountain.

On Book Mountain, there was a largest ink waterfall, and below it was a deep pool.

The inkmen called this pool literature spring.

The ink waterfall continued to flow as it landed on the literature spring, water splashed about. These black color splashes flew in the air as the water droplets formed into ink texts.

"If a person wants to continue living in Qian Kun Crystal Wall, the ink text will be your best helper. The reason why we inkmen can live here is also because of the ink text." The inkman elder told Ren Zu about this big secret.

Ren Zu received the inkman's advice, he collected a lot of ink texts and left the mountain.

Every time he walked for some distance, he would leave behind some ink texts as reference points.

In this vast world of whiteness, the pitch black ink text became very conspicuous. Even though ink texts faded over time, using them, Ren Zu no longer walked on unnecessary trails, he eventually found Great Strength True Martial.

Great Strength True Martial received Ren Zu's ink texts, every step he walked, he would leave behind some ink texts.

The ink texts recorded the information that barraged Great Strength True Martial, turning them all into pieces of literary work. These literary pieces turned into pieces of tiles that were layered below Great Strength True Martial's feet.

Great Strength True Martial was finally free, his eyes were not blurry, his ears were not buzzing, he could no longer smell the mix of countless fragrances as well.

Stepping on these tiles, he followed Ren Zu back to the inkman village.

Ren Zu asked the inkman elder again: "Oh elder, how can I find wisdom Gu inside Qian Kun Crystal Wall?"

Chapter 2161: Carefree Wisdom Heart

The inkman elder told Ren Zu: "Even though wisdom Gu often stays within Qian Kun Crystal Wall, it is hidden very deeply. To find it, you will need to venture deep into the crystal wall, it will not be possible with just ink texts and the tiles that are formed below your feet. These tiles only record all sorts of information on the superficial level, with the endless barrage of other information the limited ink texts within the tiles will change in content, they will disappear quickly and cannot last for long."

The inkman elder said again: "Oh human, you need to turn all the information into knowledge. Only with knowledge can you explain information clearly, you will be able to write them down in words, allowing you to create a real path instead of just tiles made of texts."

Ren Zu was troubled: "How can I turn them into knowledge?"

The inkman elder laughed: "There are many bookworms on Book Mountain, they record the knowledge that our inkman seniors have left behind. Oh human, you can go look at them."

"It is not difficult to gather the knowledge yourself either. Firstly, you need memory Gu to store all of this information inside your mind. Next..."

Before the inkman finished his words, cognition Gu appeared, saying to Ren Zu: "After that, I can help you to refine knowledge."

The inkman elder nodded with a smile: "Indeed, cognition can produce knowledge."

Ren Zu: "Then I will thank you all in advance."

The inkman elder shook his head: "No need to stand on ceremony."

Cognition Gu: "Don't say that human. We have always been good friends, and this situation benefits myself as well."

If cognition did not take in new information, it would quickly get outdated. Only by receiving new information and thinking about it could cognition create useful new thoughts that were healthy and vibrant, innovative and lively.

Ren Zu gathered many bookworms on Book Mountain, he obtained a lot of new information.

Next, with cognition Gu's help, he created many new knowledge from the vast amount of information.

He used ink texts to write down his knowledge, scattering them on the ground and creating a black path made of ink texts.

Ren Zu and Great Strength True Martial walked on this path, they walked for a long time, far longer than any of their previous trips.

"Oh no, I don't have enough knowledge left." Ren Zu walked to the end of the path, feeling very dejected and upset. He had gathered many ink texts but the knowledge in his mind was insufficient already.

Ren Zu and Great Strength True Martial's first attempt failed, they had to return to Book Mountain.

Great Strength True Martial continued to collect ink texts while Ren Zu gathered all the bookworms, with cognition Gu's help, he refined even more knowledge from them.

With more and more knowledge, Ren Zu found that his mind was getting filled up.

"I have too much knowledge now." Ren Zu was very satisfied, he said confidently: "Let's go, I am sure we can reach the deepest part of Qian Kun Crystal Wall this time!"

However, they still failed in their second attempt.

"Why did this happen? My mind was already filled with knowledge." Ren Zu said dejected: "This is all the knowledge I can hold."

"No, oh human, look closely again." Self Gu suddenly spoke to remind him.

Ren Zu inspected his mind, he found a Gu hiding inside it.

Ren Zu realized at once: "So you are occupying my mind, preventing me from getting more knowledge. What Gu are you?"

The Gu answered: "I am pride Gu."

Ren Zu said anxiously: "Can you hurry and get out, you are occupying such a huge area, I want to fill the place with knowledge instead."

But no matter how anxious Ren Zu was, or how he urged, pride Gu refused to leave.

When Ren Zu was out of ideas, Great Strength True Martial spoke: "Oh father, don't be anxious. Don't forget that I still have humility Gu. I will give it to you."

Great Strength True Martial took out humility Gu and gave it to Ren Zu.

Pride Gu was chased away by humility Gu, it had to fly out of Ren Zu's mind and land on Great Strength True Martial instead.

Strong Gu was very happy: "The strong have their own pride!"

After Ren Zu chased pride Gu away from his mind, he returned to Book Mountain to continue gaining knowledge.

After Ren Zu gained humility Gu, he realized that the more knowledge he had, the more he found that he was lacking knowledge, and the more he wanted to fill his mind with even more knowledge.

Ren Zu's mind was quickly filled.

Self Gu urged him: "Oh human, stop now, your mind is already full of knowledge."

But Ren Zu replied: "But I think that it is insufficient, I am certain that I still do not know a lot of things, I need to continue gaining knowledge."

Ren Zu continued to refine his knowledge, his mind was getting bloated, it was hurting and could not hold anymore information, but humility Gu made him feel like he was still lacking in knowledge.

Suddenly, there was a loud boom.

Eventually, Ren Zu's mind could not take it anymore, it exploded from an overload of knowledge.

The knowledge scattered on the ground as a little girl stood up from within.

"Father, father." The little girl hugged Ren Zu's leg happily: "My name is Carefree Wisdom Heart, I am your daughter."

...

Northern Plains.

Sincerity grassland.

Chen Cheng was dressed in green, his arms were crossed behind his back as he stood arrogantly upright.

He stared at the foreign female immortal before him as he shouted: "Who are you? Why did you request to meet me here?"

The female immortal standing before him wore a half-mask covered her nose, mouth and cheeks, only revealing the upper half of her face which showed her strong contours, sharp and long brows, bright eyes and a heroic aura.

She wore a dark gold armor that covered her whole body, bringing a heavy feeling of suppression on any that looked at it, she was definitely not an ordinary person.

"You can address me as Fairy Black Moon." This female immortal said.

"Fairy Black Moon?" Chen Cheng raised his brows: "Where are you from?"

Now that the five regions were merged, Gu Immortals no longer had region specific auras, that was why Chen Cheng asked the question.

Fairy Black Moon smiled lightly: "My identity and origin are not important. Chen Cheng, you are called the Sincerity Immortal, you cultivate rule path. Back then, you had an agreement with your friend, the loser in the battle would recognize the winner as their owner and assist them. Do you remember this?"

Chen Cheng's pupils shrank as he frowned: "I was young and arrogant then, I did not know what that truly meant, that was why the agreement was made. I was still a mere Gu Master back then, who are you exactly? You know such an obscure secret!"

Fairy Black Moon smiled coldly: "I'm only asking you, Chen Cheng, is this agreement still effective?"

Saying so, she took out a token.

Chen Cheng received it as his expression changed again: "This token is real, where did you get it? What relationship do you have with my friend?"

Fairy Black Moon said again: "I said these are not important."

Chen Cheng took a deep breath, he said with a solemn expression: "I understand now, you want us to have a fight, if you win, you will make me your servant! Since you took the initiative to find me, I am sure you are confident in your own strength. But I need to remind you, even though I am a lone cultivator, after roaming Northern Plains for so many years, I have gathered many trump cards. If you win this battle, I will acknowledge you as my master. But if you lose, I will be your master!"

Fairy Black Moon laughed heartily: "Everyone calls you the Sincerity Immortal, someone who keeps his words and promises. After meeting you, it seems that this is true after all. Let's fight!"

Chen Cheng was furious: "Regardless of who you are, today, I will see what you are capable of!"

At the next moment, thunder rumbled as the battle of two immortals ensued.

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

He Chun Qiu was taking charge of Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool.

Splash splash splash.

The water of time moved erratically, creating the mesmerizing sound of waves.

A rank eight Immortal Gu was quickly forming, landing in He Chun Qiu's hands.

"Good, all of the destroyed rank eight Immortal Gu have been refined successfully." He Chun Qiu nodded, feeling satisfied about the progress.

Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool had the ability of Regret Pool, any Immortal Gu that it refined would have an insignia left behind. When the Immortal Gu is destroyed, Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool would use the power of the tributary of the River of Time together with the insignia to refine the Immortal Gu again, the success rate would be higher than refining a new rank eight Immortal Gu normally!

When Fairy Ming Hao forced Fang Yuan's subordinates to retreat earlier, Lu Wei Yin expressed his pity over the destroyed Immortal Gu.

But he did not know that Fang Yuan's refinement path methods were unimaginably powerful, in just a few days, he refined all three rank eight Immortal Gu that were destroyed in that battle.

But Fang Yuan was still not satisfied with his current refinement path attainment.

Several days had passed since Ming Hao defeated Lu Wei Yin and the rest.

These days, the three worlds were quiet and safe, battle had stopped, there was temporary peace.

Since it was not time for the actual fight yet, Fang Yuan used this time to comprehend the profundity of the place.

He had already investigated Paradise Earth's tomb, there were countless dao marks distributed in it, the structure was complex and profound, the scale was immense, he could not unravel it in a short time.

Fang Yuan spent most of his energy on the countless big and small worlds here, trying to comprehend the refinement path profundity that they contained.

"Sage, Savage Wilderness Great World's envoy seeks your audience." At this time, a Yellow Earth Gu Immortal reported respectfully.

"It's Bing Sai Chuan." Lu Wei Yin came over as well, bringing accurate information with him.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly: "It is about time they came here."

Earlier, the loss of Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian was actually part of Fang Yuan's scheme.

Even though Heavenly Court lost to him before, Fang Yuan had never underestimated their foundation.

Heavenly Court placed a huge focus on Crazed Demon Cave, they even brought Divine Emperor City over, how could Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian defeat Heavenly Court?

With the current situation, even though Longevity Heaven, Heavenly Court, and Fang Yuan had one of the three great worlds each, Heavenly Court was still the dominant party.

The three sides were contesting but there was still the strongest and weakest side among them.

Together with Bing Sai Chuan taking the initiative to cooperate with Fang Yuan during the fate war, after Lu Wei Yin and the rest returned in defeat, Fang Yuan waited patiently for Bing Sai Chuan's envoy to come.

It was just that Bing Sai Chuan, one of the Four Desolation Immortals, actually came here personally.

It showed Longevity Heaven's sincerity right away.

"Friend Fang Yuan, have you been well?" Bing Sai Chuan smiled.

But Fang Yuan's expression was cold: "I am working together with Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable to help him revive. Bing Sai Chuan, it is really unwise that your Longevity Heaven wants to cooperate with us. After all, when the time is ripe and Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable revives, our strength will rise sharply, we can even suppress Heavenly Court."

"This..." Bing Sai Chuan's expression froze immediately.

Chapter 2162: Cooperating Once Again

The purpose of Bing Sai Chuan's visit was obvious, he wanted to work with Fang Yuan and resist Heavenly Court.

Fang Yuan did not want to waste time, he directly stated the obstruction towards their cooperation instead.

Paradise Earth's tomb was huge as a mountain, Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court knew about it long ago.

The reason why they attacked Yellow Earth Great World earlier was also because of this.

Bing Sai Chuan was a rank eight expert renowned in history after all, he laughed, the stiffness on his face vanished at once: "Fang Yuan, do you know where this Book Mountain originates from?"

Fang Yuan had a thought: "Book Mountain is not originally an arrangement of Heavenly Court?"

Bing Sai Chuan nodded: "Indeed, that is so. Book Mountain was originally in the ninth layer of Crazed Demon Cave, but because of Heavenly Court's immense foundation in wisdom path, they comprehended a portion of the profundity and took out Book Mountain from the ninth layer in advance."

"Oh?" Fang Yuan did not acknowledge nor reject the answer.

But Lu Wei Yin's expression changed.

This was something that the Gu Immortals of Yellow Earth Great World did not know of.

After all, it happened deep within Green Lotus Great World.

"Heavenly Court has such a method? They have already started comprehending the ninth layer and even managed to bring out Book Mountain? Did Limitless Demon Venerable's retaliative method not activate?"

Bing Sai Chuan sighed deeply: "If it worked, we would not have come here so urgently to seek an alliance."

Fang Yuan replied in a solemn tone: "Did you see Star Constellation Immortal Venerable?"

Bing Sai Chuan shook his head: "Not even once."

Fang Yuan asked again: "Then what is the relationship between Fairy Ming Hao and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable?"

Bing Sai Chuan replied honestly: "Since the arrangement of Limitless Demon Venerable exists, until the right opportunity arises, we will not use our full strength, thus, we did not force Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to show herself. But Heavenly Court had three female immortals that appeared, they all possess pseudo venerable battle strength, Fairy Ming Hao is one of them."

"These three female immortals are Ming Hao, Yu Xiu, and Feng Ya respectively, they cultivate wisdom path with star path secondarily. Your side has already seen Fairy Ming Hao's strength, Fairy Yu Xiu is stronger than her, days ago when we fought, our side had to send reinforcements to stall them and form a stalemate."

"As for Fairy Feng Ya, she seems to be even stronger but she has never taken action, she has been secluded in Crazed Demon Cave to comprehend the ninth layer profundity. Book Mountain is the fruit of her labor."

Lu Wei Yin could not help but sigh: "Heavenly Court is the number one force in the world after all, their foundation is unfathomably deep. After Duke Long died, they lacked pseudo venerable battle strength, but to think that three of them were hidden in Crazed Demon Cave! This shows the importance Heavenly Court is placing on Crazed Demon Cave."

Bing Sai Chuan added: "Other than these three pseudo venerables, there are also rank eight elites like Qin Ding Ling. In addition, regarding the forces they have out in the open, there are Divine Emperor City, Demon Judgment Board, and Heaven Overseeing Tower. With Heavenly Court's foundation, it will not be strange for them to bring out more Immortal Gu Houses."

Lu Wei Yin gritted his teeth: "Heavenly Court even transferred a portion of the immortal graveyard into Crazed Demon Cave, this immortal graveyard was created here by using the Tomb Earth they collected. At the crucial moment, the immortal graveyard's slumbering experts in history would awaken, they have terrifying strength too."

"Precisely so." Bing Sai Chuan concluded: "Fang Yuan and Lu Wei Yin, both our sides need to cooperate. Otherwise, how can we force Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to show up? How can we defeat three pseudo venerables? How can we ensure the revival of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable?"

Bing Sai Chuan's intention was obvious.

Heavenly Court's advantage was too great, if they were not stopped in time, even before Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable revives, Heavenly Court would have won already!

Thus, there was a need for them to work together.

Lu Wei Yin looked at Fang Yuan, who nodded slightly, agreeing to this cooperation.

Longevity Heaven seemed to have no fear regarding Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's revival, they were very confident in themselves, their trump cards were definitely not few. But currently, with Heavenly Court in the lead, they had to do something to slow them down.

Savage Wilderness Great World and Yellow Earth Great World stopped fighting between themselves, they sent out troops to attack Green Lotus Great World together.

Even though there was cooperation with Longevity Heaven, the extent was quite limited.

Fang Yuan suggested that they should exchange true inheritances. He wanted to use venerable true inheritances of equal value to exchange for Longevity Heaven's luck path true inheritance of Giant Sun.

Bing Sai Chuan rejected him with a polite tone but his attitude was firm.

Fang Yuan also suggested that they should exchange immortal materials. He wanted rank nine luck path immortal materials but Bing Sai Chuan rejected him as well.

Fang Yuan's force had already inflated to this level, when he sent out his subordinates earlier, even Bing Sai Chuan was completely stunned from their collective strength.

Bing Sai Chuan and the rest had a strong opinion against Spectral Soul and Red Lotus! To help Fang Yuan destroy fate Gu, they had truly given him too much help.

In just these few days, Fang Yuan's force had already grown to this terrifying level!

And what about his own strength?

How much had he grown until now?

In this situation, how could Longevity Heaven make a transaction with Fang Yuan? Wouldn't that be helping his growth?!

Due to the cooperation of Fang Yuan and Longevity Heaven, the situation changed greatly.

But Heavenly Court seemed to have predicted this, even though the two sides attacked with their full strength, they were still defending themselves firmly.

At times, when the defensive lines were about to break, Fairy Ming Hao and Yu Xiu would take action personally, either maintaining Heavenly Court's position by forcing enemy Gu Immortals to retreat, or using the battle opportunity to invade Savage Wilderness Great World and Yellow Earth Great World instead, causing huge destruction and countless deaths.

Fang Yuan also saw Fairy Yu Xiu's strength for the first time.

Fairy Yu Xiu had an exceptional combat system. Her attacking methods were very special, they relied on the difference between the two sides' attainment level. The bigger the difference, the stronger the attacks.

Ever since the first time they reached the base of Book Mountain, Fang Yuan's subordinates made no such advancement again.

Like this, the three sides fought with each other, the situation was in a deadlock, days went by one by one.

A large number of Gu cultivators died, their sacrifice made the three worlds grow larger with an increasing number of stable dao marks. The more Gu cultivators died in this place, the more the boundaries of the three great worlds faded, and the larger the area which the worlds were connected to became.

On this day, at the peak of Book Mountain.

Fairy Yu Xiu gathered the Heavenly Court immortals, she spoke: "Right now, Fang Yuan and Longevity Heaven have cooperated, this is giving us huge pressure. Our immortal graveyard has a backup hidden force but Fang Yuan's Wu Shuai clone has not shown up yet, Longevity Heaven is also hiding their strength."

"Since the situation is now in a deadlock with all three sides wary of each other, the small worlds around the three great worlds will be the key to our victory."

"These small worlds might be weak but they still have Gu Immortals. If we can get them to join us, we will gain an advantage in the fight between the three forces."

During this time, Fang Yuan and Longevity Heaven cooperated, managing to suppress Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court was losing more and more members.

Zhou Xiong Xin sighed: "These small worlds are easy to defend but hard to attack, even though we tried many times and are able to win by force, very few Gu Immortals decided to join us sincerely."

Prince Feng Xian added: "These Gu Immortal inhabitants lack sufficient intelligence, they are very stubborn as well, most of them bear animosity towards the three great worlds. They think that fusing their world into the great worlds would cause the destruction of their homeland, they hold a firm attitude."

"Thus," Fairy Yu Xiu smiled: "I will hold a lesson at the peak of Book Mountain to teach the countless masses. Any Gu cultivator, mortal or immortal, can join this session."

"How will you do that?" Wan Zi Hong asked.

Fairy Yu Xiu explained the details, Heavenly Court's immortals had changes of expressions.

"Lady Yu Xiu has such an incredible method? We are truly in admiration!"

"In that case, we will not have to worry about these Gu cultivators not joining us sincerely."

"These lowly Gu cultivators actually have such a great fortune to be able to get a Dao lesson from Lady Yu Xiu, this is too good for them."

"Haha, they are all just cannon fodder, they will be sacrificed in the end, there is no harm in doing this."

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals discussed among themselves, the atmosphere slowly became relaxed.

Divine Emperor City.

Qi howling painting world.

A group of beggars stood around Fang Di Chang, facing a huge elephant.

The huge elephant was pure white in color, its four legs stomped on the ground, it was unmoving like a sturdy mountain.

The beggars were in a stalemate for a long time, their morale was falling, they started to feel like they could not resist this huge elephant.

Fang Di Chang was frowning deeply: "This qi monster is made from righteous qi, the longer we fight it, the more disadvantageous it is for us."

Qi monsters had all sorts of shapes and sizes they were not fixed, they could be made from all kinds of qi, having varying temperament and strength.

For example, qi monsters made of domination qi would be domineering, qi monsters made from death qi would love to be in places filled with many deaths. Qi monsters made of life qi would have strong recovery abilities, while qi monsters made from luck qi would be hard to kill, once they were killed, the benefits to the Gu cultivator would not be small.

Even though Fang Di Chang was Fang Yuan's clone and shared his attainment level, he had lost his body and soul. With just his will left, he resided within the human path beggar Gu.

Thus, he could not resist this white elephant made of righteous qi.

But thankfully, the righteous qi white elephant was not rampaging, it did not make a move in the end, only staring at the beggars.

"I have arrived!" Shen Shang finally fought his way to them.

After finishing off his earlier opponent quickly, he came to help out Fang Di Chang.

He fought against a group of blood qi monsters earlier, he was bathed in blood.

Fang Di Chang immediately sighed in relief as he made the beggars fall back and let Shen Shang in.

Shen Shang fought against the white elephant using human path methods.

This rank eight Gu Immortal was indeed the human path quasi-supreme grandmaster chosen by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, he quickly gained the upper hand.

But right when he was about to finish off the elephant, the ground started to shake.

Rumble...

About ten thousand bull shaped qi monsters stampeded together while creating huge dust clouds behind them.

Shen Shang and Fang Di Chang's expressions changed.

The righteous qi elephant screeched in fear as it escaped in panic.

Shen Shang did not bother with it, he grabbed Fang Di Chang and quickly ran in another direction.

The stampede of countless bulls was like a tsunami that swept heaven and earth, it could not be stopped.

Shen Shang and Fang Di Chang managed to escape with their lives, they watched as the bulls charged away.

"These qi monsters are made of charging bull qi, but isn't the size of the group too big, who can block it?" Shen Shang sighed.

Fang Di Chang replied: "The bulls are running towards the closest camp. Who knows how many will die, but that camp is going to end up in ruins."

Shen Shang nodded: "Indeed, once the camp is destroyed, we can only retreat to another camp further back. Our exploration will get tougher."

Chapter 2163: Endless Learning

The two of them had deduced something earlier, thus they worked together and explored deeper into qi howling painting world, in order to find and communicate with Heavenly Court's enemy at the depths of the painting.

The enemy of an enemy was a friend.

But even after Shen Shang and Fang Di Chang did their best, they could not reach the deepest part of the painting.

Qi howling painting world was too huge, Fang Di Chang's strength was at a limit, even though Shen Shang had rank eight cultivation level, it was severely restricted in here, the difference between mortal and immortal was not evident.

The only good thing was that Shen Shang's illness was greatly alleviated here. Ever since he entered the painting world, he had not relapsed again.

According to Shen Shang's estimations, the dense human path environment here was helping him.

"Sigh, the ten children of human path have left. Without their help, how can we get through this painting and meet the one suppressed at the deepest part of the painting?" Fang Di Chang sighed.

Shen Shang was about to speak when his expression changed suddenly, he shouted: "This is?!"

Next, Fang Di Chang also sensed the aura of a rank eight Immortal Gu rapidly spreading towards him.

The two no longer cared about qi howling painting world, they quickly returned to the central area of the original painting world.

The two of them saw a rank eight Immortal Gu at the same time, it was floated in the air, shining with radiance.

"Divine Emperor City is truly deep, it actually contains this legendary Immortal Gu!"

"If I am not wrong, this should be the learning Gu recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>!!"

The two conversed, seeing the shock on each other's expressions.

"Learning Gu is a human path Immortal Gu, this is likely the highest ranked human path Immortal Gu in the current world." Fang Di Chang sighed.

"I get it now!" Shen Shang's eyes suddenly shined with bright light: "Why did beast tamers and qi cultivators appear earlier? It was the result of this learning Gu's effect. Of course, this should not be the only Gu used, it is likely a killer move. Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable had such grand ambitions, his arrangements were truly deep."

Fang Di Chang frowned: "But why did this learning Gu activate on its own now? Did something happen in the outside world?"

Shen Shang was troubled, he did not know about the situation outside.

But he quickly reacted: "This is a prime opportunity! Learning Gu must be one of the cores of Divine Emperor City, regardless of what is going on outside that caused this core to be used alone, at this point, Divine Emperor City's intact structure has a crack in it, we can find this weakness and make use of it!"

"Good idea!" Fang Di Chang's pupils expanded as he looked at Shen Shang excitedly: "Let us work together and explore the secret of Divine Emperor City."

At the same time.

Crazed Demon Cave.

Eighth layer.

Green Lotus Dao field, above Book Mountain.

Fairy Yu Xiu sat at the peak of Book Mountain, within her immortal aperture, Divine Emperor City's learning Gu spread out its radiance, cooperating with Fairy Yu Xiu's other Immortal Gu to form a human path killer move —

Endless Learning!

At the middle and bottom of Book Mountain, there were countless Gu cultivators.

The killer move's radiance was light blue in color, it spread down and covered all of these Gu cultivators.

Their bodies shook intensely.

"This is?!"

The immortals' expressions changed, they were filled with deep shock.

An indescribable profundity of the Great Dao flowed into the depths of their hearts like a gentle river.

The attainment levels of these immortals started to rise!

"There is actually such an incredible killer move in this world, if I am not experiencing this personally, I will not be able to imagine it!"

"This is the teaching of the sage, the sage is merciful and benevolent!"

Many Gu Immortals were so touched they shed tears on the spot, others knelt down on the ground, kowtowing to Fairy Yu Xiu at the peak of the mountain.

These were all non-standard Gu Immortals, but they were receiving the most traditional Gu cultivation method now.

They were all clear about how hard it was to raise attainment levels!

This was truly an unprecedented fortuitous encounter for them!

"In this world, there are indeed other methods to raise attainment level other than dream realms. Human path... Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable had already made his arrangements to this degree. It is definitely not wrong for Heavenly Court to develop human path!" Qin Ding Ling was very excited internally.

Heavenly Court's members, with her at the lead, sat down together and closed their eyes to comprehend calmly.

Fairy Yu Xiu opened her eyes slightly, looking down below her with a glance.

Sweat had gathered on her forehead, all the thoughts in her mind were used to sustain this move.

Endless learning was a human path method of strategical value, its benefit for any super force was huge beyond imagination.

Its greatest advantage was that it did not expend the user's true meaning, it created true meaning in the mind of the targets instead!

Rule path and wisdom path Gu Immortals were more adept at extracting their own true meaning compared to other paths.

When other Gu cultivators take the true meaning, their attainment levels of the corresponding path would rise sharply.

But the Gu cultivator who extracted their true meaning would experience a fall in attainment level, the losses could not be regained.

This was why true meaning was so rare in the world.

Endless learning was a killer move that made use of Fairy Yu Xiu's attainment level, the secluded domain of heaven and earth Book Mountain, as well as learning Gu.

This move could create new true meaning in the mind of the targets.

Once the true meaning was created, it would be instantly absorbed by the Gu cultivator and cause their relevant attainment level to rise.

This was the greatest advantage of the killer move endless learning, it did not consume anyone's attainment level.

But at the same time, this advantage was also its weakness.

Because the true meaning created by the killer move had limitations.

The limitations were the Gu cultivator themselves.

The Gu cultivator's aptitude, talent, comprehension and personal experiences were conditions that restricted their production of true meaning.

Attainment level profundity of the same level would vary across the different people who were comprehending them. If one reached their limit and could not comprehend the profundity, they would start to develop illusions.

As expected, not long after, Gu cultivators on Book Mountain started to see illusions.

Some of them saw surging golden lotuses, some saw azure rain, some saw surging bloody water, some saw bone forests, or rainbow colored phoenixes that growled loudly.

"I, I can't persevere anymore!" A moment later, someone spat out blood and fainted.

More and more people followed.

But some Gu cultivators were still enduring.

With this, the talent, personal experiences and comprehension of the Gu cultivators were also clearly distinguished.

But by the time, those among Qin Ding Ling's group started to waver as sweat appeared on their foreheads, about ninety percent of Green Lotus Dao field's native Gu Immortals had already fallen.

"Even if these natives become Gu Immortals, they are still inferior to humans, who have the highest natural talent and intelligence." Fairy Yu Xiu nodded to herself.

After some observation, she had already gained a clear understanding of the strengths and weaknesses of the Gu Immortals from Green Lotus Dao field.

When Qin Ding Ling and the rest started to waver, the other Gu cultivators on the mountain had already fainted.

Bai Cang Shui fainted, Zhou Xiong Xin also fainted, followed by Jun Shen Guang.

Eventually, only three Heavenly Court members were left.

They were Qin Ding Ling, Che Wei, and Gu Yue Fang Zheng.

"Brother?" Gu Yue Fang Zheng's eyes were filled with blood, he grunted before fainting.

Thereafter, Qin Ding Ling smiled bitterly as she lost consciousness as well.

Che Wei lasted until the end.

Fairy Yu Xiu nodded to herself: "As expected of the creator of weapon path. Hmm? I actually misjudged."

Fairy Yu Xiu's expression suddenly changed as she shifted her gaze from Che Wei to a meteor at the bottom of the mountain.

This meteor was large as an elephant, it was also a Gu Immortal.

Earlier, it had fallen into a state of semi-unconsciousness. Even Fairy Yu Xiu did not expect that a certain strength would gather within the rock.

At this point, the mystical strength reached its limit, there was a qualitative change occurring.

Rumble!

With a thunderous sound, the meteor shattered as golden light shined in all directions.

From the piercing and blinding light, a rock monkey flew out.

The rock monkey landed on the ground and scratched its ears, shouting: "Brilliant, truly brilliant!"

Plop.

At the other end, Che Wei could no longer endure it, he fainted on the spot.

Fairy Yu Xiu's expression became even more peculiar: "This rock monkey is born from heaven and earth, it is extraordinary. It even has incredible talent surpassing Che Wei. With such potential, it will definitely reach great heights in the future!"

"Amazing, amazing."

"What a pity, what a pity."

Fairy Yu Xiu sighed continuously.

She was referring to Limitless Demon Venerable when she said 'amazing'.

Limitless Demon Venerable created Crazed Demon Cave, the derivation of new heaven path dao marks went on for over a million years, the results were huge. This rock monkey was the proof of it!

This rock monkey's potential and comprehension ability even surpassed Heavenly Court's members, it defeated Che Wei!

If this rock monkey was nurtured well and grew successfully, it might create its own path in the future.

But this rock monkey was destined to have a pitiful ending, it could not live for long.

It was meant to be Limitless Demon Venerable's sacrifice!

Even Heavenly Court could not let it off.

Because it was not a pure human.

This was also why Fairy Yu Xiu said 'what a pity'.

The rock monkey lasted for a few more minutes before falling on the ground, unconscious.

Fairy Yu Xiu stopped using the killer move, she started to rest.

Even though she did not consume her attainment level, the price of using this move was quite high. Be they thoughts, immortal essence, or her own lifespan, they were expended.

Not long after, the Gu Immortals started to wake up.

They started to cheer, unable to control themselves.

Their attainment levels had all risen, the problems that they faced normally with killer moves or incomplete Immortal Gu recipes were all resolvable now.

Many Gu Immortals even had new ideas regarding the modification of their current killer moves.

"Thank you, sage, for imparting the Dao to us!"

"Sage has unsurpassed virtue for imparting the Dao to us!"

The Gu Immortals knelt on the ground of their own will.

Fairy Yu Xiu smiled, her voice spreading throughout Book Mountain, before spreading to the entire Green Lotus World: "Three days later, I will hold another session to impart the Dao on Book Mountain again."

The immortals were stunned, at the next moment, a thunderous cheer resounded.

Three days later, not only on Book Mountain itself, even a large number of Gu Masters gathered near the base of Book Mountain.

Gu Masters could only surround Book Mountain but not ascend it, on the mountain base and the sides, many new Gu Immortals showed up.

These Gu Immortals came from various small worlds, hearing that a sage was imparting the Dao on Book Mountain, they came of their own accord to benefit from it.

Fairy Yu Xiu used endless learning again.

As illusions started to show up, everyone saw different sights.

"I can see many flowers!"

"So many pig heads are flying in the sky..."

"Fairy, don't run, you can't escape from me! Hehehe..."

"That rascal is dead meat, I'm telling you, even a Gu Immortal cannot save him!"

"The man of my dreams is an unparalleled hero who will come and marry me while riding on a rainbow cloud, even though I am also a man."

Chapter 2164: Ant Poison Appears Again

All sorts of illusions appeared.

Soon, the Gu Masters outside of the mountain quickly fell unconscious one by one.

Next, the ones on the mountain, those Gu Immortals who had attended the previous session also fainted in succession.

During the first session, they had already reached their limits. After just three days, the growth of their foundation was very limited.

Even Heavenly Court's members were no exception.

After them were the various mutant Gu Immortals of the small worlds. They had deep foundations and this was their first time attending the Dao lesson.

"Hmm?" Fairy Yu Xiu expressed her surprise again.

Among these mutant Gu Immortals, she found another genius this time.

It was a lump of deep green colored tornado, it persevered until the end. The aptitude and comprehension ability it displayed was equally matched with the rock monkey.

When this tornado Gu Immortal fell unconscious, Fairy Yu Xiu also stopped using her killer move.

By the time they awakened, she announced again: Three days later, the next session will be held.

For the third Dao lesson, even more Gu Immortals came.

Not only the mutants of the various small worlds, even Savage Wilderness Great World's and Yellow Earth Great World's Gu Immortals came.

Eventually, the one who lasted until the end was a lizard Gu Immortal.

This immortal came from Savage Wilderness Great World, its aptitude was on par with the rock monkey and tornado, they were extraordinarily talented.

Fairy Yu Xiu conducted three Dao lessons in total, the influence was not just kept in the three great worlds, it even spread to the remaining small worlds. Not only the small worlds at the boundaries of the three great worlds, but even many other small worlds that were currently being drawn to the central area.

Fairy Yu Xiu achieved her goal, the effect was evident.

Their impression on the various Gu Immortals of Green Lotus Grand World improved greatly, many Gu Immortals chose to join them.

Yu Xiu chose three leaders from among them, they were the rock monkey Bu Tian Kong, the tornado immortal Nie Kuang Feng, and finally, the lizard Gu Immortal from Savage Wilderness Great World, Duan Hu.

But a large number of Gu Immortals still chose to watch on the fence.

These Gu Immortals mostly came from small worlds, their worlds were still moving now, they had not landed near the three great worlds yet.

"Since this change occurred in the void, the unification of the worlds cannot be avoided, we need to find a good allegiance!"

"Indeed, we are all rulers of our small world, we can influence where we end up in to a certain extent."

"Green Lotus Great World's sage gave a Dao lesson, I wonder if the other two worlds' sages will do the same?"

Unavoidably, these Gu Immortals started to hold expectations.

A capable person will often choose to find a capable leader.

Even though they were native Gu Immortals that were not human, they had ample intelligence and were quite astute.

From Fairy Yu Xiu's Dao lessons, they sensed that she was trying to recruit them.

The three great worlds were in heated conflict, the amount of losses was huge and severe, it was the stage for them to shine on.

They even started to spread the word.

"If the other two great worlds do not give such a benefit, we will join Green Lotus Great World!"

"The three great worlds have existed for so long, Green Lotus Great World's sage imparted wisdom on everyone, they are truly magnanimous and benevolent. I am sure that the other two worlds' sages are the same."

"We will join whichever world gives the greatest benefits."

These Gu Immortals wanted to gain the most benefits for themselves.

As for which world they would end up joining?

Haha, they can decide that after getting the benefits!

The situation changed abruptly, Lu Wei Yin quickly went to Fang Yuan for a discussion.

Lu Wei Yin sighed: "Currently, Heavenly Court has the initiative again, after cooperating with Longevity Heaven, we managed to destabilize Heavenly Court's advantage over us, but with Fairy Yu Xiu's Dao lessons, all our efforts ended up in vain. But thankfully, the situation is salvageable, how should we go on to recruit those Gu Immortals who are still on the fence?"

Fang Yuan was silent.

These mutant Gu Immortals who were still roaming around were top tier cannon fodder, Heavenly Court's recruitment of them was a great move.

Fairy Yu Xiu's method also expanded Fang Yuan's horizons.

"Learning Gu... endless learning..."

Other than the dream realm, this was the first time Fang Yuan saw a killer move capable of directly raising attainment levels.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, he had no recollection of such a killer move.

From what he gathered and from Lu Wei Yin's information, there was no warning or hint that such a killer move existed.

This meant that the killer move was likely a new creation of Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court had deep foundation and countless elites who progressed and developed with time.

Lu Wei Yin looked at Fang Yuan as he said: "This killer move is extraordinary, it can raise the power of an entire force. Attainment level is very hard to raise, even I am slightly moved by Heavenly Court's offer. There is also something more worrying, within \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, there are records that Ren Zu and the other two went into Primordial Domain using true meaning."

"Heavenly Court possesses the killer move endless learning, this means that they have a method of creating true meaning that is unique in this world. This method might allow them to enter Primordial Domain earlier than others, or even like Book Mountain, they might be able to obtain Primordial Domain from the ninth layer!"

Fang Yuan nodded slightly.

Lu Wei Yin was very astute, all of his words made sense.

Primordial Domain was the key factor in the conflict of the three parties, even if a venerable revives successfully, to become a true Dao Lord again, they need to rely on Primordial Domain.

One could say that whoever obtains Primordial Domain first would gain the greatest advantage, they would become the eventual winner of this fight!

Fang Yuan pondered: "Endless learning is truly incredible and useful, but we also have a strategic level killer move ourselves. I have already used it."

Lu Wei Yin's expression turned to joy as he guessed: "That lingering poisonous ant plague killer move?"

Fang Yuan nodded while adding: "I used this move in Eastern Sea before, let's see how Heavenly Court deals with it. Other than that, we need to keep an eye on Longevity Heaven, I am quite curious about their following actions."

Lu Wei Yin thought about it and added: "Lord, since you have already used lingering poisonous ant plague, we should take the initiative to attack and exert pressure, when Heavenly Court is busy dealing with it, they will not have the time or energy to resist this move."

Fang Yuan had already shut his eyes: "You can go handle this matter. I want to deduce the Paradise Earth true inheritance here."

Lu Wei Yin immediately took his leave, his best idea was to communicate with Longevity Heaven and attack in unison.

After getting Lu Wei Yin's invitation, Longevity Heaven did not hesitate, they cooperated smoothly.

The truth was, their pressure was higher.

Many Gu Immortals defected from Savage Wilderness Great World to Green Lotus Great World, even more than Yellow Earth Great World. The most famous among them was Duan Hu.

This rank eight expert was very famous in Savage Wilderness Great World, with him taking the lead to join Heavenly Court, the influence on Longevity Heaven was dire.

Days later, Longevity Heaven and Fang Yuan sent out their troops again to attack Green Lotus Great World.

In the sky, Gu Immortals fought intensely.

"Kill!" Golden Fur Immortal Monarch held two large hammers on both hands as he attacked aggressively.

He was covered in thick golden fur, he had many Immortal Gu and killer moves, allowing his defense to be tight, he had no worries about charging forward.

The formation of Heavenly Court's mutant Gu Immortals were disrupted many times because of him.

"Don't be too arrogant." A child-like wood path Gu Immortal with grass growing on his head gritted his teeth as he blocked Golden Fur Immortal Monarch.

Golden Fur Immortal Monarch's advancement was halted, he fought against this immortal.

After dozens of rounds, there was no clear victor.

"Hmph!"

"I am Grass Head Child, I was born with an Immortal Gu, I am blessed with great fortune."

"You have Immortal Gu, but my Immortal Gu are also not fewer than yours!"

This wood path Gu Immortal shouted with a confident disposition.

Suddenly, his expression became distorted as his body started twisting around.

"So itchy!" Suddenly, Grass Head Child could not endure the intense feeling.

Wave of ants crawled out of his body, piercing his grass skin.

"What is going on? What are these things!" Grass Head Child was shocked, he quickly retreated.

"Hahaha, where are you going!" Golden Fur Immortal Monarch saw the chance and chased relentlessly.

Grass Head Child was hit by the killer move lingering poisonous ant plague, he was greatly distracted and lost his momentum, after several rounds, he was smashed into pulp by Golden Fur Immortal Monarch's hammer, dying on the spot.

Similar scenes were occurring to the other mutant Gu Immortals.

With the activation of lingering poisonous ant plague, the situation was immediately changed.

Originally, Heavenly Court had many mutant Gu Immortals, they were able to enter a deadlock with Fang Yuan's subordinates who were better equipped, but now that their immortal apertures were getting attacked, they lost all their morale, they had no will to fight.

"Run!"

"Why are there ants on my body as well?"

"Don't kill me, I surrender!"

The formation collapsed entirely, Fang Yuan's subordinates chased after them and obtained great results.

"This is the outcome for siding with Green Lotus Great World!"

"All the Gu Immortals who sided with them faced the judgment of lingering poisonous ant plague."

"Kill all the captives, our master has given orders, we will not accept them!"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and the rest cheered loudly, resounding in the entire battlefield.

They worked with another group from Longevity Heaven, making great advances and forcing Heavenly Court's mutant Gu Immortals to run in fear, unable to retaliate.

The defeated mutant Gu Immortals found that they could not resolve lingering poisonous ant plague killer move, they had to rush to Book Mountain and kneel towards the peak, requesting for the sage's help.

At the peak of Book Mountain.

Qin Ding Ling frowned: "Fang Yuan used that move after all! If we cannot resolve it, our great advantage is going to be lost entirely."

Many of the mutant Gu Immortals were still watching in anticipation.

If Green Lotus Great World was too weak, even if the benefits were huge, they would not join them.

After all, great benefits were pointless unless one had sufficient lifespan to enjoy them.

At this moment, Fairy Yu Xiu defended Book Mountain while Fairy Ming Hao went to the front lines, preventing Longevity Heaven's troops from causing any more trouble.

Fairy Yu Xiu was also quite troubled: "You have already given us the information of this lingering poisonous ant plague killer move. This is quite an impressive move, it contains poison path, enslavement path, refinement path, wood path, food path, and even heaven path profundity."

"It contains heaven path profundity?" Qin Ding Ling was deeply shocked: "No wonder Eastern Sea's Righteous Qi Alliance can only alleviate the effects of this move but not remove it completely!"

Chapter 2165: Operation of Heaven and Earth

Peak of Book Mountain.

Regarding Fang Yuan's lingering poisonous ant plague, Fairy Yu Xiu explained: "Thankfully, this move had already been used in Eastern Sea before, you also made Zui Xian Weng infiltrate Righteous Qi Alliance and obtained first-hand information about it. Thus, I am prepared against it."

"But the current lingering poisonous ant plague has been modified by Fang Yuan. My original method isn't going to be suitable, I need to modify it as well."

Qin Ding Ling heard this as her expression eased up slightly: "That will be good."

Fairy Yu Xiu smiled: "I only need three days to succeed. During this period, Heavenly Court can spread the news regarding lingering poisonous ant plague to everyone."

Qin Ding Ling acknowledged and left.

Not long after, the mutant Gu Immortals learned of the situation, they became very angry.

"Yellow Earth Great World's sage is truly too vicious!"

"I've heard that Yellow Earth Great World's Gu Immortals are united and harmonious. To think that their sage is such a vicious person, this is really a huge disappointment to everyone."

"In comparison, Green Lotus Great World's sage is really magnanimous, they have the disposition of a sage. Even Savage Wilderness Great World's sage pales in comparison."

The observing Gu Immortals were very disappointed. They waited for so long but neither Longevity Heaven nor Fang Yuan gave the response that they wanted.

They gained nothing from waiting, Yellow Earth Great World and Savage Wilderness Great World directly sent their troops and started the war!

These mutant Gu Immortals were very disappointed, but they also started to get angrier.

"The sages of these two great worlds are acting like this, are they not afraid that we will join Green Lotus Great World?"

"Hmph, the sages of these two worlds are too high and mighty."

"Forget it, I will join Green Lotus Great World instead!"

All of the observing mutant Gu Immortals chose to join Heavenly Court.

"Heavenly Court's wisdom path method is quite formidable. The emotions of these mutant Gu Immortals were influenced, according to what I know, many Gu Immortals made the decision to join Heavenly Court in a spurt of anger." Lu Wei Yin sighed as he explained to Fang Yuan.

Heavenly Court first spread information of Fang Yuan's vicious method before helping the mutant Gu Immortals resolve their lingering poisonous ant plague without asking for compensation, finally, they even used a method to influence the emotions of these mutant Gu Immortals.

After this series of actions, not only did they alleviate lingering poisonous ant plague's terrifying effect, they even retaliated and caused Fang Yuan and Longevity Heaven's position to be worse than before.

"Currently, Heavenly Court has recruited many mutant Gu Immortals, their advantage in numbers is increasingly evident. Should we recall our troops at the front lines?" Lu Wei Yin asked.

Fang Yuan smiled as he waved his hand: "Heavenly Court is formidable, according to my deduction, this mysterious wisdom path killer move contains heaven path profundity too, it is similar to heaven's will and has the ability to influence the thoughts and emotions of living beings."

"Lingering poisonous ant plague has been troubling the Righteous Qi Alliance but Heavenly Court managed to resolve this move so easily."

"In fact, I even modified this move once again."

"However, Longevity Heaven is taking action now, let's watch and see before making a decision."

Gu Tou Luan was one of the mutant Gu Immortals who joined Heavenly Court.

After making the agreement with Heavenly Court, she traveled through the void and returned to her small world.

Using several days, she set up an immortal formation.

This immortal formation was Heavenly Court's reinforcement, after activating it, it could influence the travel route of the small world, allowing it to land on the boundary of Green Lotus Great World.

"Green Lotus Great World's sage is truly unfathomable. This immortal formation is amazing and has huge power but the expended immortal essence is so little."

Gu Tou Luan praised internally as she activated the immortal formation.

The immortal formation burst out with profound light, spreading from the inside to the outside of the small world.

The small world had always been moving towards the center of the void, but under the effect of the immortal formation, it started to change its trajectory slightly.

"Hmm?!" After several breaths of time, Gu Tou Luan's expression turned to shock.

"What is going on? I activated the immortal formation but the small world is uncontrollable, it is forcefully moving towards another direction!"

"Is the immortal formation ineffective?"

Gu Tou Luan quickly checked and was shocked to find out: It was not that the immortal formation was useless, but a profound force had been influencing her small world from long ago.

Compared to this vast force, the immortal formation had no strength to counter it.

Gu Tou Luan could only watch as her homeland flew and landed on the boundary of Savage Wilderness Great World.

This was not a unique situation, many small worlds were influenced and landed on Savage Wilderness Great World, while others were still on their way.

Gu Tou Luan and the other mutant Gu Immortals were stunned.

They joined Green Lotus Great World, but their own small worlds ended up in Savage Wilderness Great World, they would definitely be absorbed by Savage Wilderness Great World and fuse into it.

"This is the method of Savage Wilderness Great World's sage!"

"Unbelievable, that sage already took action long ago. He is actually able to attract all the small worlds."

"Only those small worlds at the periphery were spared."

"What do we do?"

Many Gu Immortals were starting to feel regret. Had they known this, they would not have joined Green Lotus Great World so quickly.

Peak of Book Mountain.

"This is Giant Sun's heaven and earth luck method." Qin Ding Ling sighed: "Fate is fixed while luck is a variable. Longevity Heaven disregarded the cost and brought Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace here, they have already started to influence the heaven and earth luck of the eighth layer of Crazed Demon Cave. Thus, these small worlds were all drawn to them."

"It is a venerable method after all." Fairy Yu Xiu sighed. Even though they could understand Longevity Heaven's method, they had no way of resolving it.

Not only because Longevity Heaven was superior to Heavenly Court in terms of luck path methods.

But because this method was used by Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace, to resolve it, they had to destroy the palace.

And Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace had been hiding deep within Savage Wilderness Great World, now that pseudo venerables could not use their full strength, who could reach it and destroy it?

Heavenly Court had no answer, they could only sit and wait.

This way, Heavenly Court gathered most of the mutant Gu Immortals, they had advantage in numbers. Longevity Heaven obtained most of the small worlds, Savage Wilderness Great World was growing and expanding rapidly.

Only Fang Yuan's side was the weakest, during this period, not only did they not recruit many mutant Gu Immortals, they also failed to get many small worlds.

Heavenly Court started to instruct the mutant Gu Immortals to retaliate, the front lines that went deep into Green Lotus Great World started to be pushed away outwards again.

Gu Masters gathered into armies, fighting and killing all over the battlefield.

Immortals fought in the air, it was an intense battle.

Rock monkey Bu Tian Kong roamed unhindered, with a sudden roar, it vanished on the spot.

"This move again!" Bing Zhuo's eyelids were twitching, he quickly looked around him: "Where? Where will he show up?!"

But Bu Tian Kong did not attack Bing Zhuo, it teleported behind Shi Zong instead.

"Take my fist!" Bu Tian Kong shouted.

Shi Zong quickly defended himself but his defensive killer move was quickly broken through.

Bu Tian Kong's fist pierced Shi Zong's chest, protruding out of his back.

Bu Tian Kong snickered, its body shook as a killer move was activated, Shi Zong exploded and shattered into pieces that flew everywhere.

Shi Zong and Bing Zhuo were rank eight Gu Immortals, while Bu Tian Kong also had rank eight cultivation level, to think that he managed to kill Shi Zong while going up against two opponents.

"No matter what formation this is, I will send it flying!" At the other end, Nie Kuang Feng, who was inside the Rotting Smell Vicious Cloud formation, shouted.

The six eggman Gu Immortals from Rotten Egg grotto-heaven formed into the ancient battle formation Rotting Smell Vicious Cloud as they trapped Nie Kuang Feng for some time, at this point, they were unable to hold on anymore as the latter broke out from within.

The six eggman Gu Immortals spat out blood in response, they were either dead or injured.

And on another battlefield.

Duan Hu fought against Lu Tong Lan.

Lu Tong Lan was the Desolate Extremity of the Eight Extremities, but she actually fell into a disadvantage.

Duan Hu's attacks were powerful and wild, its body was tough like a mountain, when colliding, it felt like one was colliding with the world itself, Lu Tong Lan's blue phoenix totem killer move was almost destroyed in the fight.

"These three immortals were born with immense innate luck, they are the luck children of Crazed Demon Cave's eighth layer. Originally, Yellow Earth Great World should have produced such an expert too, it is a pity..."

Fang Yuan understood the reason behind these three immortals' existence, he casted his gaze at Paradise Earth's tomb.

Using luck inspection killer move, he saw that this Paradise Earth's tomb had immense luck that resembled a yellow soil mountain, it was unmoving and incredibly dense.

These days, with their losses at the front lines, many of Fang Yuan's subordinates also died.

But Fang Yuan remained calm as ice, these fatalities were just numbers to him.

The longer this dragged on, the more advantageous it was for him.

Fang Yuan had already comprehended a lot of the profundities regarding Paradise Earth's tomb, in the past he did not have the ability to create his own Tomb Earth, but now, he could create a huge graveyard in the sovereign immortal aperture to act as a node of the earth vein.

Most of Fang Yuan's time and energy were spent comprehending the refinement path profundity here.

Ordinary Gu Immortals refined Immortal Gu, while Limitless Demon Venerable refined the worlds of heaven and earth.

This gap in refinement path was now quickly filled up by Fang Yuan, he was even gaining huge results from it.

At the same time, Fang Yuan gained a deeper and clearer understanding of Limitless Demon Venerable's arrangements.

"It is time." Fang Yuan muttered lightly, he gazed afar with his deep abyss-like eyes.

Crack!

A shocking flash of lightning landed on the battlefield.

The immortals on the battlefield were shocked.

In an instant, lightning bolts crashed down like a forest, the immortals had to stop and retreat immediately.

Thereafter, tribulations of various intensity rained down like a torrent, occurring to all three great worlds and their boundaries.

At the peak of Book Mountain, Qin Ding Ling was shocked: "What is going on?"

After making some deductions, Fairy Yu Xiu explained confidently: "This is Limitless Demon Venerable's method, so it turns out that when the fusion of worlds reach a certain stage, tribulations will befall."

At the same time, Fang Yuan's gaze focused on these tribulations that were extremely far away.

Waves of comprehension emerged in the depth of his mind.

"All tribulations are superb methods in refining heaven and earth."

"Gu Immortals manage their immortal aperture, under normal circumstances, their main source of dao marks come from tribulations."

"When Gu Immortals successfully pass a tribulation, they would gain a large number of dao marks. These dao marks will modify the immortal aperture and cause the environment to change, this is the refinement of heaven and earth."

By expanding this logic, all tribulations were refinement path methods.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly.

At this point, the refinement path profundity regarding the refinement of the world and heaven and earth had already been comprehended by him to a large extent.

"Earlier, my luck gave me an indication. Now is the time to use that move."

Fang Yuan started to activate heaven's envy Immortal Gu!

Chapter 2166: Heaven Envies Heroic Geniuses

The sky was in chaos, Gu Immortals fought intensely everywhere.

Wild winds blew, wind blades shot all over the place.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch paused for a moment, his body was surrounded by wind blades from all directions.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's square face was covered in frost, he snorted coldly, he shot out immense crystal frost qi that destroyed all the wind blades.

But at the next moment, Nie Kuang Feng suddenly arrived right before him.

Nie Kuang Feng was a green tornado to begin with, it condensed into a ball and burst out with a terrifying suction force!

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch wanted to dodge but it was too late, he was trapped by the tornado, unable to escape for the moment.

"Oh no!" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's expression changed.

It was too late to use extreme ice crystal light immortal suppression coffin now.

Normally speaking, the stronger the killer move, the longer the time needed to use it. When fighting against Nie Kuang Feng, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch could not find the time or opportunity to use this move.

At the crucial moment, this move could no longer be used. During a deadlock, using this move would expose weaknesses for the enemy to exploit. Even if he used it, with the enemy on guard, the effect would not be decisive either.

"Hehehe, this is my signature killer move — Wind Suction Life Twister! I spent thirty years to painstakingly create it, before spending a hundred years to modify it. Nobody has ever survived against this move, you will be no exception."

Nie Kuang Feng laughed wildly.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's expression was grim, it was too late to dodge now, he could only activate his defensive killer moves desperately.

"Ahh—!"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch cried out in pain.

First, his arms were absorbed into Nie Kuang Feng's body, even though they were covered in thick ice crystals, they only lasted for a few moments before disintegrating.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's arms were directly shredded into particles!

Next was Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's body.

"I am finished." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch felt despair at this moment, but suddenly, a bolt of black lightning shot down.

Nie Kuang Feng was directly hit and suffered a huge blow, its suction force stopped for a moment.

The speed of Nie Kuang Feng's wind ball tornado fell greatly, within the green wind, there was a large area of black ink-like color that got corrupted.

"Damn it, tribulations appeared again." Nie Kuang Feng gritted its teeth.

Since several days ago, tribulations started to occur at all corners of the various great worlds.

Especially places with more Gu Immortals, they would encounter more tribulations.

Now that there were many Gu Immortals fighting intensely on the battlefield, it was not strange to have many tribulations occurring here.

Nie Kuang Feng's attention was drawn to Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch again: "Die!"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch tried his best to break free but he could not get away from Nie Kuang Feng's suction force, he was pulled into Nie Kuang Feng's body inch by inch.

"I am finished!" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch felt despair at this moment once again, but suddenly, a bolt of black lightning shot down.

Crack, the black lightning bolt landed on Nie Kuang Feng.

Nie Kuang Feng froze again, the black color in the green wind tornado became denser.

"This tribulation is so strong, it can actually cause such injuries to me." Nie Kuang Feng sighed, growling at Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch: "But you cannot escape, your life is mine!"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch was sucked into the tornado again.

"It seems that my life is really going to end here." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch sighed again, but at this moment, a bolt of black lightning shot down on Nie Kuang Feng.

Nie Kuang Feng's movements froze, the tornado twisted and almost seemed like it would explode!

"What happened?"

"What is going on with this tribulation?!"

"Why did it hit me three times in a row? I am so close to Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch yet it did not even hit him once?"

"Is his luck that good? I don't believe it!"

"I'll suck him in with me!"

Crack.

Black lightning shot down, landing on Nie Kuang Feng.

Nie Kuang Feng refused to believe its luck: "I'll do it again."

Crack.

"I do not believe it, I'll draw him in!"

Crack, crack, crack!

Nie Kuang Feng could not take it anymore.

As black lightning bolts continued to shoot down, they landed on his head without any deviation.

Nie Kuang Feng's body almost collapsed, it could not draw in Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch anymore.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch took the chance to retreat, quickly getting away from Nie Kuang Feng.

"I actually survived? What in the world is going on?" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch was lucky to survive, he was filled with disbelief and surprise.

Far away, black lightning continued to land on Nie Kuang Feng.

No matter where Nie Kuang Feng went, black lightning seemed to target it specifically.

No, not only black lightning, soon, tribulations like blood dragons and grey spirits also went to approach Nie Kuang Feng.

Nie Kuang Feng was going crazy, at this moment, it felt like the entire world was going against it!

Of course, tribulations also landed on other Gu Immortals, but Nie Kuang Feng experienced the most animosity from these tribulations.

While Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch healed himself, he observed and found another person who faced the same situation as Nie Kuang Feng.

It was rock monkey Bu Tian Kong!

This unlucky monkey was currently fighting against several rank eight Gu Immortals like Solid Rock Warrior.

Countless bats and white flying cranes attacked him, disrupting the rock monkey's attacks and causing it to lose momentum.

Even though Solid Rock Warrior and the rest were also affected by the tribulations, they were less targeted and found an opportunity to retaliate fiercely.

The rock monkey was very troubled, in this situation, it could only turn from offensive to defensive.

Peak of Book Mountain.

"What is going on?" Qin Ding Ling stood up, her expression had changed.

Book Mountain was an information path secluded domain of heaven and earth, because of Heavenly Court's method, it had been collecting the information of the two battlefields.

Thus, even though Qin Ding Ling stayed at the headquarters, she quickly observed many of the changes in the battlefields.

Currently, Heavenly Court's troops had already moved into Savage Wilderness Great World and Yellow Earth Great World.

The tribulations in Savage Wilderness Great World were quite low regardless of strength or quantity.

Green Lotus Great World had an ordinary number of tribulations.

But Yellow Earth Great World was clearly abnormal, not only were they more severe, they even targeted Nie Kuang Feng and Bu Tian Kong.

"What is going on here?" Qin Ding Ling was uncertain and shocked.

Fairy Yu Xiu had started her deduction long ago, after getting the result, she said: "Amazing move, this should be Fang Yuan's work. This mysterious killer move can actually amplify calamities and tribulations of heaven and earth, prioritizing the targets that have the most outstanding aptitude and talent."

"Nie Kuang Feng and Bu Tian Kong represent the small worlds and Green Lotus Great World respectively, they are two of those who have the greatest innate luck among all the inhabitants of Crazed Demon Cave's eighth layer."

"Thus, they were targeted specifically!"

"Hmm?" Saying this, Fairy Yu Xiu's expression suddenly changed: "This killer move's range is increasing rapidly, it has already arrived here."

"Oh no." Qin Ding Ling's expression changed yet again as she raised her head to look up.

Above Book Mountain, tribulation clouds rumbled, covering the entire sky with endless thick layers of over ten thousand li of space!

"The tribulations are still intensifying, what is going on?" Qin Ding Ling gritted her teeth, even someone like her felt a terrifying might from the tribulation clouds above her.

Fairy Yu Xiu's expression was grim: "This tribulation is targeting Fairy Feng Ya. She possesses talent Gu, she has been in closed cultivation to deduce Limitless Demon Venerable's arrangement to the best of her abilities."

When wisdom path Gu Immortals made deductions, they were also exposing themselves.

Thus, heaven and earth detected Fairy Feng Ya's existence, it started to create a tribulation to exterminate her!

"Fang Yuan's mysterious killer move actually makes use of Limitless Demon Venerable's arrangement to attack our Heavenly Court, he is really vicious." Qin Ding Ling said in anger: "Lady Yu Xiu, please allow me to bring Divine Emperor City to the front lines and find trouble with Fang Yuan so that he cannot use this move casually."

"No. That is exactly what Fang Yuan wants to see." Fairy Yu Xiu shook her head and said with a firm attitude: "The key now is to protect Fairy Feng Ya. We will gather our formation and resist the tribulation, we will give Fairy Feng Ya the most optimal environment to make deductions."

At almost the same time, in Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun also sensed Fang Yuan's method, he praised in amazement: "This method contains heaven path profundity, it is truly out of my expectations that Fang Yuan seems to be cultivating heaven path! I wonder what the name of this move is?"

"Hmph!" Desolate Extremity Jiao Huo said in displeasure: "Fang Yuan has already allied with us, yet he is using this move on our Savage Wilderness Great World as well, causing our subordinates to face its effects too."

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun smiled lightly: "When we made the alliance agreement, he had already considered this, thus he used the loophole and is not breaking our alliance. After all, this move is mainly targeting the Gu Immortal Duan Hu."

"But our Gu Immortals are being weakened by the tribulation, that is the truth." Jiao Huo said.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun nodded, his gaze turning deeper: "He is forcing me to take action. Hahaha, very interesting, then I shall make my move to deal with this method."

"Master!" All the Gu Immortals in the hall shouted in concern.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun waved his hand: "Don't worry, the fate war has ended for a long time already, my strength has been recovering steadily. Moreover, I am taking action now not just to deal with Fang Yuan's killer move but also to participate in the operations of the worlds, I want to observe Limitless Demon Venerable's arrangements more deeply."

At the next moment, Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace shot out with a beam of light soaring to the sky, it was grand and powerful, shining in golden radiance.

"Very good, Longevity Heaven took action already." Fang Yuan soon sensed the commotion at Savage Wilderness Great World.

He looked over there, his gaze crossing a huge distance as he analyzed Savage Wilderness Great World.

"Longevity Heaven had a trump card indeed."

"At this moment, Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace activated and surged with luck path aura. This effect mixed into the operations of the worlds, combining with Limitless Demon Venerable's arrangements to hasten the fusion of the small worlds."

"No, there is also the method of all living beings luck in use."

"Longevity Heaven's subordinate mutant Gu Immortals are being taken care of, they are facing less pressure from the tribulations now."

Fang Yuan observed for some time and gained great insights.

At his current level, he could already gain comprehension of other paths using his own as a foundation. Right now, by just observing a move from Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, Fang Yuan could deduce a lot of the profundity of all living beings luck and heaven and earth luck.

The move that Fang Yuan activated was called heaven envies heroic geniuses, it used heaven's envy Immortal Gu as the core and targeted those people with outstanding talents.

Originally, Fang Yuan wanted to use this move on venerables, but now, it was unleashed at a superb timing, it complemented Limitless Demon Venerable's arrangements and used his power to allow this move to spread out across the various great worlds, amplifying its strength!

Chapter 2167: Wooden Statue Lord Wu Guang

It rained not long ago.

The sky of Northern Plains was pale white, it looked extremely clear.

A Gu Immortal lowered his altitude, he was only tens of feet above the ground, flying rapidly as he scanned the area below him, seeming trying to find something.

This Gu Immortal was bare chested, his body was well proportioned and his muscles were bulging. He has an ordinary face, a sharp nose and pursed lips, giving the impression of a man with perseverance.

He looked at the ground with lush growing grass, a field of green filled his vision. But observing closely, he found that the ground below the grass were cracked and shattered, there was something going on here.

Because the Northern Plains Gu Immortal had sensed something amiss here, he came to investigate.

Now, he had already inspected the range of a hundred li.

Suddenly, a green shadow flashed in the crack of the ground.

"Found you!" The Northern Plains Gu Immortal's eyes shined, he flew down rapidly with a grey shadow around him, he was filled with determination like an eagle hunting its prey.

Rumble!

The Northern Plains Gu Immortal directly crashed into the ground, causing a huge explosion, rocks flew while grass swayed in the air from the shock wave.

The Gu Immortal hit the target with one attack!

"Hmm?" At the next moment, his pupils contracted.

The ground cracked open, revealing a huge body below the topsoil, it resembled a huge yellow dragon.

But looking closely, it was not a dragon but a huge trunk of a ginseng.

The ginseng trunk was yellow in color, covered in wrinkles and gave people a feeling of great strength.

Even though it was attacked, the ginseng trunk exploded with terrifying power, as if a giant dragon was turning over its body.

Boom, boom, the surrounding ground was cracked again, grass and soil splattered, the Northern Plains Gu Immortal was sent flying by this action.

He flew up into the sky and saw the entirety of the ginseng. In the surrounding hundred li of area, yellowish ginseng roots were protruding out of the soil, it looked like a forest had appeared.

Several hundred roots that resembled yellow dragons attacked the Northern Plains Gu Immortal in a frenzy.

The Gu Immortal took a deep breath, grey shadows appeared around his body.

Under the cover of the grey shadows, his figure became blurred like a shadow, he alternated between intangible and solid.

As the ginseng roots landed on his body, they passed through like he was an illusion, there was no effect.

The Northern Plains Gu Immortal was like the moon in the lake, no matter how the water rippled, he was completely unaffected.

The Gu Immortal thus regained his footing and started to prepare his offensive method.

As the killer move was unleashed, greenish grey wooden spikes with the size of ancient trees stabbed into the ginseng roots, pinning them to the ground.

The Gu Immortal continued to use this move as the surrounding ginseng roots fell in number.

"What a good thing!" The Northern Plains Gu Immortal was called Wu Guang, he was a rank seven wood path Gu Immortal, titled Wooden Statue Lord.

He observed the ginseng roots for some time, his gaze becoming increasingly heated.

This yellowish ginseng was a mysterious product, even the wood path cultivator Wu Guang did not know much about it.

But this was quite a common situation. After the five regions merged, earth veins rumbled and qi tides surged, a vast quantity of cultivation resources appeared one by one, among which were many strange and mysterious things.

This ancient desolate plant was one of them.

It was found by Wooden Statue Lord Wu Guang by chance.

This gigantic ginseng had extraordinary value.

If Wu Guang could successfully obtain it, it would be a profitable source of revenue in the long run. But it was not easy to subdue a wild ancient desolate plant, compared to those desolate plants who were cultivated from saplings.

Subduing an ancient desolate plant required enslavement path methods, this was not Wu Guang's expertise.

But he was not asking for much now, he wanted to kill the giant ginseng and get a huge quantity of immortal materials.

Problems would arise if this dragged on, he was currently in the territory of the Huang Jin bloodline tribes, if they found him, the lone immortal Wu Guang would not reap any gains.

Immortal killer move — Decaying Wooden Death!

After the roots surrounding Wu Guang thinned to a certain extent, Wu Guang pushed with both palms, a loud explosion could be heard, a grey light pillar shot through the sky, landing on the trunk of the ginseng.

On the ginseng trunk, a huge hole was formed, it got instantly pierced by the light pillar.

The roots that were still attacking Wu Guang seemed to have lost all their strength, they fell to the ground like feeble insects, no longer having their strength like before.

"It is over." Wu Guang smiled lightly, but suddenly, his expression changed!

Rumble!

At the next moment, the ground shook intensely like heaven and earth was flipping around. A thousand ginseng roots appeared at once, they were tall and mighty, each being over a hundred feet in height, roots filled the entire place as their shadow cast down on Wu Guang's body.p

Wu Guang was greatly shocked to realize that the ginseng trunk he perceived earlier was merely a larger branch of the entire plant.

"This ancient desolate plant likely has tens of thousands of years of history. It is very close to rank eight, it is at the peak of an ancient desolate plant!" Wu Guang was deeply shook.

Countless roots slammed down.

Wu Guang quickly dodged them.

But right at this moment, the wild Immortal Gu living in a certain part of the ginseng burst out with power, causing Wu Guang's speed to fall rapidly.

Wu Guang was hit by many roots at the same time.

At the crucial moment, the grey shadows appeared again!

A thousand ginseng roots rampaged like huge whips, cracking the air as they moved, creating huge shock waves.

Wu Guang's body shook intensely, his immortal essence expenditure was very high.

"Oh no." Wu Guang could sense the aura of death. At this rate, his immortal essence storage was going to be emptied.

Even though he relied on a defensive method and managed to stay alive, this defensive killer move had a huge flaw, once activated, the Gu Immortal could not move, they had to stay at the same spot.

Wu Guang fell into danger again.

The situation changed too quickly, at the next moment, he was at the brink of life and death.

Wu Guang was feeling bitter internally.

He had been too overconfident, he did not investigate the situation more clearly.

As a matter of fact, the ginseng had been moving underground, it was not easy for Wu Guang to find it and force it to come to the surface. If he had to make a thorough investigation, by the time he finished, the ginseng would have escaped into the ground already.

"It is too late to say anything now, to think that I, Wu Guang, would die in the hands of an ancient desolate plant."

As his immortal essence dried out, Wu Guang started to feel despair.

Roar—!

Right at this moment, a fierce tiger attacked.

The tiger was black in color and gave off a metallic luster, it was huge like a mountain and had sharp and powerful claws, it easily tore the ginseng roots to shreds, it was extraordinarily fierce.

"What ancient desolate beast is this? No, wait, this is a killer move." Wu Guang stared with wide eyes, feeling surprised and curious.

The black tiger fought against the ginseng roots, the two were stuck in a deadlock, being evenly matched.

Rumble!

At the next moment, the ground shook again.

The ginseng roots suddenly straightened before falling to the ground with a loud thud, no longer moving again.

"What? This mysterious ancient desolate plant got killed by someone in one move!" Wu Guang was shocked, his internal worry became much deeper.

Often, humans were much scarier than beasts or plants.

Wu Guang did not need to think to know that the Gu Immortal who killed the ancient desolate plant was very strong, extremely strong!

Once Wu Guang escaped death, he saw a green robed Gu Immortal.

Wu Guang knew this person, he immediately cupped his fists: "So it was you who saved my life, Chen Cheng."

Gu Immortal Chen Cheng waved his hand: "I was only assisting, the one who saved your life is my master."

"Master? Whose servant did you become?" Wu Guang was shocked.

At this moment, the ground cracked as a figure flew up into the sky.

Wu Guang stared with wide eyes at this female immortal, she wore a half-mask that covered the lower half of her face.

Her brows were sharp and her eyes shined with brilliant light, she wore a black-gold armor with an aura of domination around her, intimidating her foes.

The one who entered the ground to kill the mysterious ginseng was Hei Lou Lan.

Roar—!

The black tiger roared as it returned to her, turning into a tattoo on Hei Lou Lan's skin.

It was the totem killer move — Dark Capital Strength Tiger.

Wu Guang had never seen this move or even heard of it, upon seeing this sight, his shock intensified.

Hei Lou Lan looked down at him at an angle: "I saved you, how will you repay me?"

Wu Guang's body shook, he quickly expressed his gratitude: "I will not forget the debt of saving my life! I wonder what I can do for you? As long as you tell me, I will do my best to complete your request."

But Hei Lou Lan laughed as she looked at Chen Cheng: "I see that you are acquainted with him, what use does this person have?"

Chen Cheng: "Master, we are heading to Crescent Moon Mound to challenge Yin Wu Que, this person has a close relationship with him, he can lead the way."

Wu Guang quickly added: "I am acquainted with Brother Yin, but the challenge..."

Chen Cheng smiled as he explained: "Master succeeded in her cultivation, she came out of seclusion to challenge the experts of the world, she wants to face off against the various geniuses. I lost to her and according to the agreement, I became her servant."

Wu Guang took in a deep breath: "So that's it..."

He was hesitant.

Yin Wu Que was his good friend, if he had to lead this expert to his friend for a fight, regardless of result, he would feel very troubled.

But Hei Lou Lan did not care about Wu Guang's feelings, she said: "Lead the way."

Wu Guang shook internally.

Hei Lou Lan's tone was filled with dominance that did not allow rejection.

Wu Guang was sure that if he defied her, he would end up like the ginseng earlier.

"Please follow me, benefactor and Chen Cheng." Wanting to preserve his own life, Wu Guang led the way.

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Milky white sea water rose and fell with the tides, the sea was covered in thick fog, one could not see anything including their five fingers.

In this milky white fog, countless people seemed to be moving in it rapidly at all times.

Shi Zong's mind was completely chaotic, he was muddled and dazed, he was submerged in the sea water at times, while floating in the white fog at other times.

He could vaguely hear a voice calling him: "Shi Zong, since you are awake, why are you not coming out?"

Thus, he followed this voice and walked out of the sea, arriving at the shore.

He was bare naked with no clothing on him, after leaving Human Sea, he suddenly jolted awake.

Looking at the dense white fog and sea around him, he checked his own body.

He was in disbelief: "Didn't, didn't I die already?!"

"Shi Zong, you have already revived in master's secluded domain of heaven and earth, Human Sea. But your cultivation level has been lost, you are a mortal and will need to cultivate from the start again." The Gu Immortal who led him out smiled as he said.

Shi Zong was speechlessly dazed, after a while, he fell to the ground as he knelt by the shore.

"I was able to revive all thanks to master's kindness and generosity!" Shi Zong raised his head and shouted, tears flowing down his face in excitement.

Chapter 2168: Unifying Human And Gu

Before Fang Yuan entered Crazed Demon Cave, the secluded domain of heaven and earth Human Sea had already been completed.

In order to construct the complete Human Sea, Fang Yuan ordered the slaughter of countless humans, he had unsurmountable sin and blood on his hands, but he also achieved his goal as he obtained the results that he expected at this moment.

Evidently, if news that dead Gu Immortals could revive through Human Sea spread among his subordinates, Fang Yuan's force would gain a huge boost in morale!

The truth was, in the five hundred years of his previous life, Human Sea secluded domain was used by Eastern Sea's Xia clan.

In Fang Yuan's first life of five hundred years.

When Xia clan's Gu Immortals died outside, they were not truly dead, they could revive from Human Sea. Although their Immortal Gu and immortal aperture's accumulations would be lost, they would still retain their cultivation level and immortal aperture itself.

Eastern Sea's Xia clan gained a huge reputation because of this, for the following period of time, they invaded Southern Border. Southern Border's Gu Immortals fought against Xia clan, over time, they learned about Xia clan's background and foundation, eventually, Chai clan mimicked Human Sea and created their own Human Mountain secluded domain.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, fate Gu was only damaged but not entirely destroyed. Now, fate Gu was completely gone.

Thus, Human Sea could revive Gu Immortals with much less difficulty.

But Fang Yuan did not let those Gu Immortals who revived become Gu Immortals again immediately.

Firstly, to revive a Gu Immortal who retained their cultivation level, it would cause a huge expenditure to Human Sea. After a few uses, he would need to slaughter a massive number of humans and variant humans to replenish it.

It was not that Fang Yuan could not bear to do that, but it was troublesome.

Also, if these Gu Immortals became mortals again and had to cultivate all over again, Fang Yuan could make use of them.

Firstly, these revived Gu Masters had the foundation of a Gu Immortal, they had rich cultivation experience, it was probable that they would succeed in immortal ascension again. During their ascension, the natural inspiration would be a good chance for Fang Yuan to get answers he wanted!

Secondly, when these Gu Immortals re-cultivate, they would need to undergo tribulations, Fang Yuan could help them with that and gain heaven path dao marks.

Finally, after these Gu Immortals cultivate from the start, they might gain inspiration and innovate new killer moves. In the process, they would also be more reliant on Fang Yuan, it would mean that he would gain greater control over them.

But at this moment, after using the killer move human revival sea, his heart shook as inspiration flashed in his mind.

At this moment, he obtained a crucial breakthrough in refinement path.

"So the human body Gu refinement method is like this." Brilliance flashed in Fang Yuan's mind, a light sense of joy appeared in his heart.

The so-called Human Sea revival method was in essence using a Gu cultivator method to refine the human body and soul. This was a human path method indeed, but it was also using Gu to refine a human!

Fang Yuan lacked insight on the human body Gu refinement method earlier. When he researched on Ni clan, he found that the human body Gu refinement method was related to blood path and others, this conclusion was not wrong.

"Using a human to refine Gu and using Gu to refine a human, the two are interchangeable in essence."

These two were like the two sides of a coin, they existed with one another.

The true core was — Unifying Human and Gu!

It was like sovereign immortal fetus Gu, it was a Gu worm that could turn into a human body after activation. But it did not provide a soul, instead, the sovereign immortal body would be created with the most compatibility with the Gu cultivator's soul.

When Fang Yuan used Human Sea to revive a Gu Immortal, he was refining a human body and also a human soul.

Looking at the legendary immemorial desolate beast Qing Chou, it was originally a killer move that was converted into a life form.

This meant that any life form could be created with a Gu cultivation method!

This was totally possible in theory.

And the truth was, this was already hinted in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

In \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, chapter three section fourteen, it was clearly stated. The myriad lifeforms in the world were originally secluded domains of heaven and earth — Gu worms within the Blue Sea of Life. These Gu worms were washed ashore by the waves of the Blue Sea, turning into all sorts of lifeforms.

All the countless methods converged into the same origin.

Using Gu to refine Human, using Human to refine Gu, Human and Gu were one to begin with!

Although Fang Yuan understood this logic, he had only fully comprehended the complete details of this logic at this moment in time.

This comprehension broke through the thin barrier that obstructed him, Fang Yuan could see a bright scene beyond it.

He only needed to make a small deduction now to design a killer move that could unravel Ni clan's Gu Immortal method, he could extract all sorts of Immortal Gu from the Ni clan members' bodies.

It was not easy to reach this stage.

Fang Yuan had a foundation in this aspect already, after all, he used the human isolation style Gu refinement method in the five hundred years of his previous life.

In this life, he had all sorts of encounters and accumulations in this aspect.

Even though Ni clan was not his breakthrough point, by studying and analyzing them, Fang Yuan gained a deeper foundation.

Eventually, the immense foundation led to a qualitative change, Fang Yuan unexpectedly succeeded in his breakthrough due to Human Sea.

Throughout history, refinement path had two styles.

The first was the hairy man nature Gu refinement method, it used nature and dao marks to refine Gu.

The opposite was Limitless Demon Venerable using Gu worms to refine heaven and earth.

The second was the human isolation style. Ni clan's Gu Immortal, the refinement path quasi-supreme Ni Ren, used humans to refine Gu, implanting all sorts of Immortal Gu deep within the bloodlines of his Ni clan descendants.

The opposite was sovereign immortal fetus Gu, the Human Sea revival method, and the Blue Sea of Life which used Gu to refine human.

"The depth of refinement path supreme grandmaster should likely comprise these four aspects. Currently, I have already comprehended human and Gu refinement methods, I only lack the final 'using Gu to refine heaven and earth' aspect! By comprehending the arrangements of Limitless Demon Venerable, I have already broken through this hurdle, I have passed the initial stage with no obstacles remaining, as long as I continue progressing, I will eventually comprehend all the profundities." Fang Yuan evaluated.

Treasure yellow heaven.

Bai Ning Bing's divine sense roamed around within it.

She was selling immortal materials.

Ever since she saw Fang Huan's revival by chance and killed him, Bai Ning Bing obtained a large number of desolate beast and ancient desolate beast corpses. She even obtained the true inheritance from searching Fang Huan's soul.

Bai Ning Bing's immortal materials were already about to be sold out.

Only the last portion was left.

"How are you selling these immortal materials?" At this time, a divine sense came and asked for the price.

Bai Ning Bing explained the sale price.

After Little Immortal Xing Luo heard the price, she shrank slightly and wanted to bargain: "Can it be a little cheaper?"

Immediately after, Little Immortal Xing Luo stated her quote: "If you sell at this price, I'll buy it directly!"

Bai Ning Bing wanted to refine Gu herself, she created the killer move breath concealment ice pearl, if she could refine an ice pearl Immortal Gu, it would supplement this killer move greatly.

She had already collected most of the immortal materials now, Bai Ning Bing did not excel at trading, she wanted to nod and agree to the transaction when suddenly, another divine sense got closer.

"Oh, someone is actually selling the mala[1] duck's neck? This food path ancient desolate beast is very rare, where did you find it from?" The divine sense asked.

Bai Ning Bing was unwilling to expose clues about herself, she asked directly: "Are you buying or not?"

"What price?"

Bai Ning Bing expressed the price while the divine sense said: "I'll buy it, I'll buy everything. Do you need immortal essence stones or immortal materials?"

Bai Ning Bing gave the list of ice and snow path immortal materials she needed.

The divine sense smiled: "I have them all, just wait a moment."

In Eastern Sea, Zui Xian Weng withdrew his divine sense and contacted the Righteous Qi Alliance.

The Righteous Qi Alliance had abundant immortal materials in the inventory, Zui Xian Weng used his contribution points to exchange for some ice and snow path immortal materials.

Next, he sent these immortal materials into treasure yellow heaven, allowing Bai Ning Bing and Zui Xian Weng to complete the transaction.

After getting the immortal materials she wanted, Bai Ning Bing turned around and left treasure yellow heaven.

Central Continent's Little Immortal Xing Luo's divine sense was still lingering around: "It's such a huge pity."

She failed to obtain the immortal material she wanted.

Little Immortal Xing Luo was a lone immortal, she was a single person with only rank six cultivation level. She could not match Zui Xian Weng in wealth, not to mention the fact that he took out ice and snow path immortal materials that the seller requested.

"I'll continue looking around." Little Immortal Xing Luo was very disappointed but she did not want to give up, she continued to look around in treasure yellow heaven.

"What is this?" Not long after, she was shocked to find that a huge mountain appeared in treasure yellow heaven!

"Who put an entire mountain in here?" Sensing this situation, Little Immortal Xing Luo stared with wide eyes as this was the first time she had seen such a 'gigantic' transaction.

The appearance of the mountain caused a small commotion to occur.

Many divine senses came over and many Gu Immortal wills even gathered to observe the commotion.

"Who is so amazing to be able to sell an entire mountain?"

"It is not easy to do this, they will need deep earth path attainment."

"This mountain is quite good, it contains abundant moon path dao marks. But this large resource point is very valuable, who would sell it? Selling it in treasure yellow heaven will also incur a huge fee of immortal essence stones."

The discussions had just started when this mountain vanished instantly.

"Someone actually bought it!"

"It seems that the transaction was made beforehand."

"The mountain earlier seems to be Southern Border's Moon Bowl?"

It was indeed Southern Border's Moon Bowl.

Fang Yuan had left a batch of Gu Immortals in Southern Border, Eastern Sea and various areas.

After negotiating with Wu clan, Moon Bowl was sold by Wu clan, sent into the sovereign immortal aperture through treasure yellow heaven.

"Moon Bowl has arrived, catch it, catch it!"

"Good, good, move to the left, move a bit to the right."

Bam!

The earth shook slightly as Moon Bowl landed on the ground.

Immediately, a rockman Gu Immortal came forward and used a killer move, manipulating Moon Bowl's mountain roots to stab into the ground, turning it into a node of the earth vein.

The other variant human Gu Immortals were free for the moment, they watched while conversing.

"Did you hear? Shi Zong revived!"

"Not just Shi Zong, any Gu Immortals who died in the outside world were revived through Human Sea."

"Master has divine might, he is all-powerful! Reviving us Gu Immortals is nothing more than a piece of cake!"

"But we will lose all our cultivation level and need to start all over again."

"Hmph, there is only hope for the future if we are alive, so what if we become mortals? We just need to re-cultivate!"

"If only I can receive the missions for combat."

"Don't even think about it. Those Gu Immortals who are able to take those missions have strong battle strength, even though you have rank seven cultivation level, you have just advanced, your still lack sufficient Immortal Gu."

"That's right, we need to take one step at a time. Let's work hard and do these missions to elevate ourselves first."

While a portion of Fang Yuan's elite subordinates fought outside, the rest helped to manage the sovereign immortal aperture, they worked hard and contributed their blood and sweat.

Even though unexpected events constantly occurred in the sovereign immortal aperture, it was still orderly and well managed.

[1] Mala is the spicy and numbing flavor in Chinese cuisine, which is made from Sichuan peppercorn, chili pepper and various spices simmered with oil. Back

Chapter 2169: Shocking Find of Thieving Heaven's True Inheritance

Northern Plains.

A few rounds of an intense battle had just passed.

Yin Wu Que retreated constantly while pointing his finger, aiming at Hei Lou Lan.

Immortal killer move — Crescent Moon Thrust!

Ching!

At the next moment, there was the crisp sound of unsheathing blades as a translucent pale blue crescent moon shot out from the ground like a sword towards Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan was prepared against this, she jumped up at almost the same time, avoiding it.

Yin Wu Que's pupils contracted slightly, this move was very fast and ordinary Gu Immortals could not dodge it easily. But Hei Lou Lan succeeded in that, it showed that she had an exceptional investigative killer move.

"My method has only failed against Tian Xia Xin and Zhou Ye Zi. The former is a wisdom path Gu Immortal capable of deductions while the latter cultivates time path, he had an investigative method that could peer a few breaths into the future."

"To think that today, it would fail against this mysterious female immortal. Even though this person cultivates strength path, she is not to be underestimated!"

Thoughts flashed in Yin Wu Que's mind as he retreated at the same time.

Rumble!

Hei Lou Lan exerted strength as her body charged forward like a meteor, pushing aside the air in front of her, arriving before Yin Wu Que in a few breaths of time.

Yin Wu Que gritted his teeth, he raised both hands and used a killer move — Moon Rise.

Moonlight gushed out of his forehead as he started to float up, but before he got far, Hei Lou Lan's fist already landed.

Bam.

With a loud sound, Yin Wu Que was sent flying by Hei Lou Lan like a rubber ball.

His thin body was sent flying far away, he landed on the ground and bounced along the surface for tens of steps, causing a gorge to form in his path.

Raising his head again, Yin Wu Que's vision was filled with Hei Lou Lan's figure, as well as her fist!

Yin Wu Que's heart jumped.

The fist earlier caused considerable injuries to Yin Wu Que despite his defensive method.

He did not want to face another punch.

"You fell for it!" Yin Wu Que suddenly smiled, he stretched out five fingers and aimed at Hei Lou Lan.

Clang, clang, clang, clang, clang!

Instantly, five translucent light blue crescent moonblades shot out, they were created from nothing, targeting Hei Lou Lan who was at the center from all directions.

Hei Lou Lan's eyes shined with cold light, she did not dodge but attacked with her fist instead.

Yin Wu Que's smile froze on his face, he watched as this fist got larger and larger, before landing on his eye socket.

Boom!

Yin Wu Que was originally lying on the ground with his head raised, after taking this terrifying hit, his head was pushed down into the huge pit that was created below him.

Ground shook as rocks were sent flying.

The spectators, Wooden Statue Lord Wu Guang and Sincerity Immortal Chen Cheng, had twitching eyelids as they watched Yin Wu Que get punched, they could feel his pain from over there.

Yin Wu Que was sent crashing underground from this punch, he was tens of feet below the ground surface.

Dust clouds spread but Hei Lou Lan did not chase him, she retreated rapidly instead!

Clang clang clang...

An unceasing number of moonblades were produced and shot towards Hei Lou Lan in a frenzied state.

Hei Lou Lan had a calm expression as she continued to dodge. Her actions were simple and agile, most of the moonblades were evaded while some were shattered by her fists.

Yin Wu Que attacked desperately, he finally obtained some time to regain his footing.

He flew out of the deep pit, rising towards the sky.

Currently, he was covered in dust and one of his eye sockets had cracked, the eyelid was swollen and turning purple, the vision in his eye was extremely blurred, his gaze flickered with lingering fear.

"The two punches earlier almost made me unconscious. It was so dangerous! Thankfully, the moon has already risen successfully." Yin Wu Que let out a breath of air.

Earlier, moon qi appeared from the top of his head, it had already gathered into a waxing crescent moon hanging in the sky under broad daylight.

The moonblade killer move was still being used continuously as Hei Lou Lan dodged while diverting some attention to look at the waxing crescent moon in the sky.

"Earlier, the moonblades could only be formed from the ground, but now they can appear from thin air, is this the effect of the moon in the sky?" Hei Lou Lan thought rapidly.

As her thoughts collided, they sparked brightly: "But this amplification is not worth paying such a huge price, Yin Wu Que endured two punches from me in order to activate this crescent moon."

Hei Lou Lan was calm and composed internally.

Earlier, she took the initiative to attack, now, she focused on defense, her actions were meticulous and allowed her to advance or retreat at will.

Yin Wu Que was still using his moonblade killer move.

Crescent moonblades continued to form, the attack was unceasing, but Hei Lou Lan managed to defend herself stably and even had the chance to attack the crescent moon in the sky with her fists.

The waxing crescent moon suffered an impact from her punch, but it only shook slightly like the mirage in a desert.

"The crescent moon is getting larger?" Bright light flashed in Hei Lou Lan's eyes as she found out new information at this moment.

"So that's it." Hei Lou Lan had some sort of insight in her mind.

After she stopped moving back, she charged ahead instead, enduring the attacks of the crescent moonblades in order to attack Yin Wu Que.

Yin Wu Que's heart jumped: "This female immortal's combat instincts are too powerful, it seems that she has seen through my combat system!"

Yin Wu Que had an immortal opportunity in his earlier days, he inherited the inheritance of a certain Olden Antiquity moon path Gu Immortal great expert, he thus had a complete and stable combat system.

The waxing crescent moon was hanging in the sky, it amplified the various moon path killer moves of Yin Wu Que. At the same time, when Yin Wu Que's moon path killer moves get destroyed or countered, the lingering moon path dao marks would be absorbed by the waxing crescent moon, causing it to grow.

The waxing crescent moon would grow into a half moon, before becoming a full moon.

Once it becomes a full moon, Yin Wu Que's offense and defense would be amplified to the strongest state.

Because Hei Lou Lan had seen through this tactic, she started to use her strongest offenses.

Yin Wu Que knew from the start that he was not Hei Lou Lan's match at the moment, he had to choose a delaying tactic to retreat while blocking her offenses.

Hei Lou Lan engaged in a full frontal charge.

The two immortals chased and escaped respectively, they fought intensely, rocks were sent flying wherever they went, nobody in their path was spared.

Immortal killer move — Eight Directional Strength Fight!

Hei Lou Lan shouted as her body flickered, eight figures flew out and encircled Yin Wu Que.

Yin Wu Que was caught unguarded and got surrounded in the middle.

"Oh no!" Yin Wu Que's expression turned pale at once.

...

Fang Yuan's divine sense expanded and spread out in the sovereign immortal aperture.

The sovereign immortal aperture was simply too big, it was hard to inspect it entirely, he had to extend his divine sense for some time before he could see the entire landscape.

Strange events were still occurring in various places, but with Star Collection City controlling the situation, these events were mostly dealt with by Gu Immortals nearby.

There was no longer any disturbance, Fang Yuan focused on observing the earth vein this time.

Originally, the earth vein was already created but it was crude and simple. More than ten nodes formed into a line which made a circle around the five regions, connecting the first and the last nodes.

But after this period of development, although the current earth vein was still following a singular trail, there were many branches developing away from the main trail already, it was no longer as empty as before.

"After some time, the nodes at the end of these branches will be interlinked to form a second ring that is even larger. By then, the earth vein will have two different layers of connected lines."

In the current five regions, not only were Southern Border's super forces transacting with Fang Yuan, the Righteous Qi Alliance was also preparing for this matter under Qi Sea Ancestor's orders.

Two sea islands had already been sold to the sovereign immortal aperture through treasure yellow heaven, they were used as the earth vein nodes in Mini Eastern Sea.

Eastern Sea's righteous path forces were still kept in the dark.

They did not know that the buyer was Fang Yuan.

There was profit to earn, a large sum at that, thus they were very enthusiastic.

Fang Yuan had abundant capital now, even though he faced a lack of resources in his initial investment period, this problem no longer existed.

Fang Yuan had a vast number of immortal materials!

He used these immortal materials to pay for the sea islands and famous mountains.

The immortal materials from the first six layers of Crazed Demon Cave were chaotic and could not be transacted. But the seventh layer's dao marks were obtained by Fang Yuan through Thieves Den, they became pure rank nine immortal materials.

These rank nine immortal materials were all extraordinarily valuable, there was no way to quantitatively define the price. Thus, Fang Yuan's wealth also soared, giving him great confidence in transactions.

The truth was, if he did not use them to refine Gu, these rank nine immortal materials could only be sold to rank eight Gu Immortals or super forces.

Rank six or seven Gu Immortals were not able to even make use of rank nine immortal materials.

These immortal materials were too high-end, even many rank eight Gu Immortals did not have the capability to use them.

Only those super forces wanted to stock up on them.

After inspecting the earth vein and seeing nothing wrong, Fang Yuan retracted his divine sense after noting that the development was progressing well.

As his attention returned to the main world, Fang Yuan willed as Cooking Luck Pot shook slightly.

Fang Yuan started his luck inspection.

He saw that some changes had occurred to his silver light luck pillar.

The silver light pillar had become more condensed.

It was half the size of earlier, but the density was at least five times of before!

Be it the earth vein construction or Fang Yuan's own refinement path comprehension, they were reasons that caused the silver light pillar to become more condensed.

The three clouds representing Star Constellation, Spectral Soul, and Giant Sun were still at the top of the pillar of light, showing intentions to suppress and obstruct him.

But at the bottom of the silver light pillar, the original soil dust circulating around had already turned into a mound that covered the silver light pillar, it seemed like the foundational base of the pillar.

"Recently, I have been comprehending Paradise Earth's tomb, I gained some insight, I can now create my own Tomb Earth."

"Using Tomb Earth, I can make Gu Immortals revive! Even the Immortal Gu that they had when they were alive can be produced alongside the person."

"Looking at the luck phenomenon, if I can comprehend Northern Plains' Paradise Earth true inheritance, it will help me greatly too!"

"Huh?"

Right when Fang Yuan was thinking, his luck changed again.

He saw that above the silver light pillar, a dazzlingly bright star appeared between the three clouds.

This star was shining in a silver-white light, it penetrated the cloud layer and shined directly onto the surface of the silver light pillar. They were similar silver lights, they seemed like they would benefit the silver light pillar a lot.

"What is going on?" Fang Yuan's body shook: "So that's it! I understand now."

He gazed afar, through ten thousand li, looking at the central area of the intersection between the three great worlds.

A small world revealed itself over there, emitting the intense aura of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable.

It was Thieving Heaven's space!

It was very likely to contain one of Thieving Heaven's true inheritances!

Chapter 2170: Thieving Heaven Versus Limitless

Crash crash crash....

A series of brutal assaults hit Yin Wu Que, who was on the ground.

Yin Wu Que shielded his head with both arms, he was curled up into a ball, desperately activating his defensive killer move!

However, after a barrage of punches and kicks, his defensive method soon broke apart.

"I admit defeat, I admit defeat!" Yin Wu Que shouted loudly in panic and desperation.

"Fairy Black Moon, it's over, spare him." Wu Guang who was at the side came to urge her.

Hei Lou Lan was only wanting to spar and had no intention to kill, immediately, she stopped using her method.

She turned to Chen Cheng and asked: "Yin Wu Que has been defeated, who is the next opponent?"

While she was asking, two Gu Immortals flew over from the sky.

One female and one male immortal.

The male had a skinny body and a sharp face, he had bean-like eyes, he emitted rank seven light path aura.

The female immortal had the body of a young child, her eyes were watery and bright, her petite body was cute and delicate, she was a rank seven wood path Gu Immortal.

They were Liu tribe's Liu Chang and Liu Luo.

Chen Cheng and Wu Guang looked at each other, they did not speak.

Liu Luo was the first to ask: "What is happening here?"

As nobody answered her, Liu Luo quickly turned to Yin Wu Que.

Yin Wu Que was still lying on the ground, he received Wu Guang's treatment as he smiled bitterly: "This Fairy Black Moon came to challenge me, she has outstanding methods, I am not her match."

Liu Chang heard this and his eyes shined, he smiled and said: "Fairy Black Moon? May I have the honor of knowing your name? To think that a new outstanding figure would emerge in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world."

Liu Luo mocked Yin Wu Que: "Yin Wu Que, do you know the difficulties of a lone immortal now? Our Liu tribe invited you to be our external supreme elder, it is something that would benefit you. At least, after joining our tribe, if any Gu Immortal challenges you, it will incur the wrath of my Liu tribe!"

Yin Wu Que smiled bitterly and shook his head: "Thank you for the repeated offer, but I am used to being alone, I have no intention of joining any super force."

Liu Luo frowned: "Can you not see what's good for you?"

Ever since the fate war ended, in order to prepare against the five regions chaotic war, Longevity Heaven had ordered the various Huang Jin tribes to unify Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world. Many Gu Immortals were recruited into Huang Jin tribes, while many demonic immortals were killed as well.

At the other side, Hei Lou Lan showed no intention of answering Liu Chang's question.

She said to Chen Cheng: "Let's go."

"Hold on!" Liu Luo's sharp voice interrupted her, she looked at Hei Lou Lan: "You are very brazen, do you not know that Yin Wu Que is the target of our Liu tribe's recruitment? Now that you injured him, you want to leave so easily?"

"Sister." Liu Chang called out, feeling helpless internally.

Liu Luo had just gone from rank six to seven, with the rise in strength, her temperament was also more arrogant now.

If she was alone, she might not act like this, but with her brother Liu Chang here with her to rely on, Liu Luo showed a casual and carefree attitude.

But because Liu Chang doted on his sister, he did not chide her, he stared at Hei Lou Lan: "Fairy, why be in a rush to leave? Are you interested in joining our Liu tribe? If you can become Liu tribe's external supreme elder..."

"Shut your dog mouth." Hei Lou Lan replied plainly.

"What?" Liu Chang was stumped.

Liu Luo stared with wide eyes, she was filled with rage and shock: "How dare you! Bitch..."

Before she finished, Hei Lou Lan interrupted again: "Two dogs that block my way, bark once more and I will kill you."

Seeing that the situation was going out of control, Chen Cheng quickly came in to mediate the situation.

Liu Luo called out in a shrill voice: "Today's matter will not end like this, I want to see if..."

Boom!

Hei Lou Lan attacked fiercely, a strength path phantom appeared before Liu Luo abruptly, punching the latter's face and sending her flying.

"Sister!" Liu Chang was enraged, he was about to attack.

Boom, he was also sent flying by Hei Lou Lan.

Liu Chang was a famous rank seven expert of Northern Plains, his strength far exceeded Liu Luo, he quickly stabilized his footing and said: "You dare to attack us Gu Immortals of Liu tribe?"

Boom boom boom!

Eight strength path phantoms appeared around Hei Lou Lan, the dark capital strength tiger totem was also summoned, beating the Liu tribe siblings to a pulp.

"This, this, this..." Chen Cheng watched with a dumbfounded expression.

"It cannot be resolved amicably now." Wu Guang was tongue-tied, he smiled bitterly towards Yin Wu Que: "So Fairy Black Moon's temperament is like this, Brother Yin, it was really lucky that you managed to survive at her hands."

Yin Wu Que snorted: "If Fairy Black Moon really kills the Liu tribe siblings, do you think Liu tribe or Longevity Heaven will let us off?"

Wu Guang was dazed, he showed an unsightly expression.

"Are we going to take action to help the Liu tribe siblings?" Wu Guang asked helplessly.

Yin Wu Que gritted his teeth: "Do you want to hug Longevity Heaven's smelly feet? Ever since Giant Sun Immortal Venerable created the Imperial Court contest, the entirety of Northern Plains became his kingdom. For the last three hundred thousand years, have we, the lone cultivators of Northern Plains, not suffered enough?"

Most of the immortals knew about the truth behind the Imperial Court contest.

Northern Plains' lone immortals and demonic cultivators had a poor impression of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. Back then, Five Elements Grandmaster, who was still a lone cultivator, invaded Longevity Heaven, he was the proof of this mindset.

Longevity Heaven desired to rule Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world, but the difficulty was too high.

Many Gu Immortal experts did not want to submit to the Huang Jin tribes, they did not want to obey the words of these people they detested.

With the exception of two cases.

One was during the five regions chaotic war, when Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world faced great external pressure, these Gu Immortals would have no choice but to band together as one.

The second was if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable revives successfully, his invincible might would force all these demonic immortals and lone cultivators to submit to him.

The truth was, even in the five hundred years of Fang Yuan's previous life, Longevity Heaven managed to unify Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world because of Ma Hong Yun.

Ma Hong Yun had the power of Fortune Rivalling Heaven, he seemed to be someone who started from a humble origin, he was able to unite many lone and demonic immortals as a result. But he was in fact Longevity Heaven's chess piece, an arrangement of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

By relying on this, Longevity Heaven was able to unify Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world after the five regions chaotic war started.

But now, the five regions chaotic war had yet to start while Ma Hong Yun was killed by Fang Yuan, the difficulty for Longevity Heaven to unite Northern Plains was simply much harder.

"Fairy Black Moon, I will definitely find you in the future to repay the shame of today's defeat." Liu Chang brought Liu Luo away, they escaped in anger.

He was very strong but he could not display his strength.

Hei Lou Lan targeted Liu Luo constantly, it made Liu Chang hold many reservations, he could only take hits passively, it was a terrible feeling.

"They finally escaped." Chen Cheng let out a breath of air, he had been holding his breath in anxiety earlier.

"Hmph, they cannot escape. After I defeat the lone and demonic immortal experts, I will challenge these Huang Jin tribes, I will let the whole of Northern Plains know of my might." Hei Lou Lan smiled coldly.

Chen Cheng was feeling a headache, he did not expect his master to have such grand ambitions. not only did she want to defeat the lone and demonic immortals, she even wanted to challenge Northern Plains' overlords, the Huang Jin super tribes!

"Fairy, if you have such an ambition, I, Yin Wu Que, am willing to travel alongside you as your entourage." Yin Wu Que was standing with Wu Guang's help, he walked towards Hei Lou Lan.

"Oh?" Hei Lou Lan raised her brows.

Yin Wu Que smiled bitterly: "The truth is, if I do not travel with you, when Liu tribe's Gu Immortals come to find me, they will not let me off. I do not want to be a member of the Huang Jin tribe."

"Alright." Hei Lou Lan nodded: "Back then, Chu Du also wanted to challenge the Huang Jin tribes. We both cultivate strength path, how can I be inferior to him? Let's go together."

"I will come along too." Wu Guang said: "This is an interesting matter, I want to watch it with my own eyes."

Thus, Hei Lou Lan's group grew larger again.

Crazed Demon Cave, eighth layer.

Three hundred thousand years ago.

In the void, worlds were created and destroyed like bubbles.

Suddenly, chains appeared, making loud clanking sounds as they formed into a chain domain that intertwined in the surrounding area.

"I was actually discovered." Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was slightly surprised, having been forced to reveal himself.

Limitless Demon Venerable's will appeared: "Do stop, new venerable. The Space Door that you seek is not here."

As he spoke, countless chains shot out towards Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable from all directions.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable moved like lightning, traversing between the chains, he was agile like a fish in water.

"Limitless Demon Venerable's will?" Excitement shined in his eyes: "How do you know I am looking for Space Door? Are you saying that because you do not want me to destroy your arrangements in Crazed Demon Cave? You hid the ninth layer too deeply, I actually could not decipher it immediately, why don't you let me in and take a look, as long as Space Door is not there, I will take my leave!"

Limitless Demon Venerable's will said: "Thieving Heaven, even though I do not leave Crazed Demon Cave, I know many things about the current world. The current you cannot even control yourself, how can I allow you to enter the ninth layer?"

"Cannot control myself? Why can't I control myself?" Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable raised a brow: "I just want to go home, I just want to go back and see my friends and family, but all of you want to obstruct me!!"

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable spoke with increasing agitation.

Limitless Demon Venerable was silent, the chains attacked even more fiercely now.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable snorted coldly, he stopped moving far away, no longer dodging.

A blinding blue jewel-like light burst out with radiance, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable activated his killer move, the blue light faded, forming into a huge suit of armor around his body, turning him into a metallic giant.

The metallic giant was covered in electric sparks, it moved rapidly towards Limitless Demon Venerable's will.

The endless chains came to obstruct him but they were all pushed aside by the metallic giant.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable rode in the metallic giant and charged his way forward, forcing his way to the central area of the chain domain, grabbing onto Limitless Demon Venerable's will.

But at the next moment, Limitless Demon Venerable's will dissipated.

At almost the same time, another lump of Limitless' will appeared, saying calmly: "This is Crazed Demon Cave, my will can regenerate endlessly in here, there is a limitless supply of it."

"Is that so?" Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable smiled coldly: "Then have a taste of my methods."

Bam bam bam...

A shocking battle erupted at once.

Within the void, countless worlds were implicated, they were all destroyed in the process.

Limitless Demon Venerable's will had the territorial advantage, he was able to fight evenly with Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable initially. But as time went by, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was superior after all, he started to gain the upper hand.

Limitless Demon Venerable had died long ago, this was only his will controlling Crazed Demon Cave after all.

Chapter 2171: Four Venerables Repair The World

The lightning giant attacked, each action carried unparalleled lights.

Countless chains swayed and targeted Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable as they sealed and slashed.

The damage caused by the two venerables continued to spread out, the entire void was shaking intensely, it seemed to be unable to sustain the pressure.

One by one, small worlds were implicated, they were rapidly destroyed and unable to last a few breaths of time.

Within the lightning giant, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's expression became increasingly twisted, blood surged in his eyes as his aura became more vicious and wild.

"Take this move!" Thieving Heaven shouted as the lightning giant's mountain-like body stopped on the spot.

The surface of its body started to transform rapidly, with the crisp sound of clanking metal, cannons started to extend out of its body in all directions.

Boom—!

Thousands of cannons fired at once, countless rays of light pierced the void, a rainbow color of red, orange, yellow, green, blue, purple, and others dazzled the entire heaven and earth.

As light rays shot out and crossed a vast distance, they destroyed everything in their path, many chains that Limitless Demon Venerable's will controlled were easily decimated.

"This move actually comprises metal, wood, water, fire, earth, and other paths. Each color of the cannons represent a different path. Oh no!" Limitless Demon Venerable's will was shaken.

The defensive line that he had established was penetrated, exposing the two great worlds that he was protecting.

One world had rampaging wild beasts, the other was covered in lush greenery.

They were Savage Wilderness Great World and Green Lotus Great World.

Most of the cannons were blocked successfully but a hundred of them still shot towards the two great worlds mercilessly.

"What? These two worlds contain life?" Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was internally shocked.

He could see clearly, his twisted expression froze on his face, clarity returned to his eyes that had turned blood red.

Earlier when he explored the void, he saw that the small worlds were devoid of life, they were deathly silent.

Thus, he did not care about the destruction of these small worlds.

But Savage Wilderness Great World and Green Lotus Great World contained living beings, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable did not want to be a mass murderer.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable gritted his teeth, he used all his strength to control the lightning giant and turn the cannon in another direction.

All of the cannons narrowly avoided the two great worlds.

Guh.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable spat out a mouthful of blood.

By forcefully changing his attack direction, he had to endure the backlash of the killer move.

The lightning giant that had been powerful and unstoppable was no longer shining, it dimmed by a lot.

The battle of the two venerables came to a halt at this moment.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable breathed roughly while Limitless Demon Venerable's will was protected by countless chains, he fell into deep thought.

At the crucial moment, he saw the former's true nature.

"I can open the pathway and let you enter to take a look." A moment later, Limitless Demon Venerable's will said.

"What?" Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was surprised.

But he immediately understood the reason, blood traces were still lingering on Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's lips, with his relatively severe injuries, he could not heal them in the short period.

He chuckled: "Then what are we waiting for?"

Limitless Demon Venerable's will opened a path as he led Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable into the ninth layer of Crazed Demon Cave.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable first saw a large mountain that was black and white in color.

"This is the Book Mountain recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>?" Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable dispelled his lightning giant killer move, he expressed his surprise.

Limitless' will smiled: "Book Mountain is one of the cores, with it, this crazed demon ninth void formation can continue to grow. Each time a new genius Gu cultivator appears in the world, they would help with the progress of their respective path, Book Mountain will absorb the new knowledge and develop the crazed demon ninth void formation to continuously improve and develop."

"Initially, the eighth layer's void was very small, there were no worlds at all. But afterwards, as rule path, phantom path, and refinement path developed in the five regions, this place also continued to expand and grow."

"Small worlds first appeared, before they quickly increased in number. Reckless Savage Demon Venerable left behind Savage Wilderness Great World, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable created his Green Lotus Dao field, greatly promoting the growth of the crazed demon ninth void formation. In time, living beings will be created and destroyed alongside the small worlds, no longer limited to the current two great worlds."

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable went deeper, he started to see blocks of floating ice, they had various sizes and all sorts of strange shapes.

"This is the truthful floating ice? No wonder I did not find them when exploring the River of Time, so it was you who found and kept them here." Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable realized.

And finally, he arrived at the deepest part of Crazed Demon Cave.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable showed a downcast expression, he felt very disappointed: "Space Door is not here after all."

Limitless' will did not lie to him.

Limitless' will said: "Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, if you do not believe me, you can continue to look. Space Door is not here."

"How can I find Space Door? That is my only hope of returning home!" Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable inquired.

Limitless' will shook his head: "If I knew about it, why would I need to fight you earlier? Oh Thieving Heaven, please go back, what you seek is not here."

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was in a daze, he did not speak for some time.

"No... maybe, this is what I am looking for?" Suddenly, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable emitted a peculiar laugh.

His expression was twisted, his eyes were blood red, his tone and mannerism of speech had changed completely, his voice was hoarse as if this was another person speaking.

"Oh no!" Limitless' will had a change of expression too.

The thing he was worried about the most had still happened in the end.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable continued to speak in a hoarse voice: "If I am not wrong, hehehe, this is the place where the world boundary of the Gu cultivation world is at its thinnest. Oh Limitless Demon Venerable, your crazed demon ninth void formation is using this place to pierce through the world boundary and bring those things that are beyond the world to act as the raw materials. That is how the eighth layer developed these great and small worlds, right?"

"Say, if I were to break this boundary and leave the Gu cultivation world entirely, will I be able to find a way back?" Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable said that as his eyes widened, the aura of excitement and insanity grew more intensely on his body.

Limitless' will replied solemnly: "Impossible!"

"You are a Gu Venerable yourself, do you not know the power of those things beyond the world? You have already experienced their strength, haven't you?"

"How long do you think you can last outside?"

"The venerable is the strongest person in the world, but even if you can last a long time, you will reach your limit eventually."

"Can you be sure that you will coincidentally find your original world before you reach your limit?"

"You need to know, you are not the only otherworldly demon, the worlds outside of the Gu cultivation world are more than just your original world."

"But!" Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable raised his hands as he shouted: "But do you know? Do you know how much I want to return?!"

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable then lowered his head, his fingers stabbing into his hair as his eyes were hollow, he muttered: "Do you know how tough it has been for me?"

"When I was a mortal, I told myself that if I became a Gu Master, I will be able to find a way home."

"When I became a Gu Master, I told myself that after becoming a Gu Immortal, I will be able to find a way home."

"After becoming a Gu Immortal, I consoled myself again, if I become venerable, I will be able to go home."

"But now, I am already a venerable! And yet, I cannot find Space Door! Where is Space Door?"

"Even if I find Space Door, can it really let me return home?"

"Gu Venerables are the strongest! There is no road ahead of me anymore. Sometimes, I will dream of Space Door, I dreamed that I found Space Door but realized it was completely useless."

"Whenever I wake up from such a nightmare, I will be covered in cold sweat."

"I admit that I am afraid, I am afraid that I cannot find Space Door, I am afraid that the truth behind it will send me into utter despair."

"Can you understand my feelings?"

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's breathing became rougher, he looked at the deepest part of Crazed Demon Cave, the thinnest part of the world boundary.

He suddenly laughed, his eyes lit up as he said in a hoarse voice: "So let me take a risk now! I will pierce this world!"

"Stop it!!" Limitless' will shouted.

He was already prepared, he used his full strength to stop him.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was instantly trapped by the surrounding chains.

But at the next moment, another Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable appeared in front of him, he raised his arms high and slammed down fiercely.

Boom!

With a loud sound, the world boundary was broken, the most terrifying tribulation in the world descended!

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable went out of the broken hole immediately.

But Limitless' will no longer had the time to pursue him, he tried his best to seal the broken boundary.

But terrifying tribulations were spewing out of the hole, Limitless' chains could not resist them, they could not even get close.

After a few breaths of time, the hole expanded to twice of its original size.

"The situation is critical, if we do not mend this hole now, the entire world will be destroyed. Please lend me a hand!" Limitless' will shouted loudly.

Reckless Savage's will flew out of Savage Wilderness Great World, bringing with him countless fierce beasts.

Genesis Lotus' will flew out of Green Lotus Great World, bringing along countless trees and grasses.

The power of three venerables could only maintain the situation, they could not fix this hole!

The hole did not expand but the three venerables were already dead, just the power left behind by their main body could not salvage the situation.

As the three venerables' power weakened, their expressions turned unsightly.

"To think that the world is going to be destroyed." Genesis Lotus' will smiled bitterly.

Limitless' will sighed: "I should not have taken the risk to let him in."

"No." Reckless Savage's will said grimly: "In that situation, even if all three of us took action, we could not stop Thieving Heaven, after all, we cannot take his life. Even if we force him away several times, he can still come back and challenge us until our strength is depleted."

"This is all my fault, Limitless, release me, I can help you." Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable said regretfully.

One Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had left through the broken boundary, while another Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was still trapped by Limitless Demon Venerable's chains.

"You?" Genesis Lotus' will was surprised.

"Who is the one who left earlier?" Reckless Savage's will asked.

"That is Sha Xiao." Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable smiled bitterly: "He is my Dao Guardian. He is also..."

The situation was urgent, Limitless' will interrupted him, asking: "What plan do you have?"

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable said: "Do you know why fate Gu's control over otherworldly demons is limited? That is because every otherworldly demon who comes into this world will carry their original world's insignia. Those are otherworldly dao marks."

"Next, I will use the otherworldly space path dao marks on my body to create a subspace and block this hole. Using the opportunity, I want you all to use your full strength and quickly mend it!"

Without hesitation, Limitless' will retracted his chains: "Go ahead."

Chapter 2172: Demonization

Crazed Demon Cave, eighth layer.

Large and small worlds were rapidly fusing together, all sorts of calamities and tribulations were rampaging in the worlds.

The fighting between Gu Immortals was also extremely heated.

Weaklings would lose their lives from the shockwaves of clashes between experts, strong individuals were also unable to defend themselves in this huge chaotic battle, they were like small boats facing a tsunami, with slight carelessness, they would be overturned and face death.

"Weak, too weak."

"Who else can stop me?"

"Die!!!"

"Hahaha!"

Bu Tian Kong continued to provoke its enemies, it charged unhindered, nobody on the battlefield could stop it.

It was favored by the innate luck of Crazed Demon Cave to begin with, under the effect of endless learning, its attainment level rose sharply. Afterwards, it received Heavenly Court's help and gained Immortal Gu and killer moves, its strength rose explosively.

Nie Kuang Feng and Duan Hu were also like it, at this moment, the three of them were the strongest Gu Immortals shining in this battlefield.

"Vile beast, don't think you can act so arrogantly!" Fang Yuan's four rank eight subordinates surrounded rock monkey Bu Tian Kong.

Bu Tian Kong instantly felt pressure as it stretched out its tongue, licking its lips with excitement and cruelty shining in its eyes: "Very good, you have nice numbers. Who are you guys?"

"Lightning Lion!" Lightning Lion Warrior said as he activated a transformation path killer move, turning into the Lightning Lion Warrior that had a lion head and human body.

"Remember me, I am Dharma!" Dharma Lion Warrior also activated his transformation method, turning into a lion head and human body warrior.

"Steel Rush." Steel Rush Warrior turned into a rhino person.

"Frost Butterfly." Frost Butterfly Warrior shrank in size, becoming the size of an adult's fist, it had a human shape with butterfly wings and could let out powerful frost energy.

In Gu Immortal combat, individuals often fought alone.

But these four Gu Immortals cultivated transformation path, they did not have conflicting dao marks, furthermore, they were familiar with each other, they had all originated from Beast Calamity grotto-heaven.

They originally had rank seven cultivation level, but with Fang Yuan's help, they all became rank eight.

Immediately, the four warriors surrounded Bu Tian Kong, they fought intensely.

Their battle went on until the sky turned dark, as if they could go on until the sun and moon lost their luster.

Bu Tian Kong was encircled and its injuries intensified, but it was getting more ferocious in combat.

Fists, legs, head, body, knees, elbows, all of these body parts were Bu Tian Kong's weapons.

Fist shadows flashed as collisions occurred, Bu Tian Kong would send one person flying each time. But the four were transformation path experts, their bodies were tough and sturdy, even though they were sent flying, they would quickly return and maintain the encirclement, giving Bu Tian Kong huge pressure.

The battle of the five went from the sky to the ground, before going back to the sky again.

Everywhere they went, other Gu Immortals dodged with all their might.

"Awesome, awesome!"

"Again, again!"

Bu Tian Kong got more and more excited, it felt its mind becoming clearer as all sorts of inspiration of killer moves surged internally, the barriers that it felt before were starting to loosen.

It was one of the three luck children of Crazed Demon Cave's eighth layer, its talent and aptitude were superb and unmatched.

The strong external pressure were an opportunity to squeeze out even more of its potential in this situation.

The rock monkey got fiercer and fiercer, it was originally not proficient with Heavenly Court's killer moves, but now, it had already mastered them, it even fused the moves into its own combat style.

"This rock monkey is terrifying, even with the four of us working together, we cannot kill it." Lightning Lion and the rest were feeling worried.

Even though they were still encircling the rock monkey, they felt that they were trying to suppress a volcano.

The volcano was storing up strength at the moment, turning external pressure into its own driving force. Once it reached its limit, the volcano would erupt, the commotion would shock the world, it would retaliate with a fatal attack.

"Quick, kill him!"

"Make use of master's method, let the tribulations wear it down!"

The four immortals communicated in secret, their cooperation also got smoother.

All along, Fang Yuan's heaven envies heroic geniuses killer move had been exerting its effect.

The tribulations were used by him to target Bu Tian Kong, Nie Kuang Feng, and the rest.

Of course, most of the tribulations were a form of refinement path method to refine the various small worlds, and the conflicting dao marks between the great worlds.

Especially with the eruption of tribulations within and outside small worlds.

These explosions caused small worlds to be destroyed and completely fuse with the three great worlds.

During this process, Savage Wilderness Great World had the greatest gains.

However, there was a small world that acted independently, it was 'outstanding' among the small worlds, no matter how the tribulations attacked it, it remained unmoved.

It was Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space.

Ordinary small worlds were spherical bubbles, while Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space was cubic with sharp edges.

No matter what the tribulations did, it remained in its original shape.

Within Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's gaze was already on this true inheritance space of Thieving Heaven.

"Otherworldly Demon." He snorted, memories surfacing in his mind as his expression turned unpleasant.

Back then, Giant Sun became an Immortal Venerable, he went into Crazed Demon Cave's eighth layer and learned of the true details regarding the four venerables repairing the world.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had disregarded the entire Gu cultivation world for his selfish desire, he almost caused the world to be destroyed.

Even though he extracted his own otherworldly space path dao marks at the crucial moment to seal the gaping hole by creating a subspace, the crack was already created, it could not be mended fully.

The other three venerable wills gave it their all and paid a huge price.

Other than Limitless' will, Genesis Lotus' and Reckless Savage's wills had to fall into deep slumber afterwards.

Using the opportunity, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable got rid of Reckless Savage's will and took over the control of Savage Wilderness Great World.

"When Thieving Heaven left behind this true inheritance, other than to seal the hole he made, he had a deeper motive, that was to leave it for the crucial person three hundred thousand years later — Gu Yue Fang Yuan."

"However, I made my move in advance to dismantle a portion of the true inheritance, I obtained the killer move perfect pair and imitation Gu."

Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space paid a huge price to block the hole back then, it became flawed and was not intact anymore.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun thought about the situation.

"Since Thieving Heaven's true inheritance has appeared, with Fang Yuan's possession of self luck true inheritance, he can use luck inspection to find out that this is his fortuitous encounter."

"He will definitely go there."

"And Heavenly Court will send troops to stop him."

"The greatest enemy is still Heavenly Court!"

Heavenly Court had the initiative, they were maintaining their advantage. Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was a luck path cultivator, he could not match true experts of wisdom path in deductions.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun decided to watch Fang Yuan's conflict with Heavenly Court and try to reap the gains of their fight. The main thing was to deal a heavy blow to Heavenly Court!

Peak of Book Mountain.

Fairy Yu Xiu, Qin Ding Ling, and the rest were also looking at Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space.

"Thieving Heaven's space has appeared. Since it could block the hole back then, it would not be destroyed by the tribulations within this void. We need to deal with it quickly, it is becoming our obstruction." Fairy Yu Xiu said.

"Hmm?" Qin Ding Ling suddenly received important information, she quickly said: "Our informant in Yellow Earth Great World said that Fang Yuan has already gone to Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space. But Longevity Heaven is very quiet, they are not doing anything."

Fairy Yu Xiu was not surprised: "Of course he would go, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable left behind this true inheritance for him after all. As for Immortal Zombie Giant Sun who is in Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace, he will go there as well."

Saying so, Fairy Yu Xiu smiled: "Qin Ding Ling."

"Yes." Qin Ding Ling replied solemnly.

"Let's go. We will go find Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun." Fairy Yu Xiu stood up gradually.

Excitement flashed in Qin Ding Ling's eyes, she said hesitantly: "Don't we have to mind Limitless Demon Venerable's retaliative method anymore?"

"Don't worry, Thieving Heaven's space is not part of Limitless Demon Venerable's arrangements, he needs us to destroy it or have Fang Yuan inherit it so that it will disappear. This space is an obstruction to Limitless' derivation, he will be more than happy to see us destroy it." Fairy Yu Xiu answered.

Heavenly Court's troops moved out!

Divine Emperor City brought Fairy Yu Xiu, Qin Ding Ling, and others along as they departed from Book Mountain.

At the same time, Demon Judgment Board moved with Fairy Ming Hao and Gu Yue Fang Zheng inside, they also left the front lines.

Even though Green Lotus Great World was facing the attack of Longevity Heaven and Fang Yuan, because of Fairy Yu Xiu's earlier actions, Heavenly Court had many mutant Gu Immortals joining them like Bu Tian Kong, Nie Kuang Feng, and Duan Hu.

These Gu Immortals forced Yellow Earth Great World and Savage Wilderness Great World into a disadvantage.

Immortal killer move — Spiraling Green Leaf Blade!

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

Countless flying leaves moved like blades as they spiraled towards Nie Kuang Feng from all directions.

Nie Kuang Feng laughed wildly, its body moving agilely between the flying leaves, dodging while also directly charging past the blades that it could not avoid.

It turned into a tornado at times, the wind blades around it were very sharp and thin.

Xiao He Jian gritted his teeth, he watched as Nie Kuang Feng approached rapidly, feeling intense pressure in his mind.

He had already fought Nie Kuang Feng for several minutes now.

Even though heaven envies heroic geniuses could restrain Nie Kuang Feng, it could not kill him. Nie Kuang Feng had Heavenly Court's help and managed to recover quickly, it was now treating Xiao He Jian as its own prey.

"Die!" Nie Kuang Feng shouted.

"You fell for it!" At the crucial moment, two figures appeared beside Xiao He Jian.

One was a miniman Gu Immortal, Green Forest Great Sage, the other was Black Locust, the owner of Giant Locust grotto-heaven, who was also another wood path cultivator.

Xiao He Jian's killer move changed at once as the three immortals cooperated, their strength grew explosively.

Flying leaf blades turned into seeds that were planted on Nie Kuang Feng's body.

Countless vines started to grow from them, tying Nie Kuang Feng up tightly.

Nie Kuang Feng was a tornado to begin with but these vines were still capable of binding it, interrupting its immortal essence usage.

Thus, Nie Kuang Feng's killer moves could not be sustained for long, the immortal essence flow became unsteady and the power of the moves fell to rock bottom.

More and more vines appeared, growing longer and longer, they almost covered Nie Kuang Feng completely, leaving no gaps at all.

"Don't... force me." Nie Kuang Feng struggled but it was getting weaker.

"We finally caught this guy!" Black Locust was overjoyed.

The three wood path Gu Immortals looked at each other, showing expressions of joy.

Xiao He Jian was very happy now, because Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch lost to Nie Kuang Feng earlier, while he defeated the latter. Comparing the two, it allowed Xiao He Jian to suppress Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch.

But at this moment, Nie Kuang Feng's aura started to become quite peculiar and strange.

The vines had already turned into a huge ball, but Nie Kuang Feng's voice could still be heard from within: "I am going to demonize... every time I fall into a desperate predicament, I will demonize."

"I don't want to undergo demonization."

"Because once I demonize, I will lose my consciousness until I destroy and kill everyone and everything in the world that I am in!"

"But you guys forced me, you forced my hand..."

"Ahhhhhhh!"

Chapter 2173: Perish with the Wind!

"Ahhhhhhh!"

Nie Kuang Feng shouted loudly, the louder its voice, the stronger its aura, it soon reached a shocking and unprecedented level.

Boom!

With a loud sound, the vines were torn into countless pieces.

Nie Kuang Feng regained its freedom.

But currently, it was not a deep green tornado, it had turned into a reddish brown demonic wind.

Intense winds blew, it instantly crossed several thousand steps of distance, arriving before Green Forest Great Sage.

Green Forest Great Sage had already used his defensive killer move, but after the reddish brown demonic wind devoured him, his aura quickly weakened before completely dying after a few breaths of time.

The demonic wind stopped for a moment, it was like a shark that could smell blood as it charged towards Black Locust who was nearby.

"Be careful!" Xiao He Jian quickly moved to help.

But after a few rounds, the demonic wind still managed to kill Black Locust.

The demonic wind finally targeted Xiao He Jian.

Xiao He Jian could not match Nie Kuang Feng, he had to retreat as he fought.

After a few rounds of combat, his tiny face showed a grim expression, his forehead was covered in sweat.

The aura of defeat and death was getting denser.

Rumble!

Lightning tribulations continued to strike but Nie Kuang Feng did not care about them, it was terrifyingly strong.

Elsewhere.

"Stop!" Lu Wei Yin shouted.

But Bu Tian Kong's fist still landed, smashing Steel Rush Warrior's skull into mush.

Thereafter, Bu Tian Kong growled, Steel Rush Warrior's soul was shattered.

Steel Rush Warrior could not be more dead, his headless corpse fell from the sky like a broken rag doll.

Be it his body or immortal aperture, they were absorbed by the great world as nutrients.

"Who else?!" Bu Tian Kong raised its head and roared, it was overflowing with fighting spirit, rivaling the nine heavens and resounding in the world.

At this point, the four rank eight Gu Immortals attacking it were all dead, they were mercilessly killed in a horrific manner.

Lu Wei Yin sighed as he flew towards the rock monkey.

The rock monkey stared at him fiercely: "Are you the next one? Very good, I will kill you, even if you are Yellow Earth Great World's sage!"

Lu Wei Yin shook his head: "I am no sage. Bu Tian Kong, your killing intent is too overbearing."

Lu Wei Yin had to take action against Bu Tian Kong personally.

Bu Tian Kong killed too many Gu Immortals, if it was not stopped, the overall situation of this Gu Immortal battle would be affected.

Boom boom boom!

Lu Wei Yin and Bu Tian Kong exchanged blows.

This time, Bu Tian Kong was finally suppressed.

Even though it was strong and could kill many rank eight Gu Immortals, it was still not pseudo venerable level. In contrast, even though Lu Wei Yin lacked offense, his defense was firmly in the realm of pseudo venerable level.

Lu Wei Yin endured Bu Tian Kong's fierce attacks with much energy to spare.

"You are not a sage, yet you are so strong already?! Good, very good!"

"Come and attack me, try and kill me, I have not sensed any fatal killing intent against me for some time already."

"Why are you not attacking? Why do you only defend yourself?"

"Are your attacks so weak and useless? You are too disappointing!!"

The rock monkey continued to shout as it moved rapidly like lightning in the sky, its attacks were like furious lightning bolts from heaven, its power was rising endlessly.

But Lu Wei Yin got distracted.

Because he heard that Fang Yuan had already left for Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space at the center.

"Oh no!"

"Lord Fang Yuan, please stop."

"Even though that small world might contain Thieving Heaven's true inheritance, it will be targeted by Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven together."

"Heavenly Court has already sent their main troops, there are many Immortal Gu Houses and Gu Immortals. Longevity Heaven has also sent Calamity Luck Altar."

"Now is not the time for a climactic battle, if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable attacks Paradise Earth's tomb while you are away, what will we do?"

Lu Wei Yin transmitted time and again, but Fang Yuan did not even respond to it.

Lu Wei Yin gritted his teeth, his expression turning unsightly.

"No matter how strong Fang Yuan is, he is still just a pseudo venerable, he is not a true venerable."

"I need to help him!"

"If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable shows up and kills him, who will protect Paradise Earth's tomb, who will stall for the crucial time?"

While thinking of this, Lu Wei Yin's vision suddenly turned dark.

Bam.

At the next moment, rock monkey Bu Tian Kong's fist landed squarely on Lu Wei Yin's face.

"You dare to be distracted? You are looking down on me, you will pay a terrible price!" Bu Tian Kong shouted.

Bu Tian Kong flew towards Lu Wei Yin as they got closer again.

Lu Wei Yin was forced to retreat, he quickly used his killer move.

It started to rain.

Tribulation rain fell on Bu Tian Kong's body, greatly slowing it down while also corroding its defenses.

At the same time, Lu Wei Yin's killer move showed effect.

Yellowish brown dust started to appear below Bu Tian Kong, they moved around and gradually sealed it.

"Get lost, get lost!" Bu Tian Kong shouted, using killer moves in a frenzy, trying to sweep away all of the rain and dust surrounding it.

But the rain and dust gathered together increasingly, eventually sealing it entirely.

A lump of soil that trapped Bu Tian Kong fell from the sky, after landing on the ground, it turned into a huge soil mountain.

"Just stay put here." Lu Wei Yin immediately flew towards Thieving Heaven's space.

"No!"

"I won't give in, these things cannot hold me down!"

"Roar—!"

Bu Tian Kong shouted, its voice resounding like thunder as it reverberated in the battlefield.

With a loud sound, the mountain was shattered, dust clouds emerged, from within the broken rocks, it flew out again.

"What?" Lu Wei Yin was stunned.

Bu Tian Kong's performance was out of his expectation, how could it escape so quickly?

Bu Tian Kong resisted the tribulations while flying to catch up to Lu Wei Yin.

Boom!

The two exchanged killer moves again, while Lu Wei Yin was held back this time.

"This monkey's killer moves are getting stronger, so that's it." Lu Wei Yin understood at this moment.

The tribulations were aiding Bu Tian Kong all along, as long as it was not killed, it would continue to undergo tribulations and gain more dao marks, that was why Bu Tian Kong got increasingly stronger as it fought.

"I want this heaven... to no longer shroud my vision!" Bu Tian Kong shouted as it used a move that shot out a rainbow, sweeping away the dark clouds of the surrounding five hundred li.

"I want this earth... to no longer bury my heart!" Bu Tian Kong shouted as it stomped on the ground, mountains collapsed, as Lu Wei Yin, who had his defensive method broken through, watched in surprise.

Bu Tian Kong was already in a state of insanity, it found Fang Yuan who was not far away, it abandoned Lu Wei Yin and went for Fang Yuan instead!

"Be careful!" Lu Wei Yin quickly advised: "This monkey is not simple."

Fang Yuan did not turn around, it was as if he heard nothing, he only looked at the subspace in front of him.

Bu Tian Kong moved rapidly and seemingly teleported behind Fang Yuan.

"I want all life... to understand my intention! I want this sage... to perish with the wind!!" Bu Tian Kong shouted, activating the strongest killer move it had used in its life.

Winds, clouds, and thunder roared, the world changed colors at this moment!

"Hmm?" Fang Yuan turned around slightly, waving his hand lightly towards the back.

At the next moment, Bu Tian Kong fell like a comet, crossing the entire battlefield and slamming into several mountains.

After a chain of loud explosions, it created a huge gorge of several kilometers on the ground.

Finally, it lay on the ground, its eyes were wide open but it did not move at all.

It was dead.

The unceasing chaotic battles and heated battlefields turned silent at this moment.

Nie Kuang Feng, who was unstoppable and killing everything in its path, froze in its reddish brown demonic wind state.

Fang Yuan cast his glance upon it.

Nie Kuang Feng shuddered immediately.

At the next moment, endless fear filled its mind and body!

"I will die, I will die, I am going to die!!"

It went out of its demonized state, immediately gaining clarity.

"Escape!!"

It quickly flew away, ignoring its opponent, Xiao He Jian.

Xiao He Jian was heavily injured and was on the verge of death, he had no way to fight back, with just one attack, he would die.

He stared with a dumbfounded look as Nie Kuang Feng escaped from the battlefield in a crazed state.

Fang Yuan turned around again, looking at Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space with a calm expression.

He turned to look at Heavenly Court's army, Divine Emperor City and Demon Judgment Board were arriving soon.

He looked at the other side.

Longevity Heaven's Calamity Luck Altar shined with a golden aurora, it was arriving too.

A cold and ruthless light flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes for a moment, he turned into a white ray of light as he entered Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space.

"Charge, we will fight inside!" Fairy Yu Xiu immediately ordered.

Once Heavenly Court's Immortal Gu Houses arrived, they also entered Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space.

They could not use their full strength outside, if they went past the limit, they would face Limitless Demon Venerable's retaliative method.

At the same time, it was easier to destroy Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space from the inside.

Fang Yuan's vision changed rapidly, when he regained his sight, he was already in this true inheritance space.

Every true inheritance space that Thieving Heaven left behind could be considered an artificial secluded domain.

This was a strange space, it had warm lights but no mountains, rivers, wind, or land, it was completely empty.

But there were some peculiarities in here, there were black lines that extended everywhere, covering every inch of the space.

These lines were either thick or thin, they all gave off a terrifying aura that Fang Yuan felt fearful towards.

At the same time, he felt familiarity in this aura.

He quickly thought of the mysterious black fire in the blue dragon whale's grotto-heaven.

Even though Fang Yuan did not know what happened three hundred thousand years ago, after seeing this, he realized immediately: "It seems that this true inheritance space is going to collapse soon. I need to quickly comprehend the mysteries here and decipher where the true inheritance really is."

The last time he entered a true inheritance space of Thieving Heaven, he obtained ghostly concealment.

That time, Fang Yuan went in through open door Gu and close door Gu. At that time, the true inheritance space was very stable, it had many winds of assimilation tornadoes inside. Only an otherworldly demon could dispel the wind by touching them.

Because of that, Fang Yuan accidentally saved Feng Jiu Ge.

After all the tornadoes had vanished, Fang Yuan successfully obtained ghostly concealment, it was a smooth process.

But this space was different.

There were no tornadoes at all, if Thieving Heaven's true inheritance really existed here, it would be hidden deeply and would require deductions.

But Fang Yuan was not rushing to make deductions, he took out a formation from his immortal aperture and placed it within this space.

It was the five regional limit formation.

The five regional limit formation activated, five colored smoke spewed out.

In a few breaths of time, five colored smoke spread out in the surrounding ten li, it was so dense that one could not see their own fingers.

After Heavenly Court's troops entered Thieving Heaven's space, they went inside the five colored smoke and immediately felt suppressed.

"These are... the five region's regional walls?!"

Chapter 2174: I Became Handsome, I Became Stronger!

"Why are the five regional walls mixed together in here?!"

"Is this an arrangement of Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space?"

"No, this is Fang Yuan's five restriction profound light qi, he had modified it, it is as if the five regional walls are replicated." Fairy Yu Xiu quickly deduced.

Fang Yuan's five restriction profound light qi and five regional limit formation were exposed during the fate war, with these clues, it was not an issue for a wisdom path great expert like Fairy Yu Xiu to deduce.

Boom!

Fang Yuan suddenly appeared, his killer move landing on Demon Judgment Board.

Demon Judgment Board was instantly swept away deep into the dense fog.

"We cannot fight here, Fang Yuan has the sovereign immortal body, he is unrestricted!" Gu Yue Fang Zheng shouted.

"Originally, the five regional walls had disappeared completely, to think that Fang Yuan would reproduce them, it seems that he has been preparing for this battle for a long time." Fairy Ming Hao gritted her teeth before ordering: "Find the five regional limit formation and destroy it!"

Southern restriction purple-black miasma light qi, central restriction white-gold saint light qi, northern restriction jade licorice light qi, western restriction red raging flame light qi, and eastern restriction blue water light qi. They were all different now, having being elevated to a whole new level, they were already on par with the five regional walls that existed in the past.

Back then when Tao Zhu researched on the five regional walls, he created the methods of five regional limit formation and five restriction profound light qi.

Fang Yuan used the foundation of his life's research and made a breakthrough, he reached a height that Tao Zhu had never seen in his life.

Fang Yuan had the sovereign immortal body, he was completely unaffected in the five regional walls, other Gu Immortals, however, were restricted by the regional walls, no matter what Gu worms they used, they would have to face a backlash.

With this difference, Fang Yuan's advantage was too huge, Heavenly Court did not want to see this situation.

In the past, they would not be affected by central restriction white-gold saint light qi, but now was different, with the merging of the five regions and the rampage of qi tides, the entire world's aura has been unified, Gu Immortals were no longer differentiated by regions.

And this new combined aura of the five regions was not any of the previous five regional qi.

Thus, no matter which region the Gu Immortal came from, they would be suppressed within this five restriction profound light qi.

Boom boom boom!

Fang Yuan dealt a heavy blow to Divine Emperor City, causing this huge city's green surface layer of light to shake and tremble.

But Divine Emperor City was too huge, even Fang Yuan could not destroy it for now.

From Divine Emperor City, a female immortal flew out, she was a young lady with a beautiful appearance, it was Fairy Yu Xiu.

She surged with battle intent as she went to Fang Yuan: "Gu Yue Fang Yuan, do you dare to fight me?"

At this time, another Immortal Gu House arrived in Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space.

It was Longevity Heaven's Calamity Luck Altar.

Bing Sai Chuan's voice resounded from within: "Fang Yuan, why don't we join hands and dismantle this Divine Emperor City first!"

Fang Yuan smiled lightly and replied: "No, currently, Demon Judgment Board has been thrown into the five regional walls, while Divine Emperor City is too big and hard to send flying. Your side will stall Divine Emperor City while I will go and destroy Demon Judgment Board!"

"Fang Yuan..." Bing Sai Chuan wanted to urge him.

But Fang Yuan turned around and went into the five colored smoke without hesitation.

"Ignore him, our target is Divine Emperor City!" Within Calamity Luck Altar, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun sat at the main seat as he ordered.

"Yes, master!" Bing Sai Chuan immediately moved Calamity Luck Altar, which crashed towards Divine Emperor City like a comet.

Fairy Yu Xiu gritted her teeth, she had to defend it.

Lu Wei Yin also arrived at this moment.

"Lord Fang Yuan!" He only managed to see Fang Yuan's figure disappearing into the five colored smoke.

"Sigh!" Lu Wei Yin sighed deeply, he did not dare to enter the five colored smoke deeply, he had to communicate with Bing Sai Chuan and attack Divine Emperor City instead.

The five regional limit formation continued to function as five colored smoke poured out endlessly.

Within the dense smoke, Demon Judgment Board charged everywhere, trying to find the location of the formation. Outside the dense smoke, Divine Emperor City and Calamity Luck Altar fought intensely.

"Found it!" Inside Demon Judgment Board, Fairy Ming Hao's eyes suddenly opened.

She was a pseudo venerable level wisdom path great expert, her full strength was nothing short of extraordinary.

But this deduction also dealt heavy damage to her, after all, she was using wisdom path killer moves in the five regional walls.

"Good, if we destroy this formation, we will be ruining one of Fang Yuan's trump cards!" Gu Yue Fang Zheng flew with great morale, charging with Demon Judgment Board.

The five colored smoke became denser as Demon Judgment Board's luster became dimmer, Gu Yue Fang Zheng was sustaining a huge backlash, his face soon turned pale as blood oozed out of his mouth.

Boom boom boom!

Fang Yuan found them and used killer moves continuously with terrifying strength.

Demon Judgment Board was facing greater difficulty in defending itself, it moved precariously ahead.

"Ignore him, destroy the formation!" Fairy Ming Hao's child-like appearance was filled with boldness and determination.

Demon Judgment Board paused for a moment before shooting out a blood red beam of light.

The blood red light was thick and powerful, it landed on the formation with an extremely fast speed.

The surface of the five regional limit formation radiated with five colored lights, it shook slightly but did not collapse.

"How can this be?" Within Demon Judgment Board, Fang Zheng was very shocked.

He was clear of this move's power, even within the five regional walls, it should not be this weak.

Fairy Ming Hao understood the reason immediately, her pupils shrank slightly: "Fang Yuan invested a lot into this formation, it has at least eight rank eight Immortal Gu and the defense is high, we cannot destroy it in a short period of time!"

The five regional limit formation used Region and Limit as the cores originally, as well as a vast number of mortal Gu.

Afterwards, Fang Yuan added earth vein Immortal Gu, followed by Formation Spirit and Formation Flag.

During the fate war, these Immortal Gu were mostly rank seven.

But the current Fang Yuan was different, while recuperating, he did not just modify the five regional limit formation again by raising its defense, he even raised all of the Immortal Gu in this formation to rank eight.

His wealth was simply unimaginable!

The full powered attack of Demon Judgment Board could not even remove one layer of the five regional limit formation's defense. In fact, because they activated a powerful killer move, the backlash was even greater.

This famous rank eight Immortal Gu House was now covered in cracks, it was near the point of breaking apart.

"What should we do now?" Fang Zheng could not help but be flustered internally.

Fang Yuan was attacking outside and giving him huge pressure. Their goal of trying to destroy the five regional limit formation was also impossible now.

"I advise that we retreat!" Fang Zheng gritted his teeth, suggesting to Fairy Ming Hao.

Fairy Ming Hao nodded: "Fighting here is too unfavorable. But it is fine, destroying this formation was only one attempt, even if we fail, there is no consequence on the eventual outcome. Let's go!"

Fairy Ming Hao left Demon Judgment Board and opened her immortal aperture's entrance, storing this Immortal Gu House.

Next, in front of Fang Yuan's surprised gaze, she vanished on the spot!

Soon, Lu Wei Yin, who was fighting outside, transmitted to Fang Yuan that Fairy Ming Hao had suddenly appeared beside Fairy Yu Xiu, he also asked about the situation on Fang Yuan's end.

"The two pseudo venerables Ming Hao and Yu Xiu are able to teleport to each other instantly?" Fang Yuan guessed.

Fairy Ming Hao did not succeed in destroying his five regional limit formation, while Fang Yuan also failed to destroy Demon Judgment Board.

In essence, this was a draw, Fang Yuan might have a slight upper hand.

But the situation was still stuck in a deadlock.

"As long as the five regional limit formation is still functioning, five colored smoke will continue to spread and fill the entire true inheritance space."

"But this will take too long, neither Heavenly Court nor Longevity Heaven will want to stay in here until then."

Fang Yuan pondered rapidly.

The five regional limit formation was not a battlefield killer move, it could not restrain people, they could enter and exit freely.

It would take too long for the five colored smoke to fill Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space, during this period of time, Thieving Heaven's true inheritance might be discovered by someone, or the space might collapse because of the intense fights.

Fang Yuan flew out rapidly, leaving the five colored smoke, he went to the battlefield of Divine Emperor City and Calamity Luck Altar.

On one hand, he was wary of Heavenly Court's deduction ability, similar to his refinement path attainment, Heavenly Court's wisdom path attainment was a huge advantage for them. Fang Yuan had to restrain them from having the time to deduce the true inheritance's location.

On the other hand, Fang Yuan had to join the battle and make deductions in his mind as well.

Divine Emperor City floated in the sky while spreading green light, it was grand and imposing, remaining unmovable.

Calamity Luck Altar was like a golden comet, Bing Sai Chuan manipulated it to its limit, it flew around Divine Emperor City continuously, launching all sorts of attacks.

Between the two Immortal Gu Houses, four pseudo venerables, Fang Yuan, Lu Wei Yin, Ming Hao, and Yu Xiu were fighting.

The two sides were first evenly matched, but soon, Fang Yuan and Lu Wei Yin fell into a disadvantage.

Fairy Ming Hao and Fairy Yu Xiu were very powerful, they each had a mature combat system.

Fairy Ming Hao's flying stars seemed like a singular move but they were all consecutive moves. By repeatedly hitting the same target, Fang Yuan would have to endure increasing damage each time.

Fairy Yu Xiu's methods were also very profound, she used her attainment level to suppress others. It was hard for ordinary Gu Immortals to find a countermeasure.

Lu Wei Yin fell into a tough battle due to Fairy Yu Xiu's focus on him.

While Fang Yuan also had a taste of the power of Fairy Ming Hao's pride Gu.

Thoughts collided in Fang Yuan's mind with great issues, many powerful and complex killer moves could not be used, the risks were too great.

And most importantly, Ming Hao and Yu Xiu had incredibly well coordinated cooperation.

Their coordination was extraordinary, Fang Yuan had never seen anything like it before.

Because of this, while Fang Yuan and Lu Wei Yin worked together, they were suppressed by the two fairies.

"The cooperation of Yu Xiu and Ming Hao has produced a qualitative change, if I fought alone, I would have lost already!" Lu Wei Yin had a solemn mood.

The opponents were working together impeccably, their cooperation was simply not humanly possible, they gave off a natural feeling, as if it was only reasonable for them to work together this perfectly.

While Ming Hao and Yu Xiu fought against Fang Yuan and Lu Wei Yin, they even had time to help Divine Emperor City resist Calamity Luck Altar.

"Fang Yuan, you want Thieving Heaven's true inheritance?" Fairy Yu Xiu smiled: "Then you need to know that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had once been here and damaged Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space, he took out a portion of the true inheritance by force. Thankfully, you are allies, you can ask for it."

Fairy Yu Xiu easily tried to sow discord.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly as he said to Lu Wei Yin: "Go deal with Divine Emperor City, I will handle these two."

"Lord Fang Yuan, without me, if you fight alone..." Lu Wei Yin was hesitant.

Fang Yuan looked at him coldly: "Leave, you are hindering me."

Lu Wei Yin gritted his teeth as he flew away from Fang Yuan.

Seeing this change, Fairy Ming Hao and Yu Xiu saw the weakness in their enemies, they looked at each other before launching rapid attacks at Fang Yuan together.

Fang Yuan opened his immortal aperture's entrance and let out a young Gu Immortal.

Rank eight transformation path Gu Immortal Zhan Bu Du!

Immortal killer move — Incomplete Freedom Transformation!

The young man shouted as a blood red cape appeared on his back, fluttering with the wind.

"I became handsome, I became stronger!" Zhan Bu Du clenched his fist, staring at the two female immortals with a shining gaze filled with surging fighting spirit.

Chapter 2175: Giant Sun Takes Action

In Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space, the battle between two Immortal Gu Houses had been ongoing for some time.

It was very intense.

"Come fight!" Zhan Bu Du shouted as he descended like a ferocious dragon, charging towards the two Heavenly Court pseudo venerables, Yu Xiu and Ming Hao.

Yu Xiu and Ming Hao split up at once, retreating at the same time as they created a long distance.

Zhan Bu Du missed his target again, he snorted coldly with some anger internally.

He was one of Fang Yuan's clones, he cultivated transformation path and rose to rank eight, he had his own totem killer moves. But his own battle strength was still far from the peak of rank eight, he was not the match of experts like Qin Ding Ling or Wu Yong.

But once he used the killer move incomplete freedom transformation, he would instantly reach pseudo venerable battle strength!

Incomplete freedom transformation was not simple at all, it was extraordinary.

This transformation was made up of three moves: internal breathing green fish transformation, devouring blue leopard transformation, and thunder rush yellow bird transformation.

After Zhan Bu Du used incomplete freedom transformation, he gained the advantages of all three killer moves without any of their drawbacks.

He could move like lightning, shoot out lightning bolts, possess immense recovery and regeneration, and also the ability to devour all attacks.

Even though he was human, each action held divine strength that could intimidate demons or deities! He could directly suppress all immemorial desolate beasts or plants, he was basically a moving calamity that could fight heaven and earth, dominating all that were in his way!

Even Ming Hao and Yu Xiu did not dare to fight Zhan Bu Du head on, they engaged with him from a distance.

However, when their various killer moves got close to Zhan Bu Du, they would either be devoured or endured forcefully, before his regeneration took place and healed his body completely.

After a few rounds of combat, Ming Hao and Yu Xiu lost their enthusiasm to fight against Zhan Bu Du.

The enemy was too resilient but also very fast, thankfully, he lacked in the wisdom path aspect, while Yu Xiu and Ming Hao were experts in this.

Thus, they started to use wisdom path killer moves to weaken Zhan Bu Du, while deducing and preempting many of his attacks to dodge them.

It was very wise that Fang Yuan gave incomplete freedom transformation to Zhan Bu Du.

He was a pseudo venerable in the first place, using incomplete freedom transformation was quite wasteful, giving it to Zhan Bu Du would produce another pseudo venerable instantly.

Once Zhan Bu Du took action, the situation changed.

Fang Yuan and Zhan Bu Du worked together to deal with Ming Hao and Yu Xiu, they regained their footing as Heavenly Court lost the initiative, they went into a deadlock again.

Zhan Bu Du frowned deeply: "These two are extremely slippery and utilize their advantages well, I am unable to use my expertise against them. And their cooperation is simply too fluid, even though the main body and I have the closest of relationships, we are still not as well coordinated as them. It is likely because they are both wisdom path great experts!"

Rumble...

While moving around, both sides launched killer moves again, causing a beautiful display of fireworks to occur, the firepower was getting more intense.

Fang Yuan's main body was still showing a cold expression.

Ming Hao and Yu Xiu were also secretly scheming.

"From the start, Fang Yuan has not been using his full strength, he is making deductions while fighting! He wants to deduce the location of Thieving Heaven's true inheritance." Fairy Yu Xiu was very clear of her enemy's actions.

Fairy Ming Hao gritted her teeth: "He also has the Qi Sea clone, that is another pseudo venerable battle strength, if he is let out, this will get more troublesome. If we work together, we can resist the three of them for now, but this crafty Fang Yuan will definitely use the numbers to his advantage, he will ignore us and focus on Divine Emperor City!"

Heavenly Court actually knew about Qi Sea Ancestor's true identity.

As it turned out, Qin Ding Ling knew this secret some time ago but she did not expose him at that time.

During the pursuit battle against Fang Yuan, Heavenly Court did not know. But afterwards, Qin Ding Ling learned about the truth from Heavenly Court grotto-heaven.

After all, the Qi Sea clone was created in Heavenly Court, Heavenly Court's qi harvest fruit was used in the process!

Heavenly Court had existed for millions of years, it naturally had ways to find out.

Precisely because of that, when the Qi Sea clone used the name of the Righteous Qi Alliance and invited Heavenly Court to send Gu Immortals against Fang Yuan, Qin Ding Ling did not give an affirmative response.

Fairy Yu Xiu transmitted: "Qin Ding Ling is a passable leader of Heavenly Court, when Heavenly Court lacked a pseudo venerable battle strength, she controlled herself and caused Fang Yuan to be misled into thinking that the Qi Sea clone was not be exposed, thus not using him now. Right now, we are benefiting from that."

Fairy Ming Hao nodded secretly: "We can't kill Fang Yuan here, but we cannot let him obtain the Thieving Heaven true inheritance here, we need to try and destroy this true inheritance space from the inside!"

The battle intensified but the strange thing was that neither side truly treated the opponent as their opponent.

Fang Yuan was doing his best to make deductions, he was not using his full strength in battle.

Zhan Bu Du was sent out to restrain the two Heavenly Court pseudo venerables as well. After all, he could cooperate better with his clone compared to Lu Wei Yin.

Meanwhile, Heavenly Court focused on destroying Thieving Heaven's true inheritance.

As for Longevity Heaven.

Calamity Luck Altar had been finding trouble with Divine Emperor City, all sorts of killer moves were unleashed without restraint, not caring about this true inheritance space.

Evidently, regardless of what Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was after, he still had the intention to destroy this space so Fang Yuan could not gain anything!

Even though Longevity Heaven was allied with Fang Yuan, they were only doing so out of pressure from Heavenly Court.

They did not want to see Fang Yuan get any more help.

Especially when this help came from Thieving Heaven!

Divine Emperor City's green light continued to shine densely, defending it from any attacks no matter how fierce or intense they were.

Divine Emperor City was not only defending itself, it also had offenses!

Immortal killer move — Divine Bean Soldier!

Yellow bean soldiers charged ahead, green bean soldiers shot out arrows like rain, red bean soldiers self-detonated, black bean soldiers defended at the center. There were also blue and white bean soldiers mixed among them, having their own tasks.

Each time Lu Wei Yin attacked Divine Emperor City, he would face the encirclement of these divine bean soldiers.

Lu Wei Yin used his offensive killer moves and caused great losses to these divine bean soldiers, less than ten percent of them survived.

This result shocked Lu Wei Yin, despite him being specialized in defense, his offensive methods were also at the peak of rank eight, to think that he could not completely eliminate these divine bean soldiers.

The reason was because of Divine Emperor City's other move — Graft Wood.

This move could allow the divine bean soldiers to be connected together and share the damage they suffered. The bulk of the damage went to Divine Emperor City, while the divine bean soldiers bore the rest of the burden. Thus, these divine bean soldiers were very hard to kill in battle!

After Lu Wei Yin spent a long time to break out of the encirclement, when he approached Divine Emperor City, countless lightning bolts shot towards him.

It was immortal killer move — Myriad Life Spring Lightning!

Countless sparks that resembled dragons or snakes, as well as jade green lightning balls that exploded.

After they exploded, the remaining wood path dao marks would remain in the area and modify this battlefield gradually.

Thankfully, this was Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space and not the five regions, thus this move's power could not be fully displayed.

After Lu Wei Yin endured the lightning bolts and got closer, the jade lights around Divine Emperor City started to turn into spirals as they shot out painting path killer moves.

These painting figures had countless forms, like flowers, birds, fishes, or insects, they were extremely varied and gave Lu Wei Yin a huge problem.

"Painting path is very unique, my attacks cannot get rid of them, I can't conceal myself with my defensive methods either, this is a problem."

Painting path was kept as a secret by Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, this was Lu Wei Yin's first encounter with it, there was no helping it, he felt he was without options.

Lu Wei Yin was unable to break Divine Emperor City's defense, Calamity Luck Altar was similar.

Calamity Luck Altar was a rank eight luck path Immortal Gu House, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable created it personally, it displayed great might during the fate war, but right now, it could not do anything to Divine Emperor City.

The reason was that Divine Emperor City shot out rays of white light from time to time, Calamity Luck Altar had to dodge them each time without being careless.

This was human path killer move — Broken Homes and Dead Family!

This move countered Immortal Gu Houses, during the fate war, Immortal Gu House Chicken Dog Coop was only grazed by it and the entire Immortal Gu House broke apart without a single Gu Immortal inside surviving.

This was the human path offensive killer move that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable created, Calamity Luck Altar was restrained by it.

At once, Calamity Luck Altar could only guard the surroundings. This structure with three floors of round altars and multiple pillars holding it up, having white jade railings and shining aurora, was acting like an irritating fly that was moving around a person.

However, it was also not strange.

Calamity Luck Altar displayed great might earlier when fighting against Gu Immortals. The truth was, its most valuable method was the killer move calamity luck revolution. This move could turn all sorts of calamities and tribulations into becoming harmless to the immortal aperture, instead nourishing it accordingly. Longevity Heaven relied on Calamity Luck Altar to survive countless tribulations and grow over time.

That was the use of Calamity Luck Altar, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable left it in Longevity Heaven before dying for this reason as well.

Divine Emperor City, painting world.

Fang Di Chang and Shen Shang worked together to comprehend the mysteries within.

"There is a huge disturbance in the outside world, it is likely a huge battle! Divine Emperor City possesses the methods of Divine Bean Palace and Emperor City, now that these methods are used so frequently, it shows that the ones attacking Divine Emperor City are not weaklings." Shen Shang said.

This was a good thing for them.

The more these methods were used, the more they could observe and comprehend the wood path, painting path and human path profundities within.

"Is it my main body attacking Divine Emperor City now?" Fang Di Chang guessed: "Or maybe someone is trying to save the existences within growling beast painting world and qi howling painting world?"

Right at this time, Shen Shang's and Fang Di Chang's expressions changed, they stood up in shock as their gazes pierced through the room, towards the painting world's sky.

In the sky, golden aurora gathered into two giant hands.

These two hands shrouded heaven and earth, they were unimaginably big, the left hand grabbed qi howling painting world while the right hand grabbed growling beast painting world.

Genesis Lotus' will growled loudly, the power of painting path burst out to suppress the two giant hands.

Within Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space.

The battle was at the final critical moment, the entirety of Thieving Heaven's space was covered in black lines, at the brink of destruction.

Zhan Bu Du gritted his teeth, he felt anxious internally: "The main body has not deduced the true location yet, he might not make it in time!"

"The time is now!" Within Calamity Luck Altar, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun took a look at Fang Yuan before taking a step out.

At the next moment, he appeared on the battlefield.

Chapter 2176: Primordial Domain!

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable?!" Fang Yuan's pupils contracted, even though he had a guess already, he could not help but feel internally moved.

Golden light burst out in the battlefield, Divine Emperor City shook intensely as if something was breaking out from within.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun bellowed.

In the painting worlds, countless citizens looked up at the sky dumbstruck, they saw two hands flying in the sky, directly smashing two huge holes in the painting worlds!

The two hands flew out of Divine Emperor City unobstructed, disintegrating in the battlefield, revealing Demon Immortal Qi Jue and Mao Li Qiu.

"I was saved?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue was filled with surprise and joy.

"Master!" Mao Li Qiu saw Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and was choked with tears: "I knew you would come and save me, woof!"

Mao Li Qiu's body immediately shrunk, it became tiny and jumped into Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's arms.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun showed a doting smile as he petted Mao Li Qiu's head: "You are still the same, you bark like a dog when you are excited."

"Woof woof woof!" Mao Li Qiu looked up at its master and barked with tears flowing out of its eyes.

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable? He has already recovered to this degree." Fairy Ming Hao was shocked.

"Ignore him, use our full strength to stall Fang Yuan, we are about to destroy Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space!" Fairy Yu Xiu reminded.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, opening his immortal aperture's entrance.

Qi Sea Ancestor flew out.

Immortal killer move — Unlimited Qi Sea!

At once, vast qi surged, rushing towards him from all directions.

Ming Hao and Yu Xiu were intercepted by this move, while Fang Yuan used the chance to dive into the five colored smoke.

"It's here!" He finally found the location of Thieving Heaven's true inheritance.

The five colored smoke had reached it already.

Fang Yuan instantly went there and took away the remaining content of Thieving Heaven's true inheritance.

At almost the next moment, Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space collapsed.

"Quickly leave!" Lu Wei Yin and the rest quickly retreated.

After Fang Yuan withdrew the five regional limit formation and became the last person to leave, Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space vanished into thin air at almost the same time!

"He succeeded after all." Fairy Ming Hao sighed.

Fairy Yu Xiu smiled: "This true inheritance has been half devastated already, no need to worry, our goal has been achieved in this fight. Let's go! The crucial part starts now."

Fairy Yu Xiu stored Divine Emperor City, the two immortals vanished instantly.

Seeing this, Fang Yuan revealed an expression of contemplation.

"Lord Fang Yuan." Lu Wei Yin quickly gathered alongside Zhan Bu Du, Qi Sea Ancestor, and Fang Yuan.

At the other side, there was Calamity Luck Altar and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun!

Both sides did not talk, even though they were allies, they both knew about the dependability level of their alliance.

"Four pseudo venerable battle strengths..." Bing Sai Chuan, who was within Calamity Luck Altar, was tongue-tied, in just a short period, Fang Yuan's strength had grown to such a level.

Longevity Heaven's Gu Immortals were not fools, the moment Qi Sea Ancestor appeared, they realized he was Fang Yuan's clone.

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable..." Fang Yuan looked at Immortal Zombie Giant Sun as he squinted, maintaining silence.

Even though the other party was an immortal zombie now, he still had extraordinary strength and profound methods, the moment he took action, he broke into Divine Emperor City and saved Demon Immortal Qi Jue and Mao Li Qiu, who were sealed inside the painting worlds.

Right now, Mao Li Qiu was curled up in Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's arms, wagging its tail in joy, how could one even imagine that this was a proud legendary immemorial beast?

As for Demon Immortal Qi Jue, he stood at one side without much embarrassment, his expression was hesitant and suspicious.

He was saved by Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, but the moment he came out, he saw Longevity Heaven, Heavenly Court, and Fang Yuan in a three-way battle, after that, Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space got destroyed, what in the world was happening?

The scale of the battle was huge, the situation was complex, Demon Immortal Qi Jue could not process it immediately.

"Fang Yuan." Immortal Zombie Giant Sun nodded at Fang Yuan, taking the initiative to speak: "This is Heavenly Court's scheme."

Fang Yuan raised his brows: "Oh? How so?"

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun pointed at the place where Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space was destroyed: "According to what I know, Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space was added in much later, it was used to salvage the situation. Because it greatly affected Limitless Demon Venerable's derivation, its destruction is something that Limitless' will is happy to see."

"At the same time, Heavenly Court's Feng Ya is trying to deduce Limitless Demon Venerable's arrangements, she is also obstructed by this space. Now that it is destroyed, her progress will be smooth sailing."

"Earlier, when I deduced Limitless' arrangements, I had fought against her from afar, she is the strongest wisdom path expert among the three pseudo venerables. She has already come into contact with the other core of the ninth layer — Primordial Domain!"

"Heavenly Court came here to obstruct you from getting Thieving Heaven's true inheritance on the surface, but their true intention was to force me to take action by using the captives in Divine Emperor City as bait."

"Without my obstruction, seeing that Feng Ya has not shown up even now, it is likely that they have made a breakthrough there. Their advantage and initiative has grown even larger."

The moment Immortal Zombie Giant Sun finished his words, Fang Yuan's expression changed slightly.

The other immortals' pupils shrank, along with Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, they all turned towards the direction of Green Lotus Great World.

The immortals looked past a vast distance, seeing that at the center of Green Lotus Great World, a lump of phantom image appeared at the peak of Book Mountain.

This phantom image was pure white and humongous, it was far larger than even Book Mountain, having the shape of a ball, with the inner area shining dazzlingly with white light.

The immortals were all shaken.

Lu Wei Yin's expression turned ugly as he said: "Primordial Domain!"

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, chapter five, section thirty-six states —

Carefree Wisdom Heart was born, she was intelligent and witty, Ren Zu liked his eighth child a lot.

But at the same time, Ren Zu was vexed: "My mind shattered, what do I do? I cannot store more knowledge anymore. Sigh, it seems that only the two of you can help me now."

Thus, Carefree Wisdom Heart and Great Strength True Martial used their own minds to store up more knowledge.

They filled their minds with knowledge, before moving along with Ren Zu.

Ren Zu and his children started their third attempt.

Before they took a step, they would scatter ink text and knowledge, the text would describe their knowledge and form a small black path.

Ren Zu and his children walked on this small path.

But when they finished using their knowledge and reached the end of the ink text path, they did not see any signs of wisdom Gu.

Ren Zu's third attempt failed again.

Great Strength True Martial shrugged in disappointment: "What do we do now? We have already done our best, but our knowledge is still insufficient. We cannot hold any more knowledge in our minds."

Ren Zu sighed, he was also quite helpless.

At this time, hope Gu flew out: "Oh human, don't be disappointed, I am here."

Ren Zu was surprised: "How can you help me?"

Hope Gu answered: "Oh human, I can awaken your aperture[1]."

Hope allowed people to gain enlightenment (awaken their aperture).

Thus, hope Gu exerted effort to create an aperture for Ren Zu.

Humility Gu laughed: "Then let me help you as well, human. When you have humility, your capacity will be larger, you will be able to hold more things."

Thus, the aperture expanded in size.

Ren Zu obtained the aperture and felt very happy: "This place is really huge, I can store so much knowledge! This is wonderful."

Ren Zu and his children went to Book Mountain again, they refined their knowledge and searched for ink text.

Ren Zu stored a lot of knowledge into his aperture, even he did not know the quantity he took.

Ren Zu and his children set off on their fourth journey, they stepped on the ink text path and entered deep into Qian Kun Crystal Wall.

They went very deeply and searched many places, they changed directions countless times but still could not find wisdom Gu.

They had no choice but to return to Book Mountain.

This time, because the exploration took too long, the ink text path that they created when they set off was unable to endure the endless barrage of information, a large portion of it faded away.

Ren Zu found the inkman elder and asked: "Why can't we find wisdom Gu?"

The inkman elder replied: "Sometimes, when we inkmen explore the place, we would encounter wisdom Gu. But you three have searched the entire Qian Kun Crystal Wall but did not find wisdom Gu, it means that it is intentionally hiding from you, it does not want to meet you."

Carefree Wisdom Heart quickly asked: "Then where is wisdom Gu hiding at?"

The inkman elder pondered and said: "Oh humans, you have searched the entire Qian Kun Crystal Wall. If wisdom Gu is still inside here, it can only hide in one place. That place is called Primordial Domain, it is the most mysterious part of Qian Kun Crystal Wall."

"Qian Kun Crystal Wall has a record of everything that happens in the world, it contains infinite information. Primordial Domain contains the information of the world since creation, it also has the information of the ends of all living beings. It is both the starting point and the ending point. It has nothing, yet it comprises everything."

Great Strength True Martial was overjoyed: "We have not gone to Primordial Domain yet, oh inkman elder, tell us how to get into the Primordial Domain."

The inkman elder shook his head: "It is not that I do not want to help you, but we inkmen have also only heard of the location, we have never entered it. Oh humans, we inkmen admire you a lot. You possess knowledge that far surpasses us, thus, if you want to enter Primordial Domain, you need to rely on yourselves."

Ren Zu and his children had to make their own research.

Carefree Wisdom Heart had a find, she shouted joyfully: "I found it, I found it!"

"Oh daughter, what did you find, why are you so excited?" Ren Zu asked in curiosity.

Carefree Wisdom Heart opened both her palms: "On my right palm, I found right Gu. On my left palm, I found wrong Gu."

"These two Gu are born in your body, they are ordinary looking and are much less presentable than my authority Gu. What help can they give us?" Great Strength True Martial was very prideful, he spoke nonchalantly.

Carefree Wisdom Heart answered: "These two Gu allow us to differentiate and classify our knowledge. Look at our knowledge again, the truth is, much of it is right at this moment, but after some time, those pieces of information will be wrong. There is also much of it that is right when placed here, but wrong when placed there. I think that if we use the knowledge that is always right at all times and use it to make our text path, we will be able to reach Primordial Domain."

Ren Zu nodded: "Your words are quite logical. Let us try it."

But no matter how they looked, they could not find such knowledge.

Great Strength True Martial's strong Gu said proudly: "Oh humans, you are wasting your effort. Because in this world, there has only been strong and weak, there has never been right or wrong, thus, your actions are in vain, you cannot classify right and wrong."

[1] Awaken aperture in Chinese can also mean enlightenment/reach an understanding. Back

Chapter 2177: Venerable Invincibility

"Qian Kun Crystal Wall contains everything that happens in the world, all of the information comprises genuine events with no lies. Using right and wrong will not be able to differentiate them at all, because since they exist, or rather, since they existed, they are all logical information."

Carefree Wisdom Heart was criticized, but her eyes shined with bright light: "I get it, the existence of everyone in the world, regardless of right or wrong, is logical, because this is the true meaning of their existence. This is what true meaning is!"

"Be it information or knowledge, they are a type of expression of true meaning, a form of revelation. If we can grasp true meaning, not only can we explain what is right, we can also explain what is wrong, it can explain everything!"

"Let us search for it."

The three of them started to dig up true meaning from the vast sea of knowledge.

Great Strength True Martial was the first to get impatient, Ren Zu also lost his perseverance soon, but only Carefree Wisdom Heart remained calm and composed, her expression was serious and solemn.

After a long time, Great Strength True Martial pointed at Carefree Wisdom Heart, he gasped in shock: "Look, another Gu grew on your body!"

The newly born Gu was called serious Gu.

After Carefree Wisdom Heart obtained it, she became very happy: "With this Gu, I will be able to recognize true meaning more easily."

After a long time, Ren Zu pointed at Carefree Wisdom Heart as well: "Look, another Gu appeared on your body."

The second Gu was called learning Gu.

Carefree Wisdom Heart started to learn knowledge, she converted knowledge into things that she truly understood, she was no longer just storing them using memory Gu.

She started to understand more and more knowledge, soon, a third Gu appeared on her body.

The third Gu was called talent Gu.

"I found it, I found it!" One day, Carefree Wisdom Heart shouted with joy, with the help of self will Gu, learning Gu, and talent Gu, she finally found the true meaning of knowledge.

"Quickly tell us, what does true meaning look like?" Great Strength True Martial was very happy as he asked.

But Carefree Wisdom Heart shook her head: "The true meaning contained within will be lost if I try to convey it in words."

"Then write it out using ink text." Great Strength True Martial thought about it and suggested.

But Carefree Wisdom Heart shook her head again: "The meaning can only be understood, it cannot be passed down in text!"

Ren Zu waved his hand: "Forget it, since you possess true meaning now, let's head out immediately."

Carefree Wisdom Heart was filled with true meaning, they set off from Book Mountain as she scattered ink text on the ground, the path was much wider than before, it was also more sturdy.

Ren Zu and his children walked on the great path and arrived in Primordial Domain.

Within Primordial Domain, they met wisdom Gu.

Wisdom Gu was quite helpless, it had already hidden itself so deeply but Ren Zu still found it, self Gu managed to take a bite out of it in the end.

...

Crazed Demon Cave, eighth layer.

Center of Green Lotus Great World.

At the peak of Book Mountain, everyone was present.

Che Wei took the fifth seat, Qin Ding Ling took the fourth, Fairy Ming Hao took the third, Fairy Yu Xiu took the second, while Fairy Feng Ya took the main seat.

Fairy Feng Ya's hair was tied up in a bun, she was old but not wrinkled, she retained her beauty and elegance.

Her entire body was covered in a thin layer of dazzling light, it was the sign that she possessed talent Gu.

Currently, she was taking charge of the situation, exerting power in secret to force Primordial Domain to appear at the top of Book Mountain.

After Thieving Heaven's space was destroyed, Yu Xiu and Ming Hao brought all of their troops with them as they teleported back to Fairy Feng Ya's side.

Fairy Ming Hao sighed: "To think that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had such deep painting path attainment, he easily managed to save Mao Li Qiu."

Heavenly Court had indeed wanted to use Mao Li Qiu and the rest to force Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to take action.

Heavenly Court was clear of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's protective nature towards his descendants and kin.

But unexpectedly, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable managed to easily save the captives without issue.

"He is a former Immortal Venerable after all, this is nothing strange." Qin Ding Ling said: "Furthermore, our side benefited the most from this battle."

Fairy Yu Xiu was hesitant: "It is still unclear which side benefited the most. We expanded our advantage while Giant Sun Immortal Venerable took back Mao Li Qiu, and Fang Yuan also obtained the remainder of Thieving Heaven's true inheritance. For some reason, I am feeling quite uneasy."

Fairy Feng Ya looked at Primordial Domain in the sky as she said: "The situation is clear now, Giant Sun and Fang Yuan will send their troops against us. We will remain here and stay on the defense, as long as we can endure their attacks, we will grasp the key to this battle and return victorious, we will rebuild the glory of Heavenly Court! Everyone, do you have confidence in this?"

Hearing this, the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were riled up with great morale, they answered together.

"It was all thanks to Lady Feng Ya's planning that we have such a great advantage now!"

"We need to defend it at all cost! We cannot lose again."

"Even if we sacrifice our lives, there is no regret."

"In my opinion, even though there are many enemies, Giant Sun and Fang Yuan will not work together sincerely, they will be guarded against each other."

Yellow Earth Great World.

Lu Wei Yin looked at Fang Yuan and frowned deeply: "Primordial Domain has appeared, Heavenly Court's wisdom path attainment is truly incredible, we cannot wait any longer. The situation is really terrible."

Primordial Domain had already been exposed, but Heavenly Court only managed to get that far, they had not truly obtained it yet.

Even so, Heavenly Court's advantage was immense.

Because Primordial Domain was far more important and crucial than Book Mountain!

As long as a venerable entered Primordial Domain, they would regain their supreme attainment level and become a Dao Lord again. Whoever entered Primordial Domain first would turn the advantage into victory, they would be the eventual winner of this Crazed Demon Cave battle.

Not only that, after this, when the venerable who became a Dao Lord went back to the five regions, they would take control of the world's situation. Thus, they would likely become the winner of the five regions chaotic war, ending up as the new ruler of the world.

"Lord Fang Yuan, Heavenly Court is about to obtain Primordial Domain. We need to attack with full force, if we cannot stop Heavenly Court, we will experience defeat this time." Lu Wei Yin said with determination.

Originally, his tactic was to defend first and retaliate later, but now, they had no choice but to go on the offense.

"How do we use our full strength?" Fang Yuan asked.

Lu Wei Yin showed a conflicted expression immediately.

Heavenly Court had a clear wisdom path advantage.

Ever since the start of the Crazed Demon Cave battle, Heavenly Court had held the initiative and advantage at all times.

Heavenly Court's three pseudo venerables cultivated wisdom path, due to their planning and foresight, their advantage was not just maintained, it was even expanded.

Right now, Heavenly Court even managed to draw out the other core of the ninth layer, Primordial Domain. And more terrifyingly, they did not cause Limitless Demon Venerable's retaliative method to trigger.

This meant that Heavenly Court had already comprehended a lot of the ninth layer's profundity, they were able to avoid Limitless' method from activating.

All along, Fang Yuan did not see Limitless' will manifesting, it was likely that it had already been destroyed.

Lu Wei Yin sighed deeply in admiration: "Back then, Limitless Demon Venerable fought his way to Heavenly Court and forced Star Constellation's will to play a game of chess with him, they comprehended and deduced together, obtaining all sorts of heaven path research results that were secretly sent into Crazed Demon Cave for the derivation here."

"But at the same time, Heavenly Court's methods also infiltrated Crazed Demon Cave, when Heavenly Court managed to draw out Book Mountain from the ninth layer, I had already felt something amiss. Now that they are about to bring out Primordial Domain, I can see that their wisdom path attainment is truly unmatched."

"Now that Heavenly Court has the initiative and territorial advantage, we are all forced to attack them while they only need to defend."

"And the worst thing is that we cannot truly use our full strength!"

Fang Yuan nodded slightly: "That is also my worry. Heavenly Court is skilled in wisdom path, why would they not know that both of our sides are going to attack them desperately? But they still went ahead with this, it means that they are confident in stopping our attacks. And their confidence might likely stem from Crazed Demon Cave."

Heavenly Court was able to bring out Book Mountain earlier, they also took out Primordial Domain now without activating Limitless Demon Venerable's retaliation. One reason was their superb wisdom path method, the other was that Heavenly Court's infiltration of Crazed Demon Cave had lasted for over a million years, they had deep foundations.

Fang Yuan could clearly not reach that level of understanding, if he used his full strength, he would likely face Limitless' retaliative method.

This meant that Heavenly Court was making use of Limitless Demon Venerable!

"This is the problem with fighting wisdom path experts." Lu Wei Yin continued frowning, the truth was, he still had a deep worry internally but he could not express it.

That was Gu Yue Fang Yuan's strength.

Fang Yuan was a pseudo venerable indeed with outstanding strength, he was the strongest person in the world before the trip to Crazed Demon Cave.

But now?

He was facing Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!

The appearance of Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was a huge blow to Lu Wei Yin. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, who had yet to appear, also placed a huge pressure on him internally.

Could Fang Yuan fight against these two enemies?

The truth was, Lu Wei Yin had no confidence in him.

Venerables were invincible!

This was the truth of the world in the last few million years of human history.

Because Lu Wei Yin had no confidence, he made the plan earlier to defend first and retaliate later.

Fang Yuan might be able to defend against a venerable for some time, but only a venerable could defeat a venerable!

These were Lu Wei Yin's true thoughts.

At the same time, Fang Yuan's subordinates had the same mentality.

Even if these people idolized and admired him, they were not brazen enough to think that Fang Yuan could defeat a venerable.

Venerables were invincible!

Back then, during Primordial Origin's era, variant humans ruled the world, did they lack pseudo venerable battle strengths?

They had them, and the numbers were not few.

But they had never held any hope of defeating a venerable.

Indeed, Fang Yuan had unfathomable strength and was able to easily defeat other pseudo venerable Gu Immortals. But this was not strange, even though pseudo venerables surpassed the peak of rank eight, among themselves, their difference in strength could still be huge.

But if Fang Yuan had to fight against a venerable, nobody would think that he could win, they would only think of how long he could last.

"As long as Fang Yuan lasts until Lord Paradise Earth revives, we will win. But now, Heavenly Court is pressuring us to take action. If we fight now, we might not make it in time for Lord Paradise Earth's revival!" Lu Wei Yin felt like a stone was weighing down on his heart.

Fang Yuan looked at the Primordial Domain far away as he said expressionlessly: "The situation is as such, we have to attack forcefully. Let's follow our agreement with Longevity Heaven earlier and send out our subordinates."

Chapter 2178: Intense Battle

Crazed Demon Cave, eighth layer.

Primordial Domain's silhouette remained motionless in the sky, it was getting more vivid and condensed.

The fusion of Green Lotus Great World, Yellow Earth Great World, and Savage Wilderness Great World was also getting deeper, only a small part of the boundary walls remained to obstruct their connection.

All of the small worlds had already fused into the three great worlds, Savage Wilderness Great World gained the greatest benefits, they had the most people.

This was thanks to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's heaven and earth luck method, causing most of the small worlds to fall towards Savage Wilderness Great World.

Fang Yuan sent out almost all his Gu cultivators, charging towards Heavenly Court's Book Mountain.

Longevity Heaven also sent troops with surging might and morale.

Heavenly Court was already prepared against them, Duan Hu and Nie Kuang Feng led their troops as they defended on both sides.

"As long as it is not a sage, nobody is my match!" Nie Kuang Feng roared.

It swept around with a huge fierce wind, the entire battlefield was pressured with wind, creating a great commotion.

"The enemy is in front of us, we need to work together to obtain victory!" Xiao He Jian looked at Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, the latter nodded with a solemn expression.

In the earlier battle, these two variant human Gu Immortals had fought against Nie Kuang Feng and lost individually. Not only did many Gu Immortals die, Xiao He Jian and Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch were also heavily damaged, they barely survived.

This time, after recovering their strength entirely, they decided to face Nie Kuang Feng together, putting down their grudges and rivalry.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch waved his hands imposingly as frost qi shot out, shrouding Nie Kuang Feng and slowing its movement, reducing its speed.

Xiao He Jian shot out green leaf blades that moved from all directions, they had impressive power.

Nie Kuang Feng whipped up a strong wind, heaven and earth changed colors, the leaves and frost winds were scattered everywhere.

Immortal killer move — Extreme Ice Crystal Light Immortal Suppression Coffin!

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch gave a roar, his aura got completely concealed, not a single bit leaked out.

At the next moment, his entire body exploded and spread out into countless frost lights.

The frost lights shot out with extreme coldness! Everywhere they went, air would freeze into ice crystals before falling to the ground.

"Hmm?" Nie Kuang Feng was shocked, it tried to dodge but how could it avoid in time?

It was shot by countless crystal lights, sealed in the mountain-like ice coffin.

"The thicker the ice, the stronger the amplification of the crystal lights that land on me!" Nie Kuang Feng struggled desperately but could not escape, facing the pressure of death, it went into demonization.

Crack...

From the inside, cracks started to appear and spread around the ice coffin.

"Oh no , I can't trap it anymore." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch sensed the threat.

But at this point, Xiao He Jian's move was finally prepared.

Immortal killer move — Cut Grass!

Xiao He Jian's palms slashed down like blades, aiming at Nie Kuang Feng, who was stuck inside the ice coffin.

Immediately, two blades of leaves appeared and fell slowly, stabbing into the cracks between the ice and piercing Nie Kuang Feng's body.

Nie Kuang Feng's body instantly shook.

Xiao He Jian attacked without stopping, Nie Kuang Feng's body shook as the green tornado got weaker and thinner, its resistance also started to fall.

"I am willing to surrender..." Nie Kuang Feng said weakly.

"Our master has orders, we will not accept anyone's surrender!" Xiao He Jian replied coldly.

In the end, Nie Kuang Feng lost its life at the hands of Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian.

Once Nie Kuang Feng died, the mutant Gu Immortals were left without a leader, many were killed while the rest escaped in desperation.

Fang Yuan's army charged forward and reached the base of Book Mountain.

At the other end, Space Extremity and Desolate Extremity of Longevity Heaven's Eight Extremities worked together and killed Duan Hu.

The two armies arrived at the center of Green Lotus Great World.

Heavenly Court had only obtained Book Mountain recently, they only managed to set up their formation around it.

This formation was known as four-way star formation, it had four sub-formations in four different directions, defending Book Mountain tightly with no gaps present.

At the peak of Book Mountain, Fairy Feng Ya continued to use her killer move without stopping, drawing out Primordial Domain, which was in the sky.

The two armies discussed for a while before attacking the four sub-formations.

Mao Li Qiu led its group to attack the west formation.

Gai Mei led a group to attack the north formation.

Xiao He Jian led a group to attack the east formation.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch led a group to attack the south formation.

The remaining ones were led by Bing Sai Chuan and Lu Wei Yin, they firmly supported the four vanguard groups.

The moment Mao Li Qiu entered the formation, countless starlight specks shot down like a torrential rain with countless droplets.

Mao Li Qiu growled as it expanded and became much larger, its purple fur was smooth and thick, the starlight could not penetrate it.

It charged around in the sub-formation with other Gu Immortals following it, attacking, killing, and causing destruction.

"Vile beast, you are here to cause problems again. We will kill you this time!" The star formation shook as two Gu Immortals flew in.

Nine Spiritual Fairy and Prince Feng Xian.

Nine Spiritual Fairy turned into an immemorial desolate beast to block Mao Li Qiu. The transformed immemorial desolate beast was superior to the real immemorial desolate beast, Mao Li Qiu was soon suppressed, its energy was expended and its body was hurting.

Prince Feng Xian activated his fire path killer move, all sorts of birds rained down with flames, killing more than ten mutant Gu Immortals of Savage Wilderness Great World in one move.

Mao Li Qiu was unable to resist, it had to retreat.

Elsewhere, Gai Mei went up against Zhou Xiong Xin and Jun Shen Guang.

Zhou Xiong Xin activated information path killer move and attacked, while Jun Shen Guang turned into a ray of light to support him. They worked together in unison with one as the attacker and one as support.

Yellow Extremity Jiao Huo used a totem killer move and fought against Zhou Xiong Xin, they were evenly matched.

But Gai Mei, on the other hand, was shouting loudly, he was running around and dodging Jun Shen Guang's attacks.

"Quickly go, quickly go." Gai Mei grabbed onto Jiao Huo's shoulder and dragged him away, ignoring the latter's stare.

Longevity Heaven's two groups returned without result, Fang Yuan's two groups were even worse.

Xiao He Jian and Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch were trapped, they could not even retreat.

"These two immortals met with Heavenly Court's Che Wei and Wan Zi Hong, they are in great danger, quickly send help!" The reinforcement letter had already reached Lu Wei Yin.

Che Wei created weapon path, his methods were getting more mature, his status was only below Qin Ding Ling.

Wan Zi Hong was originally a demonic immortal of Western Desert, she was recruited by Heavenly Court. During the fate war, she displayed great abilities, and now that her Immortal Gu were fully with her, her battle strength returned to its peak, she was very powerful.

Bing Sai Chuan and Lu Wei Yin held an emergency meeting: "This four-way star formation is a star path formation, we cannot take it down by force. It is simply too hard with Heavenly Court's elites guarding all four areas. Lord Fang Yuan was able to destroy the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation with that thing, I am sure he can deal with this formation too."

Bing Sai Chuan was talking about the five regional limit formation.

Lu Wei Yin nodded and was about to speak when suddenly, a Gu Immortal came out of Yellow Earth Great World.

This female immortal had snow-white skin, her ears were like rabbit ears, her eyes were blood red, it was Lady White Rabbit.

Lady White Rabbit had become a genuine rank eight Gu Immortal with Fang Yuan's help.

Lu Wei Yin laughed and said to Bing Sai Chuan: "I've already asked Lord Fang Yuan for help, I wanted to borrow the five regional limit formation to break the formation using a formation. Lady White Rabbit, thank you for the hard work."

Lady White Rabbit smiled: "Of course I need to work hard for master, I'll even give up my life, this is nothing. But master did not pass me the five regional limit formation, he said that this formation does not have a specific target range, its effect takes too long and won't be effective. Thus, I brought other methods."

Bing Sai Chuan was curious: "Lord Fang Yuan's methods must be extraordinary, please allow me to have a look."

Thus, Lady White Rabbit took out several Immortal Gu Houses from her immortal aperture.

Rising Cloud City, Profound Frost House, Unbreakable Golden Fortress, Dragon Soul Dark Castle, Red River Pavilion, Red Heavenly Altar, Scarlet Palace!

A total of seven Immortal Gu Houses which were all at rank eight.

Bing Sai Chuan was completely dumbstruck.

"Master said that he could only create these few Immortal Gu Houses in the short period of time. He has already given orders, we will charge with these Immortal Gu Houses as the vanguard." Lady White Rabbit said.

It turned out that ever since Fang Yuan entered Crazed Demon Cave and collected a vast amount of immortal materials, he had ordered the time path clone He Chun Qiu to use Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool to refine Immortal Gu.

After all sorts of rank eight Immortal Gu were created, he started assembling Immortal Gu Houses.

Fang Yuan did not intend to construct Immortal Gu Houses originally, they were not very useful to him.

But after entering the eighth layer, he could not fight with his full strength here, he made preparations to arm his subordinates instead.

He had no time indeed

These Immortal Gu Houses were all modified on the basis of Cloud City, Dark Flow Giant City, Profound Ice House, Unbreakable Iron Fortress, Blood River Chariot, Nightmare Castle, Green Wave Pavilion, Weaving Cocoon Manor, Golden Altar and other Immortal Gu Houses.

Strictly speaking, these were considered only partial innovations.

But against Heavenly Court, even with three wisdom path pseudo venerables, they could not easily decipher and break them, they needed to spend time on deductions.

That was enough!

Lu Wei Yin became very happy, he distributed the Immortal Gu Houses and charged through into the formation, saving Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian.

Afterwards, the seven rank eight Immortal Gu Houses swept through the battlefield, breaking two more sub-formations.

The two groups gathered towards Book Mountain.

At the peak of Book Mountain, Fairy Feng Ya's eyes were shut as she used her method. Ming Hao and Yu Xiu were taking charge of the situation.

Seeing so many Immortal Gu Houses, Fairy Yu Xiu had a grim expression: "Fang Yuan is so rich and has terrifying refinement path methods. It seems he intends to progress in refinement path!"

"Thankfully, his wisdom path is inferior to us, these Immortal Gu Houses are all not new, they have an origin that we can trace." Fairy Ming Hao said as she used her killer move.

Human path killer move — Humble Reciprocation!

Book Mountain shook as countless killer moves were unleashed like fireworks.

In the sky, Primordial Domain surfaced with rumbling tribulation clouds, calamities and tribulations were unceasing.

On the battlefield, countless killer moves filled the vision, surging like sea waves that crashed down in all directions.

Against such an endless tide of killer moves, Fang Yuan's subordinates hid inside the Immortal Gu Houses, moving against the waves.

Longevity Heaven had many Gu Immortals but they could not all enter Calamity Luck Altar.

Thus, Bing Sai Chuan took out five Immortal Gu Houses.

Wide Building Harem Palace, Internal Delight Harem Palace, Red Bean Harem Palace, Lovesick Harem Palace, Young Peach Harem Palace.

They were the five palaces that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable placed in the five regions when he was alive, they were all rank eight.

The foundation of an Immortal Venerable was displayed in full view!

"My lifetime accumulation cannot even rival Fang Yuan, he seems to have an overflowing number of rank eight Immortal Gu. Is he trying to become venerable through refinement path?" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun looked at the battlefield as he thought.

Fang Yuan was observing the battlefield as well while comprehending Thieving Heaven's true inheritance.

This Thieving Heaven true inheritance contained imitation Gu and the killer move perfect pair originally, but Fang Yuan only obtained the rest.

But this remaining portion was very important to Fang Yuan.

The true inheritance content was about refinement path, it talked about how Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable created a fake Qian Kun Crystal Wall in his time, how he created fake Immortal Gu and so on.

"Other than the four aspects of refinement path that I summarized earlier, there is also this aspect!"

"Refining fake Gu..."

"Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable left this true inheritance to me with deep intentions."

Chapter 2179: Battle of Book Mountain

Book Mountain was surrounded in the two colors of black and white, Gu Immortals fought intensely as they could be seen everywhere.

Immortal killer move — Great Qi Cloud Explosion!

Demon Immortal Qi Jue stretched out his finger and pointed consecutively.

Instantly, the air in front of him surged and gathered into a lump.

Several hundred white qi comets shot out at once, blocking the attacks of Book Mountain.

Fairy Ming Hao had been using Book Mountain to unleash the killer move humble reciprocation. Relying on this terrifying move, she was able to suppress the forces of Fang Yuan and Longevity Heaven.

These killer moves were all recorded in Book Mountain, there were a variety of them, this was a human path killer move in essence but the released attacks had the power of their original paths.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue faced offense with offense, after destroying the current wave of attacks, he sighed and retreated.

After he was saved by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, he did not interact with Longevity Heaven or Fang Yuan, he moved on his own and quickly learned about the current situation.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue also did not want to see Heavenly Court obtain Primordial Domain.

He wanted to enter Primordial Domain, in fact, to raise his qi path attainment level to supreme grandmaster, how could he allow others to snatch it first?

Demon Immortal Qi Jue was alone and could not take down Heavenly Court. But with Fang Yuan and Longevity Heaven working against the colossal force, he would not be Demon Immortal Qi Jue if he did not make use of this opportunity.

"To think that attacking Book Mountain is so dangerous, I can't even reach the middle of the mountain." Demon Immortal Qi Jue frowned.

When he was suppressed by Divine Emperor City, he lost many of his qi path dao marks. Furthermore, the secluded domain of heaven and earth that he relied on, Xi Land, had only about thirty percent left after the pursuit battle against Fang Yuan.

Bubble bubble...

As if a tsunami had struck, another wave of attacks swept down from the top of the mountain like a waterfall.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue had no choice but to retreat again.

"Charge, charge up!" A rank eight Immortal Gu House went past him, completely ignoring Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

That was the rank eight Immortal Gu House that Fang Yuan created, Unbreakable Golden Fortress.

The Gu Immortals in the Unbreakable Golden Fortress saw Demon Immortal Qi Jue but did not pay any attention to him. When Demon Immortal Qi Jue first appeared, he was quite the hot topic, but seeing that he had attacked Book Mountain too, Fang Yuan's subordinates also learned of Demon Immortal Qi Jue's stance.

Seeing Unbreakable Golden Fortress charge up and resisting the endless wave of killer moves, Demon Immortal Qi Jue could not help but show some envy in his eyes.

In this battle, Immortal Gu Houses were simply too important.

They provided the Gu Immortals strong defense, otherwise, as just a single person, how could he advance while resisting endless tribulations and killer moves?

Unbreakable Golden Fortress reached the middle of the mountain, in the fireworks of killer moves around it, there was a bloody shadow that flashed by.

At the next moment, the huge bloody shadow arrived, showing itself.

This was a huge red tombstone with text characters moving around it, it had a dense aura of blood path, this was Demon Judgment Board!

"Don't think of moving further!" Within Demon Judgment Board, Gu Yue Fang Zheng spoke.

Bam.

With a loud sound, the two Immortal Gu Houses crashed into each other.

Unbreakable Golden Fortress' advancement was forcefully halted.

Demon Judgment Board shot out blood red light that resembled a beam, it hit Unbreakable Golden Fortress.

Unbreakable Golden Fortress raised its defense and blocked the blood red light, but it was still forced down from the middle of the mountain by an unstoppable force.

Even though Unbreakable Golden Fortress was a rank eight Immortal Gu House, it was still far from Demon Judgment Board, which was a peak creation.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng breathed roughly.

Heavenly Court had few Immortal Gu Houses.

Even including Divine Emperor City, Heaven Overseeing Tower, and Divine Emperor City, they only had six.

Right now, these six Immortal Gu Houses were used to defend themselves, dealing with the Immortal Gu Houses that attacked them.

Over on Longevity Heaven's end, Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace did not move out, but Calamity Luck Altar and the five Harem Palaces totaled to six, they were equally numbered with Heavenly Court's Immortal Gu Houses.

While Fang Yuan suddenly brought out seven Immortal Gu Houses!

This was out of their expectations.

They had originally thought that Fang Yuan would reconstruct Dragon Palace or Myriad Year Flying Warship, but to think that he would start over and bring out seven Immortal Gu Houses like Unbreakable Golden Fortress.

So be it if he made new ones, but these Immortal Gu Houses were all rank eight.

Seven rank eight Immortal Gu Houses gave Heavenly Court an immense pressure in guarding themselves.

Heavenly Court only had around half the Immortal Gu Houses of their enemies, while Longevity Heaven's Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace and Fang Yuan's Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress had yet to join the battle, this made the hearts of Heavenly Court Gu Immortals sink.

Under Fang Zheng's control, Demon Judgment Board went around to force back the invading Immortal Gu Houses, attempting to maintain their defensive circle.

"The enemies are very strong, we can maintain the situation now with Divine Emperor City, Heaven Overseeing Tower, and myself as support. But if this goes on, we will not last long."

Gu Yue Fang Zheng's expression was pale, he understood this internally.

He felt like he was reaching his limit already.

The intensity of the battle was too high.

Demon Judgment Board not only had to go around to fight against the many Immortal Gu Houses, it also had to resist the bombardment of killer moves and tribulations.

The expenditure of immortal essence was shocking even for Fang Zheng.

Demon Judgment Board's damage level was also increasingly severe. Back then in Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space, Demon Judgment Board had already been heavily hit by Fang Yuan, it had already been repaired earlier. Now, its current damage was newly created.

If Fang Zheng was alone, he might have already lost control of the situation. Thankfully, Demon Judgment Board had the wills of the previous Demon Judgment Board Lords, these wills were helping him to rapidly repair the Immortal Gu House.

"Since when did our Heavenly Court's foundation lose to others?" At the peak of Book Mountain, Fairy Ming Hao maintained the killer move humble reciprocation while sighing to herself.

In Heavenly Court's case, the situation was quite bad. Even though Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals fought desperately to defend themselves, the defensive line was already wavering, the Immortal Gu Houses might break through at any moment and arrive at the peak.

At the peak of Book Mountain, Fairy Feng Ya was still using her full strength to use the killer move and try to obtain Primordial Domain, she could not be interrupted.

Fairy Ming Hao and Yu Xiu looked at each other, the latter waved her hand: "Go."

A tiger roar and crane cry resounded in the battlefield.

Two legendary immemorial beasts, Shabi Ninety-five and Ruan Dan, charged down the mountain.

Even though Heavenly Court did not have any more Immortal Gu Houses, they had two legendary immemorial desolate beasts. Immemorial desolate beasts had tough bodies, legendary immemorial desolate beasts were even tougher.

Shabi Ninety-five and Ruan Dan charged towards Rising Cloud City from the left and right, ignoring all the killer moves and tribulations above them.

Rising Cloud City was controlled by Fairy Miao Yin, she was about to charge into the battlefield when two legendary immemorial beasts pincer attacked her.

Fairy Miao Yin quickly used her killer move, Rising Cloud City spewed out endless cloud qi to push the Immortal Gu House upwards rapidly.

But Ruan Dan flapped its wings and flew above Rising Cloud City, activating a killer move and slashing with the crane leg, shattering the roof of Rising Cloud City and destroying countless mortal Gu.

Bam.

At the next moment, Shabi Ninety-five charged fiercely and knocked Rising Cloud City over, causing it to roll down the mountain.

Fairy Miao Yin's figure staggered, she wanted to control Rising Cloud City to ascend again but it did not respond to her, her immortal essence was instilled without getting any response.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue was to the left, upon seeing this, he immediately flew over.

He gave a cry, Xi Land's silhouette appeared above his head.

Immortal killer move — Xi Xi!

Xi Land erupted with immense attraction force, absorbing the qi ring around the surface of Rising Cloud City into Xi Land.

After getting released, Rising Cloud City immediately regained freedom.

"Thanks!" Fairy Miao Yin thanked and was about to move the Immortal Gu House back into the battlefield when she suddenly heard Fang Yuan's orders.

Fairy Miao Yin was stunned.

But she reacted quickly and brought the other Gu Immortals out of Rising Cloud City.

"Lord Qi Jue, my master ordered me to gift this Rising Cloud City to you!" Fairy Miao Yin said.

"What?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue was stunned before laughing heartily: "Fang Yuan is truly generous, I will receive it with thanks."

Demon Immortal Qi Jue did not stand on ceremony, he entered Rising Cloud City, it flew up and attacked the mountain again.

At the middle of the mountain, Shabi Ninety-five and Ruan Dan worked together and pushed down Dragon Soul Dark Castle.

Lady White Rabbit led the immortals inside Dragon Soul Dark Castle, she did not charge anymore, instead, returning to the base of the mountain to join up with Fairy Miao Yin.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue finally reached the middle of the mountain, he saw Shabi Ninety-five and his eyes lit up: "Good beast, I lack a steed myself."

Demon Immortal Qi Jue kept Rising Cloud City and only attacked Shabi Ninety-five.

The two fought for a few rounds, Shabi Ninety-five soon fell into a disadvantage, it started requesting for help.

This legendary immemorial beast cultivated qi path, it was completely countered by Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

"Don't fear, I am here!" Ruan Dan came over to help, it spat out a bright red pill.

"What path is this?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue sensed the mysterious aura of the pill, he did not dare to be careless, he brought out Rising Cloud City and went inside.

Boom!

The pill landed on Rising Cloud City and self-detonated, the intense shock wave spread out everywhere, a corner of Rising Cloud City was destroyed in the process.

Even though pill path was not specialized in offense, it was still a new path that Rising Cloud City could not guard against.

"Hahaha, Ninety-five, you owe me a favor!" Ruan Dan laughed proudly.

Shabi Ninety-five pouted and was about to answer when its expression suddenly changed: "Be careful!"

Ruan Dan's heart shook as it quickly jumped.

But the mysterious enemy was even faster.

"Can you escape?" Hearing the voice, Ruan Dan felt like its long neck was grabbed by a tiny hand.

Compared to its mountain-like body, the normal human-sized hand was definitely tiny.

But Ruan Dan felt a shudder when this hand touched its neck, it screamed in a shrill voice.

Because it twisted its neck and saw a young man wearing a red cape, standing on its back.

It was none other than Fang Yuan's transformation path clone, Zhan Bu Du!

At this moment, he had already used incomplete freedom transformation killer move, his battle strength rose to pseudo venerable level.

"Wait." Ruan Dan screamed, but Zhan Bu Du snickered and exerted strength.

At the next moment.

Boom!

An intense explosion resounded like thunder.

Book Mountain shook, black and white rocks were sent flying.

At the next moment, a huge pit appeared on the ground.

Ruan Dan was beaten unconscious by Zhan Bu Du, its body was motionlessly embedded into Book Mountain, its mouth opened as blood flowed out.

But soon, a bright light flashed on Ruan Dan's body.

Its injuries healed quickly, it regained its consciousness.

"Thankfully, I have my killer move, life-saving recovery pill!" Ruan Dan woke up and wanted to struggle.

But Zhan Bu Du's fist was already raised.

Bam bam bam...

With a series of punches, Zhan Bu Du slammed down on Ruan Dan's head each time, causing the whole of Book Mountain to shake. Only until he smashed Ruan Dan's skull completely and brain matter flowed out did he stop attacking.

Chapter 2180: Qi Sea Versus Yu Xiu

Against Zhan Bu Du, the great legendary immemorial beast Ruan Dan was completely unable to put up a fight.

But at the next moment, a bright light flashed on Ruan Dan's corpse again.

Immortal killer move — Life-Saving Recovery Pill!

With the effect of the killer move, Ruan Dan's smashed skull started to heal, it was soon revived.

"Pill path..." Zhan Bu Du also showed a look of surprise.

Ruan Dan's healing killer move was formidable, it could actually revive it from that state.

Even with Zhan Bu Du's pseudo venerable battle strength, he could not easily get around it. After all, even the main body did not understand pill path.

"Since I cannot unravel it, so be it, I want to see how many times you can revive!" Zhan Bu Du showed a ruthless expression.

Boom boom boom.

He punched time and again, each punch landed heavily on Ruan Dan, killing it on the spot.

The poor Ruan Dan had just revived and did not react in time before its skull was smashed again.

Immortal killer move — Life-saving Recovery Pill.

A few breaths of time later, the recovery method activated again.

But this time, the killer move's shining light became much dimmer.

"Persevere, Ruan Dan, I will save you!" Shabi Ninety-five shouted, rushing from another area to help out.

Even though it constantly argued with Ruan Dan normally, the two of them had a close friendship. Especially after major battles like the fate war, their camaraderie had already improved greatly.

Even if this was Zhan Bu Du, Shabi Ninety-five did not care about anything else, it wanted to save its friend.

"Hmph, trying to leave? Do you think I am not here?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue shouted in anger as he used a killer move that landed on Shabi Ninety-five's back.

Shabi Ninety-five suffered a heavy blow, it growled in pain and fell from the sky.

Seeing that Ruan Dan died at Zhan Bu Du's hands again, at the peak of Book Mountain, Fairy Ming Hao's frown became deeper.

Zhan Bu Du was an opponent that gave the three fairies, Feng Ya, Ming Hao, and Yu Xiu a huge headache.

He had terrifying strength and overwhelming defense, together with the abilities of internal breathing green fish transformation, devouring blue leopard transformation, and thunder rush yellow bird transformation, Zhan Bu Du had no weaknesses at all, the three immortals did not know how to deal with him.

If this were a normal battle, the three immortals could rapidly move and attack him from a distance, restraining and weakening him.

But now, Heavenly Court had to defend Book Mountain.

This was a defensive battle.

And the worst nightmare for a defensive battle was someone like Zhan Bu Du. If he managed to charge unhindered and went beyond the defensive line, it would be trouble.

But the three immortals had discussed it already, they had a plan against Zhan Bu Du.

Immediately, Fairy Ming Hao willed and transmitted some words to Genesis Lotus' will inside Divine Emperor City.

At the next moment, a jade light spiral appeared on the surface of Divine Emperor City.

From within the spiral, a giant flew out from the center.

The giant wore golden green armor, its left hand held a shield, its right hand held a spear, it was bursting with vitality and life force, its aura was immense.

The giant recited —

A hundred thousand years of unending hatred,

Killing the enemy with a shattered body.

Awakening once more in Divine Emperor City,

Qing Chou exists under the karma divine tree.

It was the legendary immemorial desolate beast — Qing Chou.

During the pursuit battle against Fang Yuan, Qing Chou killed Spectral Soul, but it was also completely blown to bits by Spectral Soul's self-detonation, reduced to countless pieces of flesh.

Divine Emperor City retrieved these pieces of flesh and revived Qing Chou again.

The current Qing Chou was no longer in its initial form of turtle shell, tiger claws, dragon tail, snake neck, bat wings, and human head. It was now a completely armored and equipped warrior.

Qing Chou arrived before Zhan Bu Du and its towering body slammed down like a mountain, its spear pierced the air as winds blew intensely, as if a giant dragon had struck.

"Come!" Zhan Bu Du did not retreat but moved ahead, his figure flashed and appeared at Qing Chou's forehead immediately.

Zhan Bu Du punched fiercely, hitting Qing Chou's helmet.

With an intense sound, a huge force caused Qing Chou to move backwards, its colossal body landed on the middle section of the mountain, causing Book Mountain and its surroundings to tremor.

Zhan Bu Du flew down and rained a flurry of fists, the attacks were intense and unceasing.

If Qing Chou let the punches land without obstruction, it would end up like Ruan Dan.

At the crucial moment, a giant tree formed above Qing Chou's head, absorbing the force of Zhan Bu Du's punches.

Immortal killer move — Karma Divine Tree!

At the next moment, the divine tree shook as countless fists shot out from between the leaves.

It was Zhan Bu Du's earlier wave of attacks.

This move had once caused trouble to Spectral Soul, Zhan Bu Du also felt troubled, he was forced back by the fists.

Qing Chou took the chance to stand up as Zhan Bu Du floated in the air, resisting Fairy Ming Hao's humble reciprocation killer move while regaining his footing.

Qing Chou roared and took large strides forward, it arrived before Zhan Bu Du with two steps, waving its long spear to attack him.

Rumble!

Two figures continued to fight intensely, they exchanged blows and caused the entire place to tremor, their offenses caused a huge commotion.

"I get it now, so this was Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's objective. Qing Chou has been completely subdued by Divine Emperor City, it is now the general of the divine bean soldiers. This is the strongest divine bean soldier!" Zhan Bu Du had a realization.

A few rounds later, he gained the upper hand again.

Qing Chou was not an ordinary legendary immemorial beast, but Zhan Bu Du was currently using incomplete freedom transformation!

He had genuine pseudo venerable battle strength, Qing Chou could not win.

Heavenly Court also did not expect a win, they only wanted to stall for time.

It was like how Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable invited Fang Yuan in order to stall for time as well.

As long as time passed and Heavenly Court obtained Primordial Domain, their advantage would be expanded, they would be able to claim victory!

Immortal killer move — Unlimited Qi Sea.

A figure suddenly appeared, carrying with him an endless sea of qi that surged together, shrouding the rays of the sun.

It was Qi Sea Ancestor!

Seeing that Zhan Bu Du was obstructed, Qi Sea Ancestor immediately chose another direction to attack the mountain.

At the peak of the mountain, Fairy Yu Xiu sighed as she was forced to take action, she left the mountain and fought against Qi Sea Ancestor.

Qi Sea versus Yu Xiu!

One was a qi path pseudo venerable, the other was a wisdom path pseudo venerable.

The former attacked fiercely, wanting to devastate Heavenly Court, but the latter was resolved to defend this base even at the cost of her life.

Qi Sea Ancestor attacked grandly with incredible attacks, qi tides swept the area, accompanied by pillars of white qi that shot out at times.

Fairy Yu Xiu however, was graceful and elegant, she moved agilely and dodged the endless wave of attacks while activating all sorts of wisdom path killer moves.

She had an exceptional combat system which used her attainment level to suppress others, it was extraordinary and even Immortal Zombie Giant Sun would be affected by this move.

But her enemy was Qi Sea Ancestor.

Qi Sea Ancestor was the clone of Fang Yuan, he shared attainment levels with the main body!

Fairy Yu Xiu tried many times with no success, for Fang Yuan, it was not hard to resist her attacks.

Fang Yuan was a master in dream path, space path, metal path, wind path, cloud path, lightning path, information path, light path, and sound path.

He was a grandmaster in blood path, strength path, star path, dark path, formation path, soul path, sword path, human path, wood path, food path, phantom path, luck path, ice and snow path.

He was a great grandmaster in theft path, transformation path, rule path, qi path, fire path, wisdom path, water path, earth path, poison path.

He was even a quasi-supreme grandmaster in refinement path, time path, and enslavement path!

With such attainment levels, how could Fairy Yu Xiu suppress him?

Fairy Yu Xiu had no choice, she had to use other methods against Qi Sea Ancestor.

Fairy Yu Xiu was unable to display the power of her combat system, but thankfully, she was familiar with Qi Sea Ancestor's methods.

Even though Qi Sea Ancestor had Primordial Origin's true inheritance, he obviously could not use those killer moves against Heavenly Court. As for other killer moves like heavenly astral cloth robe, yin-yang great killer hands, unlimited qi sea, and others, they were all used many times and were known to everyone.

"Let me help you!" Lu Wei Yin flew over, assisting Qi Sea Ancestor.

Fairy Yu Xiu used her strongest killer move to suppress Lu Wei Yin through attainment levels, effectively weakening him.

But Qi Sea Ancestor gained a greater advantage with his help, managing to approach Book Mountain.

At this time, Calamity Luck Altar burst out with a golden light.

The golden light surrounded Book Mountain and spread around the battlefield like vines. Wherever the golden light went, tribulations would transform and target the peak of Book Mountain instead.

And Book Mountain was also shaking intensely from the infiltration of the golden light.

Fairy Ming Hao's body shook unsteadily, her face turned pale as her pupils shrank: "This must be Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's doing! To think that he managed to counter humble reciprocation after it was only used for a second time!"

She gritted her teeth, even though she was unwilling, she had no choice but to withdraw humble reciprocation killer move.

If it continued, she would lose her life.

Earlier, when Fang Yuan and Lu Wei Yin first entered Yellow Earth Great World and led their army to attack Book Mountain, Fairy Ming Hao had stopped them using humble reciprocation.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was exceptionally talented, he thought of a way to counter this move in such a short time and successfully dealt with it now.

Without the endless tribulations obstructing them, Longevity Heaven's immortals had a clear path now, many of them cheered loudly in the Immortal Gu Houses as they attacked from all directions.

Fairy Ming Hao gritted her teeth, Fairy Feng Ya could not take action against them now, while Fairy Yu Xiu was fighting outside, in this situation, they had to rely on her.

Immortal killer move — People's United Hearts.

Immortal killer move — Hope of the People.

Immortal killer move — Heroes Among People.

The scene during the fate war was displayed again.

Light spread out towards the Heavenly Court immortals, causing their strength to rise sharply!

But this was not enough.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals and Immortal Gu Houses were just too few in quantity.

"Then awaken."

"Friends from Heavenly Court, our comrades!"

"The people of the five regions and two heavens need you, Heavenly Court needs you now!!"

Fairy Ming Hao shouted loudly.

From the northwest direction of Book Mountain, an immortal graveyard radiated with countless rays of bright light.

From the light, two figures walked out.

One was an old man with a benevolent countenance, his brows were particularly peculiar, they were like two exquisite dark brown roots that extended down from his forehead to his chest.

The other was a middle-aged man with a very robust physique, his face and muscles seemed to be made from brass as they let out cold metallic luster.

"I heard the call." The old Gu Immortal, Duke Mei, squinted and said.

"Where are the enemies?" The middle aged Gu Immortal Duke Tong looked beyond a vast distance, locking his eyes on Calamity Luck Altar.

Chapter 2181: Duke Mei, Duke Tong

Crucial information regarding the battle entered the minds of Duke Mei and Duke Tong.

At the moment when they saw the battlefield themselves, they also learned of the current situation.

Duke Mei sighed: "Duke Long..."

Back then, when he first saw Duke Long, the latter still had black hair and was a youngster.

The moment Duke Long joined Heavenly Court, he met with Duke Mei.

Even though Duke Mei was a senior, he quickly greeted in return: "Friend, you are a Dao Guardian, the happiness of all living beings is resting on your shoulders."

Duke Long replied solemnly: "I will do my best for the world, even if I have to sacrifice my life, there is no regret!"

Time passed, when Duke Mei reawakened in the five regions, Duke Long had already died ahead of him.

"Duke Long, you died a good death, throughout your life, you did not turn on the promise you made from the start." Duke Mei said with deep emotions, before flying forward: "And now, it is our turn."

Within Calamity Luck Altar, Bing Sai Chuan's eyes shined with bright light: "The immortal graveyard... so it was nearby all along, Heavenly Court has brilliant methods after all, we could not find it even with repeated investigations."

Be it Longevity Heaven or Fang Yuan, they had already confirmed the information of the immortal graveyard. They had expected Gu Immortals to awaken during this battle.

"Quickly look, Fang Yuan's side is making a new action!" One of the Eight Extremities shouted.

Bing Sai Chuan quickly shifted his gaze, he saw that four Immortal Gu Houses, Profound Frost House, Dragon Soul Dark Castle, Red River Pavilion, and Red Heavenly Altar, had changed locations, flying down the mountain.

Bing Sai Chuan could not help but feel shocked: "It seems that Fang Yuan has a plan already, but mobilizing four Immortal Gu Houses at once, isn't that too much?"

Fang Yuan had a total of seven Immortal Gu Houses, now that Rising Cloud City was given to Demon Immortal Qi Jue, and after moving four Immortal Gu Houses away, there was only Unbreakable Golden Fortress and Scarlet Palace left on the mountain.

Currently, the most important thing was to reach the peak of Book Mountain and ruin Heavenly Court's killer move so that they could not obtain Primordial Domain.

Right now, Fang Yuan diverted his forces to attack the Gu Immortals of the immortal graveyard, he was putting his emphasis on the wrong target.

But at the next moment, the four diverted Immortal Gu Houses split up.

Profound Frost House and Red River Pavilion went to help Zhan Bu Du in fighting Qing Chou.

Dragon Soul Dark Castle and Red Heavenly Altar charged towards Heavenly Court's immortal graveyard.

Bing Sai Chuan realized at once, he yelled in his mind: "So Fang Yuan is trying to free up Zhan Bu Du!"

Zhan Bu Du had incomplete freedom transformation, he was powerful and unstoppable, he was the crucial battle strength for Fang Yuan's side to ascend the mountain.

Even though Fairy Ming Hao's humble reciprocation killer move was broken now, there were three pseudo venerables at the top of the mountain, if ordinary rank eight Immortal Gu Houses charged to the top, they would be suppressed by the three.

Divine Emperor City was at the middle section of the mountain, it was a tough hurdle too.

It had the killer move 'broken homes and dead family', that was the biggest counter to Immortal Gu Houses.

Thus, letting Zhan Bu Du take the lead was the wisest decision.

Dragon Soul Dark Castle and Red Heavenly Altar flew rapidly, soon arriving before Duke Mei and Duke Tong.

Duke Mei took in a deep breath, he straightened both arms and aimed at the two Immortal Gu Houses.

Vines suddenly appeared around Dragon Soul Dark Castle and Red Heavenly Altar, these vines were dry and tough, they bound the two Immortal Gu Houses tightly.

"Oh no, the immortal essence storages in the Immortal Gu Houses are being absorbed by the vines!" Fang Yuan's subordinate Gu Immortals realized this and shouted in anger.

The two Immortal Gu Houses started to counterattack.

The surface of Red Heavenly Altar radiated bright red light, melting all of the dried vines around it.

Dragon roars could be heard from Dragon Soul Dark Castle, the vines around it were snapped and sent flying.

But with this amount of time, Duke Tong's killer move was already prepared.

Two different sized bronze rings formed instantly and attached themselves to the two Immortal Gu Houses and spinning rapidly, buzzing loudly.

The bronze rings were flying too quickly, they seemed like vague shadows that immobilized the Immortal Gu Houses that they were surrounding.

Heavenly Court had learned from their lesson. During the fate war, because of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's method, Longevity Heaven managed to directly enter Heavenly Court, catching them off guard. In that battle, even though Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals awakened, because they lacked Immortal Gu, they did not display their true battle strength.

But now, Heavenly Court prepared the Immortal Gu of their hibernating Gu Immortals in advance.

Thus, Duke Mei and Duke Tong were able to immediately act and restrain the two Immortal Gu Houses.

But good times did not last, suddenly, a dragon soul appeared from within Dragon Soul Dark Castle, the dragon soul made several attempts before managing to destroy the bronze ring.

Next, Fairy Miao Yin and Lady White Rabbit flew out of their Immortal Gu House, attacking Duke Mei and Duke Tong.

Fairy Miao Yin activated wondrous hand profound sound, her eight arms stretched out elegantly.

Lady White Rabbit had lumps of light surrounding her, her aura surged intensely.

The two immortals charged forward, Duke Mei was the first to block them, after a few rounds, Lady White Rabbit noticed a weakness and got around Duke Mei to attack Duke Tong.

Duke Tong was interrupted, he had to cancel his bronze ring killer move and fight White Rabbit instead.

The four immortals clashed and parted continuously, nobody could interrupt their battle.

Duke Mei and Duke Tong had rank eight cultivation level and their battle strength was on par with Qin Ding Ling, but they did not have pseudo venerable battle strength like Duke Long.

Dragon Soul Dark Castle and Red Heavenly Altar regained freedom, they charged at the immortal graveyard, trying to destroy it!

Rumble!

These two Immortal Gu Houses had just charged forward when a Gu Immortal repelled them.

This Gu Immortal had a calm expression, his nose was tall and his eyes were deep, his shoulders were lifted up as they held up one mini mountain each.

"With me, Uncle Feng, here, don't even think of destroying the immortal graveyard." Uncle Feng blocked the path of the two Immortal Gu Houses, he had the demeanor of a person trying to stop an army.

Fang Yuan's subordinates were not ready to give up, they controlled the Immortal Gu Houses to attack.

But Uncle Feng fought similarly to Lu Wei Yin, they were specialized in defense, even with the attack of the two Immortal Gu Houses, he still held them off.

"What do we do now?" A Gu Immortal in Red Heavenly Altar asked.

Currently, Fairy Miao Yin and Lady White Rabbit were fighting against Duke Mei and Duke Tong, the mission of destroying the immortal graveyard was in the hands of these two Immortal Gu Houses.

"No worries, he has already been hit by our method." The immortals in Dragon Soul Dark Castle snickered.

Guh.

As he said that, Uncle Feng's expression turned ashen, he spat out pieces of soul fragments.

"A soul path method?" Uncle Feng frowned.

In his era, there was no soul path.

Right at this moment, a newly awakened Gu Immortal flew out of the immortal graveyard.

"It seems like my awakening was timely." This female immortal was just a soul, she had no body.

She blew at Uncle Feng lightly.

This blue-gray breath reached Uncle Feng's body and quickly fused into his soul.

Uncle Feng felt a sense of relief, his soul injury was rapidly healing.

"Oh no, this is Heavenly Court's soul path great expert from Spectral Soul's era, Fairy Maiden Soul who is on par with Thunder Ghost True Monarch. She is most skilled at healing methods!" The Gu Immortals in Dragon Soul Dark Castle had a change of expression.

The ones in Red Heavenly Altar gritted their teeth: "Kill this healing Gu Immortal first, otherwise, all our efforts will be nullified by her."

The battle erupted again, the two Immortal Gu Houses focused their target on Fairy Maiden Soul.

All sorts of killer moves were unleashed, Uncle Feng defended desperately, both sides gave it their all as the sky turned dark from their clash, winds and waves were rising.

While they were in a deadlock, another immortal awakened and joined the battle.

This immortal had a round head and large ears, he wore a loose robe and qi path aura surged around him.

Boom boom boom!

As the air exploded, the qi path immortal charged in between the two Immortal Gu Houses.

"Take this move — Rugged Fiendish Qi."

The qi path immortal shouted as he waved his sleeves, blowing out countless traces of fiendish qi.

The fiendish qi gathered and took form, becoming huge rocks that turned into mountains and valleys, enveloping the two Immortal Gu Houses.

Red Heavenly Altar and Dragon Soul Dark Castle tried to charge out at the first moment, destroying countless fiendish qi mountains.

But after these mountains shattered, they quickly formed again to obstruct the Immortal Gu Houses.

"This is... Senior Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch!" Uncle Feng and Fairy Maiden Soul were surprised.

Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch was a famous qi path expert renowned in history, after he became rank eight and traveled the world, he purposely looked for the fiendish qi sea springs and created the Shabi from them. He refined a total of ninety-nine Shabi, he formed a grand army with them. These Shabi were compatible with his immortal killer moves, he could use them extremely well, during that era, almost nobody could rival him.

The current Shabi Ninety-five was one of them, after a long period of time, its strength had risen to legendary immemorial beast level.

With the help of Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch, Heavenly Court managed to defend the immortal graveyard.

Thereafter, more and more Gu Immortals awakened, Heavenly Court survived the initial stage which was the most dangerous, they started counterattacking.

Many Gu Immortals directly got around the small battlefield and tried to reinforce Book Mountain.

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable! Are you there? Come out and meet me!" Golden Hooped Great Immortal shouted in deep anger.

He had once invited Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to tour Heavenly Court, during that time, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable planted a seed that erupted during the fate war, causing Longevity Heaven to arrive in Heavenly Court and cause huge losses to them.

"Ninety-five, come here." Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch blocked Demon Immortal Qi Jue and beckoned Shabi Ninety-five.

"Master." Shabi Ninety-five was filled with admiration and fear, it went to Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch with injuries all over the body.

Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch petted it lightly, Shabi Ninety-five instantly became revitalized, its injuries mostly healed.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue had a dark expression, with the appearance of Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch, his plan of capturing Shabi Ninety-five became hopeless.

"Stop him!" Right at this moment, Fairy Ming Hao shouted.

Zhan Bu Du moved like a raging dragon, he arrived at the middle of the mountain from the southeast direction.

Behind him, Qing Chou was chasing relentlessly but it was obstructed by Profound Frost House and Red River Pavilion, it could not move quickly enough to stop Zhan Bu Du.

Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch took in a deep breath: "You are one of the clones of the current generation demon, Fang Yuan? Let me have a taste of your power."

Right when he was about to go, Demon Immortal Qi Jue blocked him.

The latter chuckled: "You think you can leave?"

Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch had a solemn expression: "Since senior insists, then I, the junior, will have to risk my life to face you in battle."

"Where are you going?" Gu Yue Fang Zheng shouted loudly.

Demon Judgment Board which was flying around the place quickly arrived, but with a loud sound, it was sent flying by the Unbreakable Golden Fortress that had just arrived as well.

"Help Zhan Bu Du to fight his way to the peak of the mountain." The other immortals saw a chance, they took action and blocked the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals for Zhan Bu Du.

Fairy Ming Hao saw this and sighed deeply, she had no choice but to fly out and stand in front of Zhan Bu Du: "Wait..."

"Get lost!"

Zhan Bu Du shouted, sweeping his arm fiercely.

Boom!

Fairy Ming Hao's body was covered in dazzling starlight, even though she blocked this move, her entire person was sent flying like a cannonball, she crashed through many rocks on Book Mountain before stopping.

Chapter 2182: Hu Elevation!

Fairy Ming Hao's body shook as she quickly stood up.

She was not injured, but the issue here was that she could not block Zhan Bu Du.

In this current situation, Zhan Bu Du's threat level was far greater than the Immortal Gu Houses.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

Fairy Ming Hao stomped lightly as she quickly flew out, her palm stretched out as tens of stardust specks flew around.

Zhan Bu Du did not dodge, he allowed the stardust to land on him, he was as fierce as a dragon or tiger, only aiming for the mountain peak.

Fairy Ming Hao gritted her teeth, she could only fly forward and face Zhan Bu Du in close combat.

Zhan Bu Du kicked and she was sent flying again, he completely ignored her.

"Charge!" Some Gu Immortals saw Zhan Bu Du ascending to the top of Book Mountain, they were about to cheer when suddenly, starlight flashed before them.

Zhan Bu Du was enveloped by starlight and quickly vanished, when he reappeared, he was at the base of Book Mountain.

The immortals were shocked before understanding why.

This killer move was not new, it had been used during the fate war.

As expected, when Zhan Bu Du raised his head to look above Book Mountain, he saw a tiny and delicate Immortal Gu House.

Which other chessboard looking Immortal Gu House could it be but Star Constellation Chessboard?

Star Constellation Chessboard radiated with starlight, any enemy that approached the peak of the mountain would get enveloped by starlight and forcefully teleported elsewhere, it was an impossible position.

Fairy Ming Hao charged at Zhan Bu Du again, trying to stall him while feeling nervous internally: "Hopefully, no one can break this killer move!"

This move had been used before.

The more a Gu Immortal uses their method, the greater the risk of it getting seen through.

Zhan Bu Du's gaze turned slightly dim, he soon made a decision.

He endured Fairy Ming Hao's furious attacks as he charged to the top again at full speed!

He seemed to have made no advancement, but he had succeeded in his goal. Fairy Feng Ya was originally fully invested in retrieving the Primordial Domain, now, she had to multitask and control Star Constellation Chessboard, her efficiency was greatly reduced.

Fang Yuan's side had to continue exerting pressure to distract her.

Fairy Ming Hao had an outstanding combat system, the more stars that hit the target, the greater the damage they would progressively take.

Zhan Bu Du initially resisted the stars which could not even pierce his skin. But after hundreds of stardust strikes, he was bathed in blood. When the attacks reached over a thousand, his wounds were deep until bones could be seen.

During this period, he had already failed in three attempts to charge up.

He was transported by Star Constellation Chessboard each time.

"It seems that at this moment, nobody can break this method." Fairy Ming Hao relaxed at long last.

During this period, Gu Immortals had taken action, but Star Constellation Chessboard's killer move was constantly modified by Heavenly Court to a mild extent, allowing it to display effectiveness even now.

"This cannot drag on." Qi Sea Ancestor had been fighting against Fairy Yu Xiu all along, seeing Zhan Bu Du's state, he made a decision.

He waved his sleeves, a silhouette flew out, taking the place of the main body to deceive Fairy Yu Xiu.

Fairy Yu Xiu quickly exposed this fake body but Lu Wei Yin flew in front of her, desperately blocking her.

Because Fairy Yu Xiu was stalled for a moment, Qi Sea Ancestor, who was far away summoned a secluded domain of heaven and earth above his head.

"Hu Land?!" Demon Immortal Qi Jue was fighting against Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch, at this moment, both of them turned around together and shouted in unison.

"Move aside." Qi Sea Ancestor's sleeves fluttered intensely along with his beard, his face was flushing red.

Lu Wei Yin quickly dodged to the side.

But Qi Sea Ancestor suddenly changed directions, aiming towards Book Mountain instead.

"Oh no!" Fairy Yu Xiu saw this and her heart jumped, she quickly used a killer move, disregarding the danger as she stood between Qi Sea Ancestor and Book Mountain.

Immortal killer move — Hu Elevation!

Hu Land suddenly shook intensely as countless qi currents shot out of it fiercely.

Qi currents surged intensely and grandly, there was righteous qi, evil qi, blood qi, strange qi, and others, they had gathered into a single force under the effect of Hu Land, they were tightly connected and inseparable!

Bam!

Heaven and earth shook, it could astound demons and gods.

An immensely thick qi beam shot out abruptly, it flew towards Book Mountain with terrifying force that could split heaven and earth.

Fairy Yu Xiu gritted her teeth, she used the strongest defensive method that she possessed, traces of fresh wisdom path insignias surrounded her body, radiating over the world.

As the qi beam approached, the wisdom path insignias were quickly melted, and Fairy Yu Xiu's tiny body was quickly submerged in the vast force.

The qi beam was obstructed by this and lost thirty percent of its power, but it still moved towards Book Mountain with an unstoppable momentum.

"Don't even think of it!" At the crucial moment, Bai Cang Shui controlled a rank eight Immortal Gu House and charged forward.

With a heaven-shaking sound, Heavenly Court's rank eight Immortal Gu House only lasted for a few breaths of time before disintegrating.

On Book Mountain, Star Constellation Chessboard shot out a beam of light that landed on Bai Cang Shui through the gaps of the Immortal Gu House, bringing her away.

Without Bai Cang Shui controlling it, the Immortal Gu House quickly got destroyed by the qi beam, turning into scraps.

Next, even the scraps were blown to oblivion by the qi beam!

The qi beam's power weakened by another twenty percent, but it was less than a hundred steps away from Book Mountain.

At the crucial moment, a golden green giant appeared.

It was Qing Chou.

Qing Chou raised its shield and blocked the qi beam.

Boom.

The qi pillar sent Qing Chou crashing into Book Mountain as well, creating a huge pit that was hundreds of feet deep.

Even as the qi beam dissipated, the lingering aura permeated the battlefield.

Qing Chou did not move at all, its shield was destroyed and a huge hole that was completely see-through appeared on its chest.

Divine Emperor City quickly came over with flickering green light, a spiral appeared and sucked Qing Chou's dead body back into it.

Elsewhere, starlight specks started to shine beside Fairy Ming Hao as Fairy Yu Xiu appeared.

Her hair was disheveled, she was in a pitiful state.

Her expression was pale, her body was unstable, she fell to a half-kneeling position on the ground immediately after.

Qi Sea Ancestor's Hu elevation killer move was terrifyingly powerful, he defeated Yu Xiu, destroyed the Immortal Gu House, and killed Qing Chou in just one move!

But Qi Sea Ancestor was in poor condition as well.

After using this move, he lost thirty percent of his immortal essence storage, he even expended ten thousand qi path dao marks.

Chains started to appear from the space around him, binding Qi Sea Ancestor in a fixed position.

"Qi Sea Ancestor's killer move was too powerful, it caused Limitless' retaliation method to trigger!" Lu Wei Yin saw this and his expression changed slightly.

If this Hu elevation was not used on Book Mountain, which was guarded by Heavenly Court desperately, it would have caused immense destruction to the great worlds.

That would severely affect Limitless Demon Venerable's final derivation.

Thus, Limitless Demon Venerable's method activated, restraining Qi Sea Ancestor immediately.

Qi Sea Ancestor wanted to struggle but was helpless to find that he could not move, the chains even moved into his mind, stopping the collision of his thoughts, there were also chains in his immortal aperture that sealed all his immortal essence.

Lu Wei Yin quickly went to him and guarded his body.

The peak of Book Mountain was still not taken down, the Primordial Domain silhouette in the sky was becoming more vivid, but Bing Sai Chuan smiled from within Calamity Luck Altar: "Heavenly Court is at their wits end too."

Earlier, even though Heavenly Court blocked Hu elevation at the critical moment, they had expended their trump cards, they were exhausted now.

Bing Sai Chuan could tell that they were weakened, he immediately said to the Eight Extremities behind him: "The time is now, go and attack Book Mountain!"

Heaven Extremity Gai Mei, Earth Extremity Gan Ni, Black Extremity Sun Ming Lu, Yellow Extremity Jiao Huo, Space Extremity Chang Bai, Time Extremity Man Xin Yi, Flood Extremity Yu Yi Yi, and Desolate Extremity Lu Tong Lan, they were all mobilized.

Once they left Calamity Luck Altar, the eight of them activated an ancient battle formation — Eight Extremities!

This ancient battle formation was very special, normally speaking, ancient battle formations gathered the strength of many Gu Immortals into one, but this ancient battle formation split the gathered power into eight Gu Immortals, causing the Eight Extremities' battle strength to surge immensely, making them go from rank seven to rank eight elites.

Once the Eight Extremities moved out, from the direction of Yellow Earth Great World, a group of people came.

They were led by Fang Yuan's enslavement path clone Wu Shuai, and the giant formed from the Twelve Zodiac battle formation.

Originally, Fang Yuan was waiting at the back while observing the situation, once he saw a chance, he mobilized his people to attack.

Heavenly Court's pressure intensified at once.

In order to prevent the Gu Immortals from breaking through, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals flew out of their Immortal Gu Houses.

Instantly, the battle surrounding Book Mountain reached the most intense climax.

Almost each breath, there would be a killer move unleashed.

Countless killer moves weaved together and created a beautiful fireworks of varying colors, from within the dazzling display, there was deep killing intent.

Red Heart Traveler suddenly held up a sun of blood that shone brightly, shielding Nine Spiritual Fairy.

Nine Spiritual Fairy gave a clear roar, the nine-colored barrier shook and the nine layers of light mixed together, becoming extremely dazzling.

Next, the mixed light sphere flashed as Nine Spiritual Fairy transformed into a colorful rhinoceros.

The rhinoceros had a large head and small body, it was shining with various colors. It spoke human language: "Thank you!"

Saying so, it charged towards the Twelve Zodiac Giant.

Rumble!

The two huge existences clashed, dust clouds rose and rocks were sent flying.

The moment Nine Spiritual Fairy left, Yellow Extremity Jiao Huo appeared behind Red Heart Traveler.

Pew!

As flames surged, Red Heart Traveler was caught unguarded and got hit by Yellow Extremity, his defensive killer move was pierced and he got substantially injured.

"How can this be?" Red Heart Traveler was shocked but quickly retaliated.

But at the next moment, Yellow Extremity pierced through space, escaping far away.

Red Heart Traveler saw this, his heart sank, he could tell that Yellow Extremity was a fire path cultivator, but he managed to unleash a space path method.

"So Longevity Heaven's eight extremities killer move can not only connect the thoughts of the Eight Extremities together and share their vision, they can also share killer moves!"

Under the effect of the killer move eight extremities, the Eight Extremities cooperated smoothly, the battle strength they displayed was beyond imagination.

Red Heart Traveler became incredibly alert, he swiftly dodged attacks.

At the next moment, countless army ants swept the base of the mountain like a tsunami, quickly rising to the middle of the mountain.

Wu Shuai did not step onto the mountain, he was outside manipulating his army.

Divine Emperor City sent out countless divine bean soldiers to fight against the army ants.

In the chaotic battle, a figure flew out like a rampaging dragon, there were huge waves wherever he went. There was a cape behind him that was blood-red in color, he was Zhan Bu Du!

Fairy Yu Xiu had already gone to obstruct the Eight Extremities, while Fairy Ming Hao was sent flying by Zhan Bu Du again.

"Stop him!" Fairy Ming Hao shouted loudly.

Ruan Dan was nearby, it hesitated upon hearing this, not daring to move forward.

Zhou Xiong Xin gritted his teeth, he stood before Zhan Bu Du.

Immortal killer move — Rumors Become Tigers!

Fierce tigers roared, charging towards Zhan Bu Du with imposing might.

Zhan Bu Du sucked in with his mouth as the tigers were absorbed into his stomach, he easily arrived in front of Zhou Xiong Xin.

Zhan Bu Du punched directly, piercing Zhou Xiong Xin's chest as his hand appeared behind the victim.

Zhou Xiong Xin's eyes were wide open, he died on the spot.

Zhan Bu Du waved his arm, this corpse was sent flying, he met with the awakened Gu Immortal Fairy Maiden Soul next.

Zhan Bu Du shouted loudly, his monstrous strength obliterated Fairy Maiden Soul, her soul was completely destroyed.

Zhan Bu Du stomped as he finally arrived at the top of the mountain, this time, Star Constellation Chessboard had ceased attacking as well, it did not shoot out any more star pillars.

Chapter 2183: Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!

Star Constellation, as a child, was laughing happily.

She wandered around the back mountain, roamed the multi-colored flower fields, and played with the sweet mountain springs.

She teased a young, intelligent leopard cat which she had saved coincidentally.

These last days, she would often come to the cave to see it, feed it, and play with it.

"You are playing around again?!" A voice suddenly came from behind.

The child Star Constellation's body shook, she felt her skull turning numb as she slowly turned around and saw the white robed, solemn-looking Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable.

"Master..." Star Constellation lowered her head, saying softly.

"Give your hand." Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable brought out a ruler.

Star Constellation gritted her teeth as she stretched out her small white hand.

Slap.

The ruler struck her palm and left a red mark.

The intense pain struck her, but Star Constellation fought back the tears.

"The homework that you did recently is a total mess, instead of training killer moves, you are playing with a cat here?" Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable looked at the leopard cat behind Star Constellation.

The child Star Constellation immediately brimmed with tears: "Master, don't be angry, don't chase Little Yellow away. Its injuries have just healed, I promise I will definitely practice my killer moves."

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable fixed his gaze at Star Constellation, but Star Constellation drummed up her courage and held her gaze, like she would protect the leopard cat no matter what.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's expression was stiff, he picked up the child Star Constellation: "Come with me."

Star Constellation felt a strong wind brushing past her face and could not open her eyes.

After some time, the roar of the wind suddenly stopped and she felt her feet touching the ground.

"Take a look." Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's voice reached her.

Star Constellation opened her eyes and saw that she was in a ruin.

Her pupils shrunk, her sight was filled with burning houses and corpses of man, woman, old, and young...

"This village was peaceful and quiet, but because it is near the regional wall, a group of variant human bandits invaded and massacred everyone."

"Do you know how often this situation occurs?" Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable asked.

The child Star Constellation was deeply shocked, shaking her head subconsciously.

"This kind of situation is happening almost every day." Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable heaved a sigh, "Not only at the periphery of Central Continent, there are remnant variant humans even deep within Central Continent itself. They come out occasionally and kill us humans."

"Heavenly Court is already established in Central Continent, humanity has firm dominance, while the variant human super forces have gone into hiding or have left Central Continent. As for the other four regions? Variant humans still hold power. Do you know why that is the case?"

The child Star Constellation answered quickly: "I know! I heard from the senior brothers and sisters that master roamed the five regions and attacked all the variant human super forces. No matter how many variant human Gu Immortals there are, they cannot beat you. But they all hid away, so we cannot find them."

"Right." Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable nodded his head, "When immortal apertures are placed in the world, they shrink down to the size of a speck, searching them is extremely difficult, like searching for a needle in the ocean."

"Because of this, even though humanity has me, an Immortal Venerable invincible in the world, we are still unable to get rid of those variant humans."

"Although we have taken control of Central Continent, the other four regions are still not liberated. Because our human population is too small, we cannot compare to variant humans."

"Even if we target the four regions' variant human Gu Masters and mortals, even if we kill them all, as long as those variant human blessed lands and grotto-heavens exist, they can easily nurture countless variant humans."

Once blessed lands and grotto-heavens hid, they were difficult to find, and the time inside was much faster than the outside world. The population inside could increase much more rapidly.

Every once in a while, the blessed lands and grotto-heavens could open their entrance and release the extra population in the four regions.

"These Gu Immortals' immortal apertures are the foundations of the variant humans. If we cannot find their specific locations, when I die, humanity will still be in a perilous situation, the past tragedy will repeat once more." Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable heaved a deep sigh and stroked the child Star Constellation's hair, "This is why you need to work hard! Fate has decreed that you will become the future Immortal Venerable and create wisdom path."

"With wisdom path, we can deduce the location of most of the blessed lands and grotto-heavens, we can kill those variant human Gu Immortals and ensure the prosperity of humanity for countless generations ahead."

"Xing Su[1], you need to understand that with every moment you spend playing around, more of our people will die under the blades of the variant humans. Among them, there are many old people, and also many who are the same age as you. While you are playing, the children who are of your age lie in a pool of blood, unable to see the sun of tomorrow."

The child Star Constellation was pale as paper as she pursed her lips in silence.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable used his killer move again, bringing her back to the back of the mountain. He did not instruct her anymore and left her by herself.

Several days later.

The child Star Constellation parted with the leopard cat Little Yellow.

Despite Little Yellow being very reluctant to leave, she still returned it to the forest.

When she was alone, she squatted on the ground and held her knees, weeping softly to herself.

"Although master is completely right, I am only just a child. The senior brothers and sisters can have fun, so why can't I?"

"Is it simply because fate decreed me as the future Immortal Venerable?"

The child Star Constellation cried for a long time till nighttime, the sky was filled with stars.

She slowly stood up, her small, round face still had tear stains.

A lump of starlight gushed out of her heart.

Star Constellation held this starlight and threw it on the back of the mountain.

This lump of starlight bore a vague resemblance to her shadow.

The child Star Constellation said to this starlight shadow: "Actually, I don't want to become an Immortal Venerable, but fate cannot be changed. Everyone is so kind to me, I need to think for them as well and bring happiness to the whole of humanity."

"If there is a second life, I want you to play all you want and make up for my regret in this life!"

The starlight shadow did not leave.

The child Star Constellation looked at her and said: "Let me give you a name. Since master often praises my wittiness, bright eyes and white teeth, let's call you Ming Hao."

The starlight shadow seemed to be very happy after receiving the name, it left quickly.

Teenage Star Constellation grew into a young lady, and she was now an immortal.

She did not just stay in closed cultivation, she often traveled to different places to enrich her experience.

There was no use in just cultivating behind closed doors, because what she needed to do was not to inherit Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's legacy, but to create wisdom path.

When she was traveling Eastern Sea with a disguised identity, she became acquainted with a Gu Immortal.

Under some coincidences, she and this Gu Immortal ran into each other time and again. They joined hands to fight and got rid of variant human tribes, they explored sea trenches, and so on. Their friendship deepened, which eventually turned into feelings of fondness.

But...

"You are a variant human!" When Star Constellation saw her beloved's true appearance, she stepped back in shock.

"Xing Er, I did not hide it on purpose, please listen to my explanation." Her beloved one was anxious.

Star Constellation, however, shook her head and flew up to the sky.

The man gave chase without letting up, but because of his heavy injuries, he fell from the sky in the end.

When he gained consciousness, he found that he was lying on a beach and Star Constellation was beside him.

"You saved me, Xing Er! I know it is you, where are you? Come out and meet me!" The man was both surprised and happy as he struggled to get up and shouted with all his strength, but he received no reply after all.

In the end, he could only leave the island.

Under the setting sun, looking at his lonely receding figure, Star Constellation stood on the beach and revealed herself.

Her eyes were brimming with tears along with reluctance to part with him: "Why do you have to be a variant human? How great would it be if you were human? Do you know that I already thought of marrying you? According to customs, master had already prepared Embroidered Tower for me as dowry."

"But I cannot do it."

"Because I am Star Constellation, the future Immortal Venerable of humanity."

"I need to get rid of the variant human Gu Immortals for my people, if I become your wife, how can I attack them? Once the variant humans get comfortable, what will happen to the future of humanity?"

Her master's anticipation, the hope of humanity, and the support of the people around her; all of these burdens were weighing on Star Constellation's shoulders.

But her heart still ached!

The pain of unfulfilled love almost tore her soul apart.

Starlight started to gush out of Star Constellation's heart.

She held this lump of starlight again.

She mumbled to the starlight shadow: "Since he praised my beauty and talent, I will name you Yu Xiu. If there is another life, please live well for me, don't care about the future of humanity, don't think about the safety of people, for just once, live for yourself and be selfish, go ahead and love, you can cry to your heart's content!"

The starlight shadow rippled as if replying to her.

In her later years, Star Constellation had already become a venerable.

Inside a hall, she sat on the main seat, looking at her senior sister who had always supported and taken care of her, she was like her own mother.

"Let me do it!" The senior sister shouted, "Ah Su, you are the great Immortal Venerable, you cannot sacrifice yourself to merge with heaven's will."

"No." Star Constellation shook her head softly, "Precisely because I am the Immortal Venerable, I need to do this."

The senior sister's eyes were filled with tears: "Ah Su, you were only three years old when you became master's disciple. I have taken care of you this entire time, I looked at you grow bit by bit, mature step by step, and finally become the Star Constellation Immortal Venerable of humanity."

"No one knows better than me how much sadness and pain you have endured in this process. You have already sacrificed too much over these years."

"Now, you have already done a great job and fulfilled everyone's expectations. Don't make sacrifices anymore, you still have a lot of time to do what you want to do."

"Didn't you often complain to me? Although your life seemed great and you have been praised by countless people, you still hold many regrets. Ah Su, you deserve a better life from now on."

"You have sacrificed too much for humanity, it is time for you to live for yourself."

"So this time, let me assimilate with heaven's will."

Star Constellation smiled, her figure flashed and appeared before her senior sister.

She softly wiped her senior sister's tears and took out a lump of starlight from her heart.

"Senior sister."

"You praised me for my great magnanimity. I shall name this starlight shadow Feng Ya, let her accompany you in my stead. I was an orphan from birth, you looked after me all my life, you are my sister and also like my mother. How can I let you do this?"

"In any case, I have already sacrificed and given up so much, it is already like a habit for me. Haha."

"Let Feng Ya stay and look after you, she will help me make up for the regrets in life."

"I have left behind three starlight shadows, they are also my arrangements for revival."

"I do not want to see the day where I can revive, but if the situation aggravates to that degree and I revive, I will listen to you, my senior sister. Forget about this world or the whole of humanity, I will live for myself and myself only!"

"For once, I want to be selfish too."

Crazed Demon Cave.

When Ming Hao, Yu Xiu, and Feng Ya woke up, they received devastating news.

Fate Gu was destroyed, Heavenly Court had fallen to an abysmal state, the great demon Fang Yuan had risen up, the righteous path was declining while demons surged, Central Continent was surrounded by danger on all fronts.

I once vowed to myself!

I want to live my own life..

To live for my pleasure, to live for my love, and to live for my happiness.

Was I wrong?

I had already completed my mission, I created wisdom path, I already got rid of most of the variant human Gu Immortals, I even led humanity on the path of prosperity.

It was time I took a rest.

But why?

Why did I subconsciously make plans and arrangements?

Why am I still fighting here?

Why?

Fairy Ming Hao looked at the rising fire and smoke, she curled her lips.

Fairy Yu Xiu looked at Demon Immortal Qi Jue and the Eight Extremities with a cold gaze.

Fairy Feng Ya looked at the charging Zhan Bu Du and smiled plainly.

At this moment, starlight flickered on the bodies of the three fairies, resonating with bright radiance.

The three immortals recited together —

A life of selfless giving,

Worrying and helping the people.

Sacrificing my body and life,

For starlight to radiate the world.

Everything changed upon revival,

The five regions became unrecognizable.

Only my heart remained the same,

The three avatars unite to save heaven!

Starlight connected and fused into one, its radiance rising towards the sky.

The light soon formed into an immortal with peerless beauty, her eyes shone brightly like stars in the sky.

Star Constellation?

Star Constellation.

Star Constellation!

[1] Star Constellation's name which also became her title later, much like Paradise Earth. Back

Chapter 2184: Immortal Venerables Enter Primordial Domain

"Star Constellation Immortal Venerable?!"

On the peak of Book Mountain, the scene of three star avatars joining into one and turning into Star Constellation Immortal Venerable shocked the immortals, who were bathed in blood.

Although the immortals already expected the revival of venerables with fate Gu being destroyed, when a venerable really revived in front of them, they still could not help but feel intense shock.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!

The only female among the ten venerables. She created wisdom path, inherited Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's will, developed Heavenly Court, assimilated with heaven's will, and helped Heavenly Court resist three Demon Venerables.

Her name was always resplendent in the history of humanity, her glorious reputation had never dimmed.

Now, she had revived!

"Star Constellation, take this punch!" Zhan Bu Du did not have any hesitation as he stepped on the mountain peak, and with a thunderous voice, he attacked Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's revival did not surprise Fang Yuan.

In fact, he already had some speculations regarding the identities of Ming Hao, Yu Xiu, and Feng Ya.

These three had extremely high strength, they were all pseudo venerables.

Just this point alone was enough to explain the problem!

Heavenly Court was persistent in repairing Fate and had worked for it for over one million years. But in the crucial fate war, there was only one pseudo venerable battle strength - Duke Long - defending Heavenly Court.

But right now in Crazed Demon Cave, Heavenly Court had suddenly brought out three pseudo venerable battle strength experts, this proved that these three female immortals had revived only after the destruction of fate Gu.

If not for this, how could they not participate in the fate war?

Since they were revived pseudo venerables, their names should have been renowned in history, but they were shrouded in mystery.

More importantly, there was no trace of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable from the start.

With these several clues and his strong wisdom path attainment, Fang Yuan deduced that the probability of these three immortals being Star Constellation was increasingly obvious.

It was like how Fang Yuan could create clones like Qi Sea Ancestor, Zhan Bu Du, and Wu Shuai, why could Star Constellation Immortal Venerable not do the same?

It was just that Star Constellation's three avatars were more profound and mysterious than Fang Yuan's clones —

The three fairies could become Star Constellation by fusing together!

Zhan Bu Du showed no fear against the revived Star Constellation. Before his punch even landed on Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, the intense wind from his punch blew Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's long hair into the air.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, however, was smiling.

At the next moment, Zhan Bu Du struck Star Constellation, but he passed right through her.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's figure vanished like an illusory bubble.

This was fake, it was merely an illusion.

Zhan Bu Du realized this and quickly activated an investigative method, but could not detect Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's main body.

"Star Constellation, please hold on." Suddenly, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's voice came from Calamity Luck Altar.

Golden light drifted in the air, revealing Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's figure.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used a killer move.

Inside her immortal aperture, Fairy Feng Ya's talent Gu, and Fairy Yu Xiu's serious Gu and learning Gu, which were temporarily taken out from Divine Emperor City, activated one after the other.

Immortal essence was consumed intensely, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's figure turned illusory again.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's golden light could not obstruct her any longer.

Under everyone's gaze, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable flew to the sky grandly and entered Primordial Domain!

"Damn it!" Zhan Bu Du gritted his teeth as he gave chase.

However, although he caught up to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, she was like a silhouette that could not be disturbed by Zhan Bu Du. She quickly entered the depths of Primordial Domain.

But Zhan Bu Du passed through Primordial Domain.

"Without special methods, there is no way to enter Primordial Domain!" Zhan Bu Du's eyes burned with anger.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was revived.

But she did not fight Zhan Bu Du, instead choosing to directly head to Primordial Domain.

She was a venerable, she could not make a move casually; otherwise, she would be suppressed by Limitless Demon Venerable's methods just like Qi Sea Ancestor.

She directly left without caring for Heavenly Court's immortals, Book Mountain, and the whole battlefield, but this became a fatal move!

Lu Wei Yin's expression was ashen and extremely unsightly.

Primordial Domain was the crucial factor of the battle in Crazed Demon Cave.

The reason they attacked Book Mountain furiously was to obstruct Heavenly Court from obtaining Primordial Domain. They never expected that even though Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was unable to get Primordial Domain, she could directly fly into it.

Zhan Bu Du lacked suitable methods and could not block her.

In fact, even Immortal Zombie Giant Sun made a move but was unable to obstruct Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!

"What do we do?" Lu Wei Yin was at a loss.

Once Star Constellation Immortal Venerable entered Primordial Domain to replenish her lost attainment level, she would quickly become a wisdom path supreme grandmaster and regain her status of the wisdom path Dao Lord.

"Is Heavenly Court going to continue controlling the future of this world?" Bing Sai Chuan sighed dejectedly.

"Not necessarily." Immortal Zombie Giant Sun sneered, "Let's go!"

At the next moment, Calamity Luck Altar shone with dazzling golden light.

The golden light shot everywhere before joining together and making a path that stretched forward.

It was Calamity Luck Altar's killer move — Luck Changing Golden Light Path!

At the same time, Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace that was stationed in Savage Wilderness Great World also let out a majestic light.

Ever since Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace was brought into Crazed Demon Cave, it had actively participated and cooperated with Limitless Demon Venerable's deductions regarding the development of the worlds, it had gotten deeply involved.

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace's light shone on Calamity Luck Altar, creating mysterious changes in the luck changing golden light path.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun flew out of Calamity Luck Altar and followed the golden light path into Primordial Domain.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was unable to stop Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, but he possessed the number one luck path attainment in the world. He made use of Calamity Luck Altar and Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace to enter Primordial Domain.

Longevity Heaven's immortals cheered as they saw this.

But Fang Yuan's subordinates were pale.

"Damn it, damn it!" Lu Wei Yin's expression was extremely unsightly.

Although Longevity Heaven cooperated with Fang Yuan, their main goal was to make use of him. Right now, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun directly abandoned Fang Yuan and entered Primordial Domain himself.

It was obvious that he was seeking to replenish his luck path attainment level in Primordial Domain and become a luck path Dao Lord once again!

Both Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven threw Fang Yuan aside.

"Is this a venerable's foundation?" Xiao He Jian heaved a sigh.

"Should we retreat?" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's will started to waver.

Fang Yuan was the source of these variant human Gu Immortals' confidence, but currently, it was obvious Fang Yuan could not compare to the two venerables. This made the variant human Gu Immortals' morale fall sharply.

"No need to worry." At this time, Fang Yuan's main body came over from Yellow Earth Great World.

His expression was still calm.

Lu Wei Yin's eyes shone with hope: "Lord Fang Yuan, you have a way?"

Fang Yuan nodded, looking towards Rising Cloud City: "Qi Jue, let's cooperate once again."

Demon Immortal Qi Jue flew over from Rising Cloud City: "Heh, I knew you had ulterior motives when you gave me the rank eight Immortal Gu House. But your killer move has no issue, come, let's work together!"

Fang Yuan stretched out his hand, taking out Hu Land from the Qi Sea clone's immortal aperture.

At the same time, Xi Land appeared above Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

Hu Land and Xi Land came together and shone on each other.

Lu Wei Yin was exulted when he saw this: "I get it, \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> has records of this!"

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, chapter five, section thirty-seven.

Wisdom Gu was bitten by self Gu, it felt very angry and decided to take revenge.

Wisdom Gu found lie Gu: "No matter what I say, my words are filled with wisdom, they will advise and help others. This won't do, so I came to you for help."

Lie Gu asked: "How do you want me to help you?"

Wisdom Gu said: "This is easy and simple. Ren Zu and his children are in Primordial Domain now. In front of Primordial Domain is Xi Land, while behind it is Hu Land. Go to Primordial Domain and deceive Ren Zu, tell him Hu Land is in front while Xi Land is behind."

Lie Gu was puzzled: "That can help you take revenge?"

Wisdom Gu laughed loudly: "Humans need to breathe in first before they can breathe out. Meanwhile, Xi Land and Hu Land are the breathing of heaven and earth. Just follow my instructions."

Lie Gu followed wisdom Gu's arrangements and went to Primordial Domain. It told Ren Zu: "Human, you need to be careful. You are in a mystical place, you will reach Hu Land if you go forward and Xi Land if you move back."

Ren Zu had been thinking of leaving Primordial Domain, he thought: "The beastmen once advised me to not go to Hu Land. In that case, I shall head towards the back and go to Xi Land."

Ren Zu moved towards the back of Primordial Domain with his children Great Strength True Martial and Carefree Wisdom Heart.

Thus, they arrived at Hu Land.

"This is not Xi Land!" Carefree Wisdom Heart knew they had been deceived.

Ren Zu patted his chest: "Fortunately, I died once and betrayal Gu has already left me. Otherwise if I care[1], betrayal Gu will harm me."

But Great Strength True Martial suddenly realized something and shouted: "This is bad!"

"What's wrong?" Ren Zu was just about to ask when self Gu flew out of his body.

Self Gu left Ren Zu, leaving behind a sentence: "Oh human, after you put attitude Gu on me, you deceived even yourself, so don't blame me for leaving you."

Back then, Ren Zu protected weak Gu. Weak Gu urged Ren Zu to put attitude Gu on self Gu to deceive himself; creating the perfect deception that managed to even deceive the Predicament.

If humans deceived themselves, their sense of self would leave and the person would lose themselves.

Ren Zu was angry and anxious: "What to do, self Gu left me. How can I obtain freedom without it? How can I break free of the restraints of fate?"

"Self Gu once took a bite of betrayal Gu, so it gained the inclination to betray. I was already dissatisfied with it." Great Strength True Martial's ability Gu shouted.

The skilled were naturally dissatisfied with themselves.

"Self Gu will be out of our sight soon, we need to give chase!" Carefree Wisdom Heart reminded.

The three immediately chase after self Gu.

Self Gu left very fast and dove into a river.

The river's surface was calm with ice of all sizes floating on it.

"This is the River of Time, the ice floating on the river is called truthful floating ice." Ren Zu's group recognized it immediately, they had gained this knowledge in the Qian Kun Crystal Wall.

Ren Zu looked afar and said: "I think self Gu is hiding in the center of the floating ice, let's quickly go and catch it!"

[1] 'Care' is read as 'At Hu' here, its a word pun. Back

Chapter 2185: Fang Yuan Enters Primordial Domain

Ren Zu's group sized up the situation by the riverside.

Every piece of floating ice in the River of Time was a piece of truth.

Ren Zu observed for a long while before pointing towards a floating ice: "This floating ice is neither big nor small and has a smooth surface, let's step on this."

But Great Strength True Martial said: "This floating ice is clearly too small, it is not enough for us three."

Carefree Wisdom Heart shook her head: "This floating ice is quite big but there are many spikes on it, they will pierce our feet."

Even when looking at the same truth, from the perspectives of different people, they could be big or small, minor or severe, difficult or easy. Some could accept it, but some could not.

Ren Zu's group discussed for a long while before they chose a floating ice and stepped on it.

When Ren Zu stepped on this ice, he immediately cried and sniveled; Great Strength True Martial shouted in anger, while Carefree Wisdom Heart laughed happily.

When looking at the same truth, different people would have different feelings and emotions regarding it.

Ren Zu and his children could only endure this.

"Every piece of floating ice in the River of Time is a cold and silent truth. But we humans have hearts, we feel emotions when we come across truths, and when truths and emotions mix, they create different situations[1] for everyone." Carefree Wisdom Heart recalled the knowledge in her mind.

The floating ice carried the group and drifted for a while before it started shrinking and submerging.

"Let's jump to that floating ice." Ren Zu pointed towards the left, at his front.

Before the floating ice under them submerged, the three jumped to the second floating ice.

This piece of truth created different emotions in Ren Zu's group.

The longer they stood on the floating ice, the more these emotions accumulated.

As the floating ice continued to sink, the emotions they felt also changed. Some went from angry to happy, while others went from happy to depressed.

"I can't endure this anymore, I feel horrible." After persisting for a while, Ren Zu said while grasping his heart, "Let's jump to that floating ice."

The three jumped over, but shortly afterwards, Carefree Wisdom Heart said: "I cannot stand this situation, I am also feeling extremely down. I even want to die."

Ren Zu's group of three quickly changed to another floating ice.

No matter what truth they came upon, in reality, they could be endured by gritting one's teeth. The most dreadful thing was the suffering of the heart.

If the heart could not endure it, the person would be unable to continue moving forward.

After changing several pieces of floating ice, Great Strength True Martial felt the least amount of discomfort: "I am still fine."

Strong Gu shouted proudly in his heart: "There are too many situations in the world, but it has always been the weak who suffer more than the strong."

Fortitude Gu called out: "The credit here goes to me because I have been helping you since the start."

Fortitude Gu could suppress emotions.

Suddenly, two Gu worms grew on Carefree Wisdom Heart's palms.

The Gu on the left palm was called Good. The Gu on the right palm was called Bad.

"Humans, we can help you distinguish which situation is good and which is bad." Good Gu and bad Gu said together in a soft voice.

Thus, with the help of good Gu and bad Gu, Ren Zu's group was able to choose a piece of floating ice that had a good situation.

All three of them felt happy when standing on this floating ice.

When the floating ice started to submerge and good situations turned bad, the three jumped away.

Like this, the three gradually turned happy, then ecstatic, before finally becoming euphoric. They could not move forward anymore as they drowned in emotions of endless joy.

The three forgot about their situation, the truthful floating ice they were standing on submerged completely, they fell into the river one after the other.

...

Crazed Demon Cave, eighth layer.

Xi Land!

Hu Land!

The two secluded domains of heaven and earth let out misty white light that mixed into one and formed a horizontal pillar of light.

"The final step." Fang Yuan let out a breath of relief as he activated a killer move.

Qi aura flew into the light pillar, forming a vortex in the middle.

The vortex shot to the sky, and when the white light vortex touched the surface of Primordial Domain, it expanded and shrouded the whole Primordial Domain like a fog.

Fang Yuan followed the white vortex of light and went into Primordial Domain!

"Amazing, amazing! Primordial Domain is in between Xi Land and Hu Land, using these two secluded domains of heaven and earth, he managed to locate Primordial Domain." Lu Wei Yin praised loudly as he followed after Fang Yuan.

Behind him were pseudo venerable battle strength experts like Zhan Bu Du, Demon Immortal Qi Jue, and Qi Sea Ancestor.

After these immortals entered Primordial Domain, the white vortex dissipated rapidly, disappointing those Gu Immortals who had been thinking of making a move.

Fang Yuan was floating in Primordial Domain, frowning deeply.

The moment he stepped in, countless inspirations appeared in his mind.

But this was not a natural process, it was like a forced instillation, Fang Yuan experienced an indescribable pain.

This pain did not come from his body or soul, it came from his mind.

His mental state had been like a lake with no waves, being tranquil like a giant mirror. But now, there were fierce waves moving roughly.

This was like a process where an infant who only knew how to eat, drink, sleep, and excrete got forced to learn the joy of a child jumping and playing. If infants jumped and played, they would injure themselves.

It was also like a child who thought toys were the most precious thing, but was forcefully instilled the perspective of an adult — that money was the most important thing.

A Gu cultivator's attainment level was very hard to raise. By entering Primordial Domain, Fang Yuan was increasing his attainment level unnaturally and forcefully, it went against the law of nature.

Fang Yuan clenched his teeth and endured it.

There was no trace of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, who had entered earlier. Fang Yuan also did not concentrate on them, he quickly inspected his body and came to a realization.

"Many paths' attainment levels are increasing rapidly! Refinement path is also among them, but rule path's progress is the fastest."

Fang Yuan thought about it and started to move in Primordial Domain.

He used a method which allowed him to fly in Primordial Domain like a free bird.

Primordial Domain crumbled apart wherever he went.

Fang Yuan's heart sank.

Although Primordial Domain was a secluded domain of heaven and earth, it was extremely fragile!

Fang Yuan did not even attack, it was just that he had too many dao marks, even Primordial Domain could not endure it.

Fortunately, before those areas of Primordial Domain collapsed, the attainment levels they contained were transferred into Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan felt a sense of urgency.

"I must find the correct direction quickly."

"If those areas in the Primordial Domain that contain refinement path are destroyed, it will be terrible!"

Fang Yuan was unfamiliar with Primordial Domain, but all kinds of thoughts clashed in his mind and his profound wisdom path attainment allowed him to quickly understand his situation.

Primordial Domain contained the profundities of all paths, any Gu cultivator could benefit from it.

Fang Yuan acutely adjusted his direction and moved in Primordial Domain, gaining a lot of progress in his refinement path attainment level.

His direction was correct, and soon, his rate of progress in refinement path became the highest, among several other paths that were growing too.

Fang Yuan's feeling at this moment could not be expressed in words.

Even though he was feeling incomparable pain and his mental state was unstable, he also felt full and satisfied, at the same time, there was also an increasing 'thirst'!

This 'thirst' was towards knowledge, towards attainment levels.

"It is no wonder that in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, after Ren Zu obtained knowledge, he was not satisfied, he kept taking in more knowledge until his brain reached its limit and exploded."

Fang Yuan felt a sense of resonance with Ren Zu.

"Almost, almost there!" Fang Yuan endured the pain as joy appeared on his face.

His intuition was telling him strongly that he was only a short distance from refinement path supreme grandmaster.

Rumble!

Right at this time, Primordial Domain shook and large areas started collapsing and breaking apart.

Fang Yuan's refinement path attainment level that had been rising stopped abruptly.

"Giant Sun, Star Constellation!!!" Fang Yuan's gaze turned cold and sharp.

He looked far away, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable were fighting.

They selected the location of their fight really well, it was in the main area of refinement path.

Once this portion of Primordial Domain was destroyed, Fang Yuan's refinement path attainment level could not increase anymore.

In previous fights, Fang Yuan had probed many weaknesses of Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court; similarly, details about him were also taken notice of by Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

They were aware that Fang Yuan wanted to break through in refinement path.

Since they came to Primordial Domain a step earlier, how could these two venerables watch without doing anything?

Thus, as they fought, they destroyed the future prospects of Fang Yuan!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable must have taken the initiative to attack, and although Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was in an alliance with Fang Yuan, he was definitely happy to take advantage of the situation.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable saw Fang Yuan's main body, immediately pointing at him.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

Hundreds of deep blue stars shot towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan gave a shout, his whole body emitting seven-colored radiance.

Immortal killer move — Seven Kills Rainbow!

Metal path's yellow light, wood path's jade-green light, water path's light blue hue, fire path's red light, earth path's brown light, wind path's green radiance, and lightning path's deep blue light; seven lights from these seven paths mixed together and shot forward in a drill shape.

Bam!

The seven kills rainbow destroyed most of the stars and continued towards Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Starlight flashed around Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, blocking this killer move. But she still staggered, and her face revealed surprise.

"What killer move is this?"

It was naturally a compound killer move.

This seven kills rainbow was modified from the five technique rainbow. The latter was once used by Fang Yuan in Eastern Sea when the Righteous Qi Alliance attacked Xia clan headquarters to retrieve Xia clan's lost territory.

Five technique rainbow used metal, wood, water, fire, and earth, for a total of five paths. But seven kills rainbow went a step further, containing the swift wind and violent lightning.

It was hard for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to defend against such a killer move.

Because to block this move, she had to simultaneously consider metal, wood, water, fire, earth, wind, and lightning, these amounted to seven paths!

There were many killer moves that seemingly involved many paths, but they were without any substance in essence.

For instance, when Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable fought with Limitless' will in Crazed Demon Cave, he had used a killer move that imitated other paths' strength.

The essence of the killer move was still one path, it was just that it imitated other paths.

In fact, to deal with his killer move, only theft path needed to be targeted.

But seven kills rainbow genuinely contained the strength of seven paths.

With just one exchange with Fang Yuan, even the grand Star Constellation Immortal Venerable felt troubled!

One aspect was the difficulty of defending against compound killer moves, the other aspect was Fang Yuan's vast dao mark accumulation.

He had too many dao marks, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable might have been able to match it before, but the current her had just revived.

The three avatars merged into one, their dao marks were also added together, which became the current Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's foundation.

But clearly, the number of dao marks that Star Constellation had was lower than Fang Yuan.

[1] The Chinese character for situation/thing is made up of truth and emotion. Back

Chapter 2186: Snatching Primordial Domain

Crazed Demon Cave.

Primordial Domain.

Fang Yuan's main body finally fought against a venerable!

Immortal killer move — Sword Tongue Dragon Soul.

Fang Yuan roared again, his body shook and over a hundred evil dragons rapidly condensed around him.

The evil dragons roared and charged towards Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

"Another compound killer move?" Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's pupils shrank slightly, she immediately noted that the evil dragons in front of her contained profundities of at least transformation path and enslavement path.

Fang Yuan's dao mark quantity was horrifying, although Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could fight him head on, that was not her style.

She was a wisdom path supreme grandmaster!

This was true in her previous life, it was also true now.

Her body immediately flickered as the surrounding starlight split into a thousand specks, each of time transformed into one Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

"Hmm?" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun quickly activated his investigative method to distinguish the real body.

Fang Yuan's pupils shrank, but he still ordered the dragons to charge forward.

The dragons fought with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's illusions, instantly, the whole battlefield was turned into a chaotic scene.

The evil dragons bit, swung their tails, stabbed with their horns, or used their claws, some even shot out sharp sword qi with their tongues...

At the start of the fight, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's illusions were caught off-guard and suffered heavy losses.

But not long later, they realized the patterns of these evil dragons, Star Constellation Immortal Venerables stabilized the situation and began to counterattack.

The methods of these Star Constellation illusions were ordinary, each illusion only had one killer move and there were only six kinds of killer moves altogether.

But these Star Constellation illusions had extremely high cooperation, not much inferior to the three avatars.

The Star Constellation illusions used their numerical advantage, about ten illusions would attack one evil dragon and kill it after sacrificing several illusions.

Fang Yuan's evil dragons began to decrease rapidly in number.

"Fang Yuan's sword tongue dragon soul has enslavement path profundity, so they can be controlled. But he is far from being Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's match in terms of wisdom path." Immortal Zombie Giant Sun evaluated inwardly.

"But Fang Yuan knows his strengths and weaknesses as well as the enemy's, it would not be worth the effort if he put his attention on carefully controlling the dragon souls. So he is just activating this move repeatedly."

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun did not interfere for the moment, he just observed from the side.

While observing the battle, he continued to activate his methods. Crimson light flew and wrapped the surrounding areas of Primordial Domain, pulling them into his immortal aperture.

Information was extremely important to Gu cultivators.

Especially when facing an enemy like Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, killer moves were most effective during the first time they were used.

Fang Yuan did not use other methods, he was still activating sword tongue dragon soul without stopping.

Groups of evil dragons that numbered over a hundred each continued to rush to the battlefield.

They were killed by the Star Constellation illusions, but they soon gained the upper hand in terms of overall strength.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was inwardly surprised: "So this move contains soul path as well?"

He saw these evil dragons being annihilated, but gradually, the souls of the evil dragons appeared. At first, these dragon souls were extremely weak, their battle strength was only ten percent of the evil dragons.

But as evil dragons continued to die, the scattered soul path dao marks in the battlefield surged continuously; the dragon soul beasts born from the deaths of these evil dragons also grew increasingly strong.

Twenty percent, forty percent, sixty percent...

The evil dragon souls' battle strength continued to increase, finally defeating the Star Constellation illusions and tilting the battle situation in Fang Yuan's favor.

And when there were only dozens of illusions remaining, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's main body could not remain hidden.

She smiled at Fang Yuan and actually retreated from the battlefield, taking her leave.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly.

From this fight, he gained a deeper understanding of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's nature.

Even though Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had revived and clearly had the battle strength to fight Fang Yuan head on, she did not battle frontally, she was very rational and flexible in thoughts.

It was like how she retreated this time and made Fang Yuan's efforts go to waste.

These soul path dao marks on the battlefield were advantageous to Fang Yuan, but with Star Constellation's casual retreat, Fang Yuan had to give chase, giving up this favorable battlefield.

It was not pleasant at all to fight with such an opponent.

"Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, hold up." Immortal Zombie Giant Sun smiled, magnificent lights appeared and blocked Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

"Good!" Fang Yuan praised, taking the chance to catch up.

It seemed like the alliance agreement between Longevity Heaven and Fang Yuan was still effective.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's choice could be explained easily.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun saw Fang Yuan's battle strength, and adding on the fact that he was still in his immortal zombie body, he regarded Heavenly Court as the main enemy.

Were Fang Yuan to be weaker, he might have been jointly attacked by Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, to get rid of this easiest target and prevent him from obtaining benefits while the two venerables fought.

Fang Yuan fought Star Constellation Immortal Venerable once again, while Immortal Zombie Giant Sun barely made any moves.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable lightly waved her jade-like hands, sending out a flurry of stars.

The stars were extremely fast, whistling through the air as they shot at Fang Yuan's body.

Fang Yuan had tried to dodge them before, but these stars had homing ability, they reached him no matter how he dodged.

Fang Yuan would need a long time to deduce and plan before he could decipher this killer move.

Crack crack.

Soft sounds echoed as the light barrier around Fang Yuan started to break.

This light barrier was a compound killer move as well, it had outstanding defense, but under the continuous attack of the stars, it had already broken several times.

The power of each flying star never changed, but they were tightly connected as a consecutive move.

This was very terrifying.

Suppose that a flying star's power was one, the first star would have the battle strength of one, second would have at least three, third would have six...

Their strength increased progressively, reaching a terrifying level at the later stages.

This was Fairy Ming Hao's combat system.

The barrier of light collapsed, Fang Yuan immediately used a new defensive method, a halo shone above his head.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled. Just like what Heavenly Court's intel described, Fang Yuan was very cautious. After using the defensive killer move a few times, he would change to a new one, afraid that his defensive killer move would be deciphered, which could cause heavy injuries or even death if he was caught off-guard.

In fact, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's plan was exactly this.

However, every time she got some results in her deductions, Fang Yuan would readjust his methods, making her deductions pointless.

"Fang Yuan, you are really well-prepared for this battle, you have been changing your killer moves so frequently, I am really curious how long can you continue this for?"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable spoke while using a killer move.

This wisdom path killer move was formless and invisible. It created a whirlwind out of thin air, but it did not target Fang Yuan, instead targeting the surrounding Primordial Domain.

In an instant, all the areas of Primordial Domain within thousands of steps were emptied by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!

On the other side, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun sent out golden light similarly, absorbing a small area of the Primordial Domain into his aperture.

Fang Yuan's eyes shone with dark light.

These two venerables had extraordinary methods, they had been absorbing Primordial Domain even during the battle.

Fang Yuan's accumulation was much inferior when compared to them.

He had also tried, but did not find an effective method to collect the Primordial Domain, he could only watch as these two made gains.

"Since it is so..."

Fang Yuan resolutely activated a killer move.

Flames flew and lightning shot out.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun had been collecting Primordial Domain when the lightning-fire wave formed by Fang Yuan's killer move swept over and emptied out the areas of Primordial Domain around him.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun failed to gain anything, but he remained silent.

Fang Yuan activated another move.

Strong winds blew, an ice storm filled the area.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was implicated once again, the areas of Primordial Domain he was about to absorb into his immortal aperture were destroyed once again.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun clenched his teeth while taking a look at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan activated another move.

Eerie souls moved and golden light shone, destroying all the surrounding areas of Primordial Domain.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun could not help but glance at each other; the former was no longer smiling, while the latter's eyes were twitching.

"If I can't have it, you can also stop dreaming about it!"

With this thought, Fang Yuan attacked without any restraint.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun needed some time to collect the Primordial Domain, flaws appeared during this process.

Fang Yuan was directly destroying Primordial Domain, which was much faster and more convenient.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was interrupted again and again, but Fang Yuan used the excuse of attacking Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. He did not suffer restrictions from the alliance agreement, and there was no obvious point to criticize.

He was really feeling impatient, as he transmitted his voice to Fang Yuan: "Fang Yuan, let's negotiate. If you block Star Constellation Immortal Venerable while I collect the Primordial Domain, we can split the gains with a seven-three ratio!"

"No, I want half!" Fang Yuan immediately answered, as if he had been waiting for this.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was naturally unwilling: "Without my method, you won't be able to collect even a portion of the Primordial Domain. If you dare to comprehend the Primordial Domain now, you will be met with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's attacks, the risk is too high."

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was not wrong.

It was not difficult to interrupt the instillation of Primordial Domain.

But even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not dare to comprehend Primordial Domain while fighting, and was only trying her best to collect it.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun put forward a fair argument, but Fang Yuan paid him no attention.

Boom...

Lightning exploded and qi waves rose as the surrounding Primordial Domain was once again destroyed by Fang Yuan's killer move.

Primordial Domain might have been a secluded domain of heaven and earth, but it was different from Book Mountain and Dang Hun Mountain, it was fragile.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun gritted his teeth.

Fang Yuan used actions to tell him: It had to be fifty-fifty! If you don't agree, then even you, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, won't get any Primordial Domain.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun could only relent: "Alright, we will split it fifty-fifty!"

Fang Yuan continued: "Giant Sun, can I trouble you to put half of the Primordial Domain in treasure yellow heaven at your own convenience?"

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun could not help but open his eyes wide.

Fang Yuan urged: "Don't worry, with me disturbing her with all my strength, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable will not be able to collect much of Primordial Domain."

These words were a reminder to him: Look, Heavenly Court is still our biggest enemy. Also, weakening Heavenly Court was also Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's intention all along.

"Alright." Immortal Zombie Giant Sun sent half of his Primordial Domain into treasure yellow heaven to express his sincerity.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, attacking Star Constellation Immortal Venerable even more fiercely.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was only one person, she was starting to suffer losses after Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Fang Yuan collaborated to target her.

Chapter 2187: This Rascal Fang Yuan!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable fell into a disadvantage.

Fang Yuan was in charge of disturbing her, while Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was collecting Primordial Domain. Although Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also obtained some with difficulty, her opportunities were decreasing rapidly as she fought with Fang Yuan.

After this situation lasted for a while, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made a decision.

She resolutely activated a killer move, attacking Primordial Domain!

The Primordial Domain's stability was like an avalanche, at first it was only a small piece that got affected, but in just a short while, the collapse became increasingly severe.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun gave a shout, sending out a golden-red aurora light.

He succeeded in obstructing Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's killer move; however, she activated the killer move again.

"Fang Yuan!" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun shouted.

Even without Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's reminder, Fang Yuan was already attacking fiercely to force Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to defend and give up on destroying Primordial Domain.

This time, it was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's turn to use killer moves continuously.

Since the battle started, this was the first time she had taken the initiative to attack!

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's response was not fast enough. Many of these offensive methods were used for the first time by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was not able to effectively block them.

Rumble...

After dozens of moves, Primordial Domain was completely destroyed.

Most of the destruction was done by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

"Star Constellation, you live up to your reputation!" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun praised in amazement.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable saw that her efficiency in collecting Primordial Domain could not compare to Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's joint effort, so she directly attacked Primordial Domain instead.

Such decisiveness and rationality, she was indeed an Immortal Venerable of human history, the second generation Immortal King of Heavenly Court!

"Hmm? This place is..." Fang Yuan's expression was slightly strange.

Primordial Domain was completely destroyed, but he did not fall down from the sky, instead, he found himself in a void.

There was no trace of the worlds of the eighth layer of Crazed Demon Cave.

"This is Crazed Demon Cave's ninth layer!" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun said.

He slowly flew over and stood a hundred steps away from Fang Yuan as they faced Star Constellation Immortal Venerable together.

Previously, Heavenly Court used Thieving Heaven's true inheritance and the captives in Divine Emperor City to lure Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun into taking action, giving them time to seize the Primordial Domain.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Fang Yuan responded extremely quickly, mobilizing all their forces without caring for consequences.

Heavenly Court had experienced the fate war and were no longer in their prime condition, they could not block the joint attack of the two forces.

Since they could not seize it, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could only choose the next best alternative, she directly flew into Primordial Domain and raised her wisdom path to supreme grandmaster attainment level.

However, Fang Yuan, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, and other pseudo venerables also entered Primordial Domain.

The battle situation gradually escaped from Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's grasp, forcing her to destroy the whole of Primordial Domain.

Primordial Domain was not seized by her, it was actually still in the ninth layer. The moment Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, Fang Yuan, and other immortals entered Primordial Domain, they had also entered Crazed Demon Cave's ninth layer!

"The void in this ninth layer is far smaller than the eighth layer. Is this the truthful floating ice depicted in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>?"

Fang Yuan stared at Star Constellation Immortal Venerable while also noticing the mysterious floating ice behind her.

These bluish-white floating pieces of ice were of all sizes and had a huge quantity. They were floating quietly, they did not rotate by themselves, but because of the attractive forces between them, they flew around in groups. All the flying floating ice groups were slowly orbiting around the center.

From afar, these orbiting pieces of truthful floating ice looked like a giant ball on the whole.

The truthful floating ice's orbit was filled with mysterious profundity, Fang Yuan felt dizzy after just taking several glances.

He intuitively sensed that these truthful floating ice pieces were continuing to grow bigger.

"Looks like this formation is the foundation for the construction of the whole of Crazed Demon Cave. Book Mountain and Primordial Domain are the cores that Heavenly Court took out from this formation."

"Amazing, truly incredible!"

"This rank nine formation keeps on orbiting and deducing, these truthful floating ice pieces are its gains. Those dead Gu Immortals and immortal apertures in the eighth layer are the fuel for this formation and also the clues for deductions."

"If so, the derivation Gu recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> and Limitless Demon Venerable's study of eternal life are at the center of the formation?"

Just as Fang Yuan was thinking this, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun shouted in a cold tone.

At the next moment, a luck path killer move pierced through Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable dissipated like a bubble.

Her true body appeared, but it was no longer in front of Fang Yuan, she had already entered the rank nine formation.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's expression sank slightly: "Such a good method, this illusion was destroyed with one touch, but even I was unable to detect it was a fake. If not for a fluctuation in my luck, I would still have no clue. We need to move quickly! Limitless Demon Venerable used everything to arrange Crazed Demon Cave and it has been deducing for over a million years. We can't let these gains go to Heavenly Court."

Why would Fang Yuan hesitate, he immediately moved with Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and arrived at the periphery of the formation.

The two immortals stopped.

"This formation is really terrifying, all the truthful floating ice are formation cores and also the safest places. All the other areas besides them are extremely dangerous. If we stop at other areas, we will be crushed by the formation."

Fang Yuan's heart jumped as he saw this.

This rank nine formation's crushing force came from the fusion of sacrificing countless Gu Immortals and great worlds, even he would not be able to endure it.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun inspected for a bit and jumped on a piece of truthful floating ice.

Be they the leading Star Constellation Immortal Venerable or Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, they both made the same choice. Fang Yuan was naturally going to follow them.

He jumped on an elephant sized truthful floating ice.

The moment he stepped on the floating ice, a strong guilty conscience attacked Fang Yuan's heart, like he was a bandit that had invaded a peaceful village.

Fang Yuan's expression changed slightly as he quickly resisted this strong emotion.

After adapting to it, Fang Yuan jumped to the second truthful floating ice.

This time, an intense sadness engulfed his heart, the intensity was higher than before.

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth and adapted to it with difficulty.

He looked ahead, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun had already jumped to the fifth truthful floating ice, while Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was far ahead, already at the central area of the formation.

"I don't have time!" Fang Yuan was hurried, he quickly jumped to the third floating ice.

The outcome of the fight in the Primordial Domain was not ideal to Fang Yuan.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun were likely to have already regained their supreme grandmaster attainment level, while Fang Yuan's refinement path was still lacking.

However, since the opponent was the grand Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, this outcome was also within Fang Yuan's expectations.

The Primordial Domain's battle was already like that, he could not let these two venerables get their hands on Limitless Demon Venerable's eternal life research results as well.

"Eternal life ... eternal life..." Fang Yuan mumbled.

Reaching eternal life was Fang Yuan's goal and dream, even if he did not obtain it, he could not let it fall into other people's hands.

The deeper into the formation, the higher the intensity of the emotions brought by the truthful floating ice.

These emotions were of all kinds, some were happiness, some were grief, some were sadness, some were anger...

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was still taking the lead.

Her advantage in this formation was extremely obvious!

Firstly, the game of chess back then was the fight between Limitless' will and Star Constellation's will.

Secondly, Heavenly Court had already begun infiltrating three hundred thousand years ago, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's Green Lotus Great World was the best proof.

Lastly, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable cultivated wisdom path.

Wisdom path had three aspects, thought, will, and emotion.

Dealing with emotions and even using them to battle was what wisdom path was most proficient in.

With all these reasons, it was no wonder Star Constellation Immortal Venerable rushed to the formation instead of fighting.

"But...." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable stepped on a truthful floating ice and gazed back, her brows slightly furrowed.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was rushing forward, constantly drawing nearer to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was not surprised about this.

The deeper into the formation, the more terrifying the intensity of the emotions and the more obstruction they created for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun had not hesitated to leave Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace behind to take part in the deductions. He himself had seized Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's Savage Wilderness Great World in his era.

Reckless Savage Demon Venerable came after Limitless Demon Venerable.

When Reckless Savage Demon Venerable entered Crazed Demon Cave, it was over a million years ago!

Thus, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun also had a high understanding of Crazed Demon Cave.

And his luck path methods also helped him to choose the most suitable path.

"But why is Fang Yuan also getting close? It even seems like he is going to surpass Immortal Zombie Giant Sun?" Star Constellation Immortal Venerable frowned.

This was beyond her expectations.

Heavenly Court had naturally handed all the information about Fang Yuan to her.

So, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable knew Fang Yuan very well.

She knew that although Fang Yuan's wisdom path attainment was also extremely high, his specialty was not in deducing but in guarding against others' deductions.

From this, it was clear that though Heavenly Court's expedition against Fang Yuan had failed repeatedly, they had considerable gains as well.

At least, under Heavenly Court's pressure, Fang Yuan had to give up on deductions, the handling of emotions, and other aspects of wisdom path, he could concentrate only on raising his defense against deductions.

Right now was obviously Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's time to profit, but how could Fang Yuan still pursue them closely?

Not only was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable surprised, even Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was astonished.

He watched as Fang Yuan jumped forward rapidly and surpassed him!

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun sensed a peculiar aura from Fang Yuan's body.

Suddenly, he understood the truth.

"Fortitude Gu!" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's mind jolted, gritting his teeth.

He recognized the aura of fortitude Gu.

Fang Yuan had never been good at hiding his aura, and there was also no need to hide it at this moment.

"So it was him!"

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun finally realized that the biggest mastermind who plotted against Hei Lou Lan in Myriad Beast Fusion Color Heaven was Fang Yuan!

"This rascal took away fortitude Gu and ability Gu from Myriad Beast Fusion Color Heaven."

"These two strength path Immortal Gu are at rank eight..."

"Fortitude Gu can suppress emotions, no wonder he is at ease in this formation!"

"Don't tell me, Myriad Beast Fusion Color Heaven is also Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's arrangement to help Fang Yuan?"

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's thoughts started to run amok.

He suddenly had a bad feeling.

"Although I seized Savage Wilderness Great World, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable still arranged for Fang Yuan to obtain fortitude Gu and ability Gu... Then, the portion of Thieving Heaven's true inheritance that I extracted before, could it also be bait arranged by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable?"

Chapter 2188: Bedazzlement

Northern Plains.

Two figures were flying in the air and exchanging killer moves rapidly; air currents and thunder resounded constantly.

Among them, the male immortal who was dressed in a white robe cultivated light path. He had a skinny body and a sharp face, and his eyes were small like beans.

Meanwhile, the female immortal was covered in dark gold armor and was wearing a half mask, her every move was filled with domineering aura.

Besides these two, there were over ten Gu Immortals watching the battle in the surroundings.

"Big brother, quickly kill this bitch!" The female immortal Liu Luo shouted with her gaze fixed on the battlefield.

Beside her were Liu tribe's Gu Immortal elders.

Besides them, other Huang Jin tribe Gu Immortals also came, like Chanyu tribe's Chanyu Xiong and Gong tribe's Gong Tong Kuai.

The male immortal in combat was a famous rank seven expert of Northern Plains' righteous path — Liu Chang.

The female immortal was Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan used Black Moon as her alias and challenged experts everywhere. After defeating Chen Cheng and Yin Wu Que, she continued to challenge lone and demonic immortal experts. She was not defeated even once, her reputation rose rapidly, shocking Northern Plains.

The two siblings Liu Chang and Liu Luo had failed to recruit Yin Wu Que, and even came into conflict with Hei Lou Lan.

To take revenge, Liu Chang publicly challenged Fairy Black Moon.

Once the news got out, it immediately shocked Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

This battle was the result of that!

Immortal killer move — Light Horse Crossing.

Liu Chang activated a killer move, a small steed appeared below his legs, carrying him into the sky with a rapid speed.

This movement killer move was exceptional, it allowed Liu Chang to maintain a fixed distance from Hei Lou Lan throughout the battle.

After the loss against Hei Lou Lan the previous time, Liu Chang sensibly chose a long ranged battle tactic in this battle.

"Big brother, this is it!" Let that bitch suffer more and die in vain later! Hahaha." Liu Luo cheered on Liu Chang with a shrill voice, her laughter was very painful to the ears.

But right at this time, Hei Lou Lan's figure disappeared from her spot.

It was an illusion!

"When did she do it?" Liu Chang was shocked and knew he was tricked, subconsciously dodging.

But Hei Lou Lan's true body immediately appeared behind him.

Bam bam bam...

Fist shadows rained down and enveloped Liu Chang firmly.

Liu Chang screamed while trying his best to activate defensive killer moves to endure the beating.

Liu Luo's laughter stopped abruptly.

Hei Lou Lan's attacks were extremely fierce, even the Gu Immortal spectators felt their eyelids twitch.

"Great!"

"Awesome beating."

"She finally caught this crafty Liu Chang!"

Among the spectators, the lone and demonic immortals cheered and praised.

In this group, besides Chen Cheng, Wu Guang, and Yin Wu Que, there were also many other people.

Some of these people were defeated by Hei Lou Lan, while some heard of Hei Lou Lan's deeds and followed her of their own accord.

"Lady Black Moon has the upper hand." Wu Guang transmitted his voice while smiling.

"Don't you feel that Lady Black Moon has grown stronger recently? Now that I think of it, Lady Black Moon has been challenging others continuously, her battle strength has been rising during these challenges. Brother Wu, could it be that you don't sense it?" Yin Wu Que was bewildered.

Wu Guang mumbled, shaking his head and transmitting his voice: "I also noticed it. But how could there be such rapid progress and growth in this world? It might be that Lady Black Moon was hiding her strength before, or maybe she had been in closed cultivation all this time and started to connect her methods with the increase in her battle experience, thus, it caused us to feel that her battle strength is increasing rapidly."

Yin Wu Que nodded and was about to speak, when there was a change in the battle.

Gu Immortal Liu Chang was indeed worthy of being a famous expert in Northern Plains, after some efforts, he finally escaped from Hei Lou Lan's attack range.

Hei Lou Lan naturally did not want to let him go and immediately gave chase.

But Liu Chang suddenly stopped, smiling darkly towards her: "Black Moon, you have fallen into my trap!"

Immortal killer move — Bedazzlement!

In an instant, intense light exploded, enveloping the whole battlefield.

The Gu Immortal spectators closed their eyes immediately, even Hei Lou Lan shut her eyes subconsciously.

But when she opened her eyes again, the scene was still completely white.

She was struck by the killer move bedazzlement, her vision turned into a scene of white and she could no longer see.

"Damn it, Liu Chang actually learned this killer move."

"No wonder he was not afraid to openly challenge Lady Black Moon!"

"This move is Liu tribe's trump card method. Once a Gu cultivator is hit with this move, it will be extremely difficult for them to recover unless they use Liu tribe's special recovery method."

Many lone and demonic immortals had changed expressions, the mood immediately became heavy.

This battle was not just a simple fight between Liu Chang and Hei Lou Lan.

In the current situation, this battle already held much political meaning.

Fairy Black Moon, who had no roots or background, represented the lone immortal faction. While Liu Chang represented Northern Plains' righteous path.

Ever since the fate war, Northern Plains' Longevity Heaven had been actively uniting Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

Lone and demonic experts like Yin Wu Que were actively recruited by the Huang Jin tribes, and the recruitment process was extremely forceful.

So be it for the few lone immortals who were willing to accept this, however, the main thing was that most of the lone immortals and demonic immortals rejected this. But being lone forces, they did not want to offend those Northern Plains righteous path forces, so they kept silent even though they were furious.

Under this situation, Hei Lou Lan's appearance was like a rallying banner for these Gu Immortals.

Hei Lou Lan dared to issue challenges everywhere without fearing the Huang Jin tribes, which gave these lone and demonic immortals a huge boost of morale.

Especially now that Snowy Mountain blessed land was destroyed and the demonic head Old Ancestor Xue Hu had hidden himself, the lone and demonic cultivators needed a leader.

Because of this, Wu Guang, Yin Wu Que, and others followed Hei Lou Lan on their own initiative. Many lone and demonic immortals came to observe this battle and support Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan was struck by the killer move and could not see anything. These Gu Immortals became extremely anxious and worried.

Liu Chang easily retreated, smiling.

Immortal killer move — Vitality Glow.

His injuries began to heal slowly.

Immortal killer move — Gleaming Light.

Light shone around him, like countless gleaming fish scales.

"This is not good!" Chen Cheng frowned, "This move restricts investigative methods."

Yin Wu Que and Wu Guang stopped conversing secretly as they fixed their gazes on the battlefield.

Even if Gu Immortals could not see, they had all kinds of investigative methods. But with Liu Chang using this killer move, other investigative methods might be useless.

Since she could not see, Hei Lou Lan simply closed her eyes.

She was not panicking, instead, she sighed lightly: "Liu Chang, oh Liu Chang, it is such a pity, you missed your final chance."

Liu Chang was stunned before scoffing: "Fairy Black Moon, who are you trying to bluff? You have already lost, how can you counter my Liu tribe's bedazzlement killer move in this battle? There is no use in stalling for time!"

Hei Lou Lan did not retort.

She replied to him with her actions.

A killer move was activated.

Immortal killer move — Dark Capital Strength Biao!

A black tiger condensed into solid form.

"This move again?" A trace of solemness flashed on Liu Chang's face.

"It is different now!" Yin Wu Que's eyes shone, "This dark gold tiger seems to have grown wings?!"

"What? I didn't see it clearly." Wu Guang quickly replied.

The moment the totem black tiger condensed, it disappeared, many including Wu Guang did not see it properly.

"Where is it? Does it have the ability to hide itself?" Liu Chang's expression changed slightly as he activated investigative methods.

But at the next moment, his pupils shrank to pin size, his face was filled with shock and horror.

The giant dark gold tiger appeared behind him!

Whoosh.

The tiger swatted, sending Liu Chang flying like a rubber ball.

Howling winds rang past Liu Chang's ears while his vision spun like a whirlpool, he felt terrified internally.

That attack had huge strength, almost destroying his defensive killer move.

"It is not that the black tiger has a concealment method, the reason is its speed, it is too fast, simply too fast to react to!"

The dark gold tiger's speed was so fast that it had already surpassed the limit of what the Gu Immortals' naked eyes could perceive. It was like a phantom, appearing and disappearing suddenly.

Every time it appeared, it sent Liu Chang flying.

Liu Chang was completely at a disadvantage with no strength to retaliate.

If he could use light horse crossing, he might be able to escape for some time. But right now, he had fallen into a passive position and had to focus all his strength in maintaining his defensive methods, otherwise, he might be turned into meat paste by the black tiger.

Rumble!

The black tiger's strike sent Liu Chang flying to the ground.

Dust clouds rose, a deep crater formed, Liu Chang remained unmoving, he had fallen unconscious.

"Brother!" Liu Luo screamed shrilly, pointing at Hei Lou Lan, "You bitch, you killed my brother. How dare you do this! I want you to die, I want you to die!"

She was about to charge forward but was stopped firmly by a Liu tribe elder.

Right at this time, a feeling of joy spread in her heart.

Liu Luo was stunned.

She felt incredulous at herself: "Big brother is in such a state but I feel happy?!"

The other righteous path immortals also had a change in their expressions, they were all feeling happiness.

Gong Tong Kuai slightly shook his head to calm himself, saying in a quiet voice: "Liu tribe's fairy, please don't be anxious, Brother Liu is not dead yet."

"Calm down, so many people are looking, don't cause Liu tribe to lose face!" A Liu tribe elder berated and flew towards the battlefield.

He cupped his fists towards Hei Lou Lan: "Fairy Black Moon, you have won this battle."

He had just said that, when he almost started crying.

An intense wave of sadness filled his heart.

Hei Lou Lan nodded: "Okay, so what about this battle's wager?"

She did not feel well either.

First was the baffling happiness, followed by the intense sadness, what in the world was going on?

Liu tribe's elder forcefully calmed down, replying to Hei Lou Lan: "It has been sent to treasure yellow heaven."

Since Liu Chang lost, and with so many people watching, Liu tribe's elder had to openly send a considerable amount of cultivation resources to treasure yellow heaven.

Treasure yellow heaven had treasure light to distinguish value of the items, at the same time, it also showed Liu tribe's openness and upright handling of the loss.

The immortals present used their Gu worms to connect to treasure yellow heaven, they saw Liu tribe's wager indeed.

"That secluded domain of heaven and earth is still there!"

"More accurately, this is a portion of the Primordial Domain."

"I wonder which great expert is openly transacting the Primordial Domain!"

The Gu Immortals' attention was drawn to another direction.

Not long ago, a portion of the Primordial Domain had appeared in treasure yellow heaven, shocking the entire five regions' Gu Immortal world.

Yin Wu Que shouted to bring back the attention of the immortals: "According to the agreement, please dispel the bedazzlement killer move on Fairy Black Moon's body."

"Naturally." Liu tribe's elder used a killer move straightforwardly, restoring Hei Lou Lan's vision.

Hei Lou Lan slightly nodded at the Liu tribe elder, and withdrew the dark capital strength biao which was beside Liu Chang.

This totem killer move had gone through modifications, its battle strength surged and it had already become her unique method!

Chen Cheng breathed a sigh of relief when he saw this: "Lady Black Moon's reputation is going to rise even higher."

Liu Luo carried Liu Chang, while saying with hatred: "Black Moon, don't be pleased with yourself. Our righteous path is filled with experts, you might have won against brother by chance, but can you win against others? Let's not talk of others, just Chu tribe's first supreme elder Chu Du is someone you won't be able to surpass."

However, right at this time, an intense emotion of affection rose in her heart.

Liu Luo's expression turned twisted immediately.

"What's going on! Why do I have such a strong feeling of affection when I look at this Black Moon whore?"

Hei Lou Lan did not feel well either, but her expression did not change as she sneered: "Chu Du? I have heard of his name, he also cultivates strength path. I am challenging him next!"

The lone and demonic immortals' expressions changed.

Chapter 2189: The Answer To Eternal Life

Crazed Demon Cave.

Ninth layer.

Four Gu Immortals arrived at the periphery of the Crazed Demon formation.

"This is the truthful floating ice?" Zhan Bu Du's eyebrows rose.

"Seems like it is not easy to enter deep into this formation." Qi Sea Ancestor was solemn. Unlike the main body, they did not have the assistance of fortitude Gu.

"Star Constellation is at the front, nearest to the center of the formation. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable is second, while Fang Yuan is the last." Lu Wei Yin's heart tensed up as he looked ahead.

Fang Yuan did not have the upper hand, so Lu Wei Yin had to do his best to help him!

Demon Immortal Qi Jue stared at the formation in front of him, he mumbled softly as if recalling something of the past: "Limitless, this fellow..."

He leaped forward and stepped on a piece of truthful floating ice.

The other three immortals glanced at each other before moving as well.

The record in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> was true, the pieces of the truthful floating ice were of different sizes and shapes in the eyes of different people, the emotional impact they felt were different as well.

Because of this, Gu Immortals could not move forward in a group. The best method was to move alone, choosing the floating ice most suitable for oneself.

Fang Yuan had been maintaining the activation of fortitude Gu.

This Gu was only at rank eight level, while this Crazed Demon formation was as high as rank nine.

The deeper he went into the formation, the stronger the emotions he felt. When he had just activated fortitude Gu, these emotions could be ignored and he did not feel anything.

But now, Fang Yuan felt like when he had just stepped on the formation and started probing it.

As for Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, after these two recognized Fang Yuan's method, they brought out their trump cards.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun activated familial emotion Gu, sharing his emotions to others.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable brought out a mysterious secluded domain of heaven and earth!

This secluded domain looked like a cage as well as a lantern, Fang Yuan could not help but recall a certain chapter in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

The two venerables' foundation was much deeper than Fang Yuan's.

They had also made ample preparations for Crazed Demon Cave.

Thus, Fang Yuan still fell back to the last position among the three.

Fang Yuan did not give up, continuing to move forward while gritting his teeth.

The situation was getting worse.

The emotional impacts became stronger, shaking his mind and spirit.

But Fang Yuan was happy instead.

Since he was receiving such fierce emotional impacts here, the two venerables who were ahead would face even fiercer emotions.

Fang Yuan's perseverance soon got favorable results.

The leading Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was moving increasingly slower, she needed to rest for a long while after stepping on a piece of the truthful floating ice before she could move forward.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's speed became slow, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was the same.

Gradually, the distance between the three Gu Immortals started to shorten.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable often looked back, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun who was in the middle also stopped often and observed Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Fang Yuan. This was a difficult journey, the three immortals fully realized each other's vast tenacity and patience.

After this situation continued for a while, a change occurred.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable suddenly spat out a mouthful of blood, she collapsed on the truthful floating ice.

Her body flashed with deep blue starlight.

After the starlight dimmed, it actually split into three, becoming three avatars again!

"Could it be that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's revival is not complete and she has only revived temporarily? The stable state is still in the form of three pseudo venerables?" Fang Yuan's thoughts shook.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun felt an urge to take action: "A chance!"

He gritted his teeth and persevered, slowly surpassing Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation's three avatars stopped on the same truthful floating ice, they were trying to recuperate as soon as possible.

When Fang Yuan overtook them, he hesitated for a moment.

Should he take advantage of this situation?

Fang Yuan quickly suppressed this impulse.

Right now, he was deep in Limitless' Crazed Demon formation, if he were to even make an attack, he might trigger Limitless' countermeasures. His situation might be even more severe than the Qi Sea clone's.

Moreover, if Fang Yuan were to fight with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, would it not be giving an advantage to Immortal Zombie Giant Sun?

Look at Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, he directly went to the center of the formation without paying attention to Star Constellation's three avatars.

"If regaining supreme grandmaster attainment level gave these venerables the initiative, then gaining Limitless Demon Venerable's deduction results might let the winner rise above other venerables!"

Fang Yuan was increasingly certain of this speculation.

"It is time!" Fang Yuan stopped on a truthful floating ice piece, enduring the vast emotional impact as he activated an immortal killer move.

Immortal killer move — Calm and Steady!

The killer move's effect was immediate, the vast and strong emotions that were crushing Fang Yuan and almost destroyed his mental state disappeared almost completely.

Fang Yuan possessed countless Immortal Gu recipes along with just as many killer moves.

This calm and steady killer move was part of them.

This move required two main cores, calm Gu and suppression Gu.

Fang Yuan did not have calm Gu and was unable to refine immortal level calm Gu, but he had fortitude Gu. Previously, Fang Yuan had been moving while modifying the killer move, and was finally able to use this move now.

As for suppression Gu, Fang Yuan had it.

Speaking of which, he needed to thank Heavenly Court.

Before the fate war, Fang Yuan had fought several battles with Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals in the River of Time. In one such battle, Fang Yuan destroyed the river suppression lotus sealing formation, obtaining suppression Gu from it.

Suppression Gu was rank eight, fortitude Gu was also rank eight.

The killer move with two rank eight cores would naturally have stronger effect than just fortitude Gu alone.

Fang Yuan's speed increased again!

However, he had already been somewhat far from Immortal Zombie Giant Sun before, so despite trying his best, Fang Yuan could not catch up to him.

"I did not expect Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to be the first to reach the center!" Lu Wei Yin heaved a deep sigh.

Under Fang Yuan's, Star Constellation's three avatars, and other pseudo venerables' gazes, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun suddenly stopped.

He stopped on the truthful floating ice that could be said to be one step away from the largest truthful floating ice at the center.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun showed hesitation at this moment.

What was he hesitating for?

While he was hesitating, Fang Yuan caught up.

"Fang Yuan, it is somewhat strange here." Immortal Zombie Giant Sun spoke.

Ever since he and Fang Yuan entered the formation, they were competing secretly. The mood between the two became strained, this was their first conversation.

Fang Yuan's eyes shone as he carefully sized up the truthful floating ice in front of him. For a moment, he was unable to find any clues.

But he did not take a risk to step forward.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was the best model.

He was so close to success, but he still stopped. It could be seen that there was definitely something strange.

"It is odd indeed." Fang Yuan nodded, revealing an expression of realization.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was slightly surprised. The reason he stopped was because his luck path investigative killer move showed a slight fluctuation, making him feel something wrong, but he was unable to tell what it was. However, looking at Fang Yuan's expression, did he realize a crucial point?

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun had been putting a lot of attention on Fang Yuan.

In his view: Fang Yuan was chosen by heaven's will, he had talent that ordinary people could not match. To cause the destruction of fate Gu, many venerables helped Fang Yuan. Moreover, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, and Reckless Savage Demon Venerable were still helping him now!

Even if Immortal Zombie Giant Sun did not think highly of Fang Yuan, he could not disregard the other venerables.

So, he did not find it strange for Fang Yuan to see a crucial clue when he could not.

"Please enlighten me on what you found out." Immortal Zombie Giant Sun said.

Fang Yuan was surprised, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun had the dignity of a grand venerable, but he actually took the initiative to ask for guidance with no mental obstruction.

However, Fang Yuan had actually not noticed anything.

Therefore, he first looked back at Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Those three fairies were still at the original spot, resting with their eyes closed.

Then, Fang Yuan looked at Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, smiling: "The eternal life research results are not easily obtained, but we can share them. Giant Sun, how do you want to pay?"

No matter what the oddity was, he would first extort some benefits from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable!

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's eyes shone, he was just about to speak when a person actually came out of the truthful floating ice at the center.

"Huh?" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's attention was immediately attracted.

Fang Yuan was also stunned.

Afterwards, Star Constellation's three avatars, Lu Wei Yin and the rest also discovered this abnormality.

A rank seven Gu Immortal came out of the truthful floating ice.

Fang Yuan even recognized this rank seven Gu Immortal!

It was Not Immortal of the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics!

The Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics were wisdom path Gu Immortal Secret Schemer, earth path Gu Immortal Pang Shan, and rule path Gu Immortal Not Immortal respectively.

These three lived in Crazed Demon Cave, they had been trying to find a way to enter the deepest layer of Crazed Demon Cave, to obtain the secret of eternal life.

Regarding this goal, they and Fang Yuan were kindred spirits.

The Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics did not have enough strength, they could not even enter the eighth layer, so they took in the strength path Gu Immortal Chu Du. Chu Du then invited Fang Yuan, which was how Fang Yuan entered Crazed Demon Cave.

Later, to prepare for the fate war, Fang Yuan came to Crazed Demon Cave to invite the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics to take part in the battle.

The Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics agreed, but they were not seen throughout the fate war and even after it. Thus, they lost contact with Fang Yuan.

Who could have thought that Not Immortal would actually appear here!

Not Immortal looked at Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and was stunned, immediately showing a vigilant expression. He did not recognize Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, but from the terrifying aura, he knew this immortal zombie could not be provoked.

He then looked at Fang Yuan, his brows rose as he revealed joy: "Fang Yuan, you are finally here!"

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's mind jolted, he immediately turned around to look at Fang Yuan: "Fang Yuan, you made such deep arrangements, I am in admiration."

Fang Yuan shook his head: "How could I possibly arrange this? Not Immortal, I wonder if Secret Schemer and Pang Shan..."

Not Immortal immediately replied: "They are inside."

He then showed an ashamed expression: "The three of us agreed to your request to participate in the fate war and fight Heavenly Court. But that day, there was suddenly a change in Crazed Demon Cave, and us three were pulled into here. With Limitless Demon Venerable's will's guidance, we understood the full details."

"Because us three lived here for a long time, our sincerity was finally seen by Lord Limitless' will. He arranged for us to be here to cooperate with the formation, by controlling practice Gu to carve this piece of truthful floating ice."

"Once all the worlds in the eighth layer are merged into one, they will disappear completely and turn into clues and energy for this Crazed Demon formation's derivation. Then, we will finish carving this truthful floating ice and find the method of eternal life!"

Chapter 2190: Star Constellation's Scheme

"Method of eternal life?" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's eyes shined with bright light.

Not Immortal did not hide anything. The immortals present on the scene were all peak experts of the current five regions, they all heard it.

In an instant, the immortals' hearts pounded with excitement.

Gu Immortals could obtain longevity, but they were bound by lifespan, Fate, and other restrictions. Even though Fate was destroyed now, and lifespan restrictions were greatly relaxed, they could still be killed by a stronger enemy.

Eternal life was absolutely greater than longevity.

Speaking of longevity, the ten thousand years old turtle living in the sea could also be considered to have longevity, but it could not be considered to have eternal life.

Eternal life meant that everyone and everything could not threaten the individual's existence.

It meant complete invincibility.

Be it time, space, or living beings, none could threaten an entity with eternal life.

The concept of eternal life was paramount and above all.

Even venerables only had longevity and could not be said to have eternal life! Especially now that multiple venerables existed in the same era, they threatened each other's existence.

Shortly afterwards, there was commotion ahead. Secret Schemer also came out from the central truthful floating ice.

Secret Schemer cultivated wisdom path, after seeing the situation in the formation, his mind shook as he quickly said: "Us three need to maintain the activation of practice Gu at all times, there has to be someone activating it and carving this truthful floating ice piece continuously."

"It is still too early now."

"It is not ready yet. The great worlds in the eighth layer are still not destroyed, so many lifeforms are still living."

Secret Schemer then urged: "Fang Yuan, I am aware of your goal. But right now, it is best if you don't step in here. Us three have already used all kinds of methods, after we stepped on this truthful floating ice piece, we are unable to get off. That is, unless the derivation is complete or the formation is destroyed!"

"He is right!" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun nodded.

After he stopped, he had been secretly activating methods to investigate and deduce.

He still needed some time, but with Secret Schemer's reply, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun checked it and realized Secret Schemer was not lying.

Secret Schemer was solemn, but showed anticipation as well as resolution, continuing: "The most important thing now is to protect this formation and hasten Limitless Demon Venerable's arrangements, letting this formation complete its derivation. Fang Yuan, we have the same goals, please protect the formation and guard against all these malicious characters. The three of us will stake everything including our lives to maintain the usage of practice Gu."

They did not know Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's true identity, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also split into three avatars, their intel seemed to stop at the period before the fate war.

Fang Yuan's thoughts moved rapidly, he first nodded towards Secret Schemer before looking back at Star Constellation's three avatars with a solemn expression.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun sighed and turned to look at Star Constellation's three avatars as well: "I don't want us to be schemed against."

The moment he said that, Ming Hao, Yu Xiu, and Feng Ya opened their eyes.

Starlight emerged as the three fairies converged once again.

At the next moment, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable appeared.

"Rise." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable said softly.

There was a sudden change in Crazed Demon formation, the truthful floating ice's orbiting speed became faster and seemed to trap Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun inside.

Star Constellation's will and Limitless' will had been deriving heaven path research results using their game in Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court had infiltrated Crazed Demon formation deeply, they were able to take out the cores, Book Mountain and Primordial Domain, so how could they not know about the situation of Crazed Demon formation's derivation?

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used this to exploit Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's lack of information. Her main body personally moved to lure Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun deep into Crazed Demon formation.

Be it Primordial Domain or Crazed Demon formation, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Fang Yuan would not let Star Constellation Immortal Venerable obtain either easily.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used this to trap Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun.

Crazed Demon formation changed, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Fang Yuan quickly tried to get back.

However, Crazed Demon formation had become a lot more dangerous than before. Truthful floating ice pieces even collided with each other, if they were careless and fell off the floating ice, they would be crushed to a pulp by the terrifying strength of the formation.

Even if they wanted to jump to a different floating ice, they would need to deduce and wait till the formless force between the floating ice pieces weakened before they could take the risk.

Fang Yuan was already deeply in danger as he hopped over several truthful floating ice pieces, he turned around and inquired loudly: "Secret Schemer, can you three control this formation?"

Secret Schemer shook his head: "We three are only in charge of activating practice Gu."

Not Immortal was pale: "As expected of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, she actually infiltrated the formation to such a degree that she can even be considered half the formation's owner. She activated the formation but did not influence its derivation, instead she is accelerating it; Limitless Demon Venerable's arrangements will not trigger from this!"

Secret Schemer replied in a loud voice: "Please don't destroy these truthful floating ice pieces. They are all a part of the formation, this concerns the success or failure of the derivation. If you two make a move, you will definitely cause Limitless Demon Venerable's retaliative method to trigger!"

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's expression became unsightly.

"Friends, take a rest. We will exchange pointers later." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled and retreated after leaving behind these words.

Lu Wei Yin and the other pseudo venerables instantly prepared themselves for this huge enemy.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable ignored them, she flew out of the formation and disappeared into the void.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was worthy of being the number one person in wisdom path. Currently, Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun were unable to get free, pseudo venerables like Qi Sea and Qi Jue would not be able to obstruct Star Constellation Immortal Venerable even if they hurried back to the eighth layer.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had infiltrated Crazed Demon formation to such a shocking degree. Once she unifies the great worlds in the eighth layer and gains a hold of all the sources of fuel and clues for Crazed Demon formation's derivation, her grasp over Crazed Demon formation would rise massively!

It was possible that Crazed Demon formation might even change owners!

One could easily fall into a trap if they were careless when fighting against wisdom path Gu Immortals. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's scheme was the same, it progressed step by step and was interlinked with each step as it latched onto the enemy's weaknesses; even Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun could only fall into the trap unknowingly.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was solemn as he looked at Fang Yuan: "The situation is urgent, I wonder if Friend Fang Yuan has a good plan?"

Fang Yuan shook his head, sighing indifferently: "This Crazed Demon Cave battle has ended in Heavenly Court's victory. They have prepared for many years and spent a lot of energy, and with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable leading them, it is only natural for them to gain victory. Looks like Heavenly Court is still going to lead the five regions for a long time. But as long as I have a breath left in me, I won't let Heavenly Court have an easy time."

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun stared at Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan did not look at him, he was continuously deducing the violent formation, looking like he wanted to retreat.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun gritted his teeth before laughing and shaking his hand: "Friend Fang Yuan, it is too early to be discouraged, please look at my method!"

At the next moment, golden light spread out from Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's body.

The threads of golden light shone on the surrounding truthful floating ice pieces, constantly dying the floating ice pieces with a golden hue.

At the same time, a majestic rank eight Immortal Gu House flew over from outside the formation.

It was Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace!

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace stopped outside the formation for a while before entering the formation directly.

Lu Wei Yin and the rest exclaimed in surprise, thinking that Immortal Zombie Giant Sun wanted to break out forcibly.

However, Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace safely entered and orbited alongside other truthful floating ice pieces. It acted like a piece of truthful floating ice as well, just that its appearance was somewhat strange.

"Friend Giant Sun, you have a great method!" Fang Yuan could not help as he praised.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun snorted: "Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could infiltrate the formation, but my luck path methods are also not inferior. It is just that before the formation stops, I won't be able to take out Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace. Let's leave quickly!"

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace took part in the operation of Crazed Demon formation, so Immortal Zombie Giant Sun could also influence this formation now.

He also copied Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and accelerated the formation; at the same time, he made a way out conveniently.

Relying on this, he and Fang Yuan retreated together.

As for Lu Wei Yin, Qi Sea and the rest, they were also brought away by Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun to the eighth layer.

In this while of delay, the combat in the eighth layer had almost stopped completely.

Heavenly Court was victorious!

Only half of Longevity Heaven's Eight Extremities remained, Bing Sai Chuan was also severely injured.

The casualties on Fang Yuan's side were even more severe. Experts like Xiao He Jian and Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch had perished.

"Star Constellation!" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun shouted with fury as he charged forward.

This time, he was much more active than in the Primordial Domain.

Fang Yuan moved right behind him.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable remained at her spot and did not evade.

The other immortals quickly got out of the way in panic.

Boom boom boom!

The three sided battle erupted once again.

Chapter 2191: Fighting And Entering The Immortal Graveyard

Rumble...

Thunder rumbled ceaselessly. Immortal Zombie Giant Sun breathed out countless golden rays; Star Constellation Immortal Venerable emitted beautiful starlight; Fang Yuan's killer moves engulfed the battlefield.

Worlds shook like a huge pancake, mountains and rivers continued to be destroyed completely.

In such a battlefield, the three great worlds became food on a chopping board.

Fang Yuan breathed out indifferently; countless sword qi flew out like lumps of clouds, blocking the starlight. He then pushed with his hand as another killer move shot out like a divine wind that roared like dragons or tigers.

Fang Yuan was not able to do anything more than that in combat.

He had too many dao marks, his killer moves were also too powerful. He could only choose the weakest among those to use.

In fact, although the fight between the three was filled with explosions, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable were also like Fang Yuan, they were holding back.

This was not Primordial Domain.

They could show their skills fully in Primordial Domain, but this was the eighth layer. Crazed Demon formation still needed the great worlds to act as clues and fuel, if this place was destroyed, it would definitely trigger Limitless Demon Venerable's retaliative measures.

"But it doesn't matter, we only need to restrain Star Constellation Immortal Venerable." Fang Yuan was happy to accept this outcome.

Both him and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun were delayed in Crazed Demon formation, resulting in Heavenly Court's victory in the fight between the great worlds.

With their return now, another change emerged in the overall battle situation.

Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun joined hands to obstruct Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, while Zhan Bu Du and the rest counterattacked.

Qi waves surged as Demon Immortal Qi Jue ran rampant in the battlefield.

The phantom image of the damaged Xi Land appeared above his head, facing Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch and Shabi Ninety-five once again.

Shabi Ninety-five roared towards the sky as it charged into the battle.

Immortal killer move — Xi Xi!

Demon Immortal Qi Jue was already prepared, immediately using his strongest method. Shabi Ninety-five's qi path killer move was absorbed by Xi Land, increasing Demon Immortal Qi Jue's foundation.

Shabi Ninety-five got a huge fright, retreating quickly.

If not for Xi Land being damaged and only thirty percent of it remaining, even some parts of Shabi Ninety-five's body would have been devoured.

"Senior, let me lend you a hand!" At the crucial moment, an Immortal Gu House in the shape of a tombstone flew over.

It was Gu Yue Fang Zheng in Demon Judgment Board.

Immortal killer move — Blood Extraction Light!

A scarlet blood light pillar pierced the skies and shot towards Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

"If not for my Xi Land being damaged and only thirty percent of it remaining..." Demon Immortal Qi Jue flew away, dodging this vast attack.

Right at this time, a qi wall suddenly spread out and seemed to connect heaven and earth, it suppressed Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals.

Qi Sea Ancestor had made his move.

There was similarly a secluded domain of heaven and earth above his head, it was Hu Land.

Using Hu Land as the core, his various qi path killer moves had boundless might and unparalleled vastness.

Qi wall killer move was originally only limited to defending, but Qi Sea Ancestor did the opposite, spreading it to entrap enemies.

Even Demon Immortal Qi Jue was surprised at such power.

He took several glances at Hu Land specially, commenting inwardly: "Truly the secluded domain of heaven and earth that is comparable to Xi Land. It is just that Xi Land is good at absorbing, while Hu Land is specialized in releasing. If both lands were gathered and used together in a complete circulation..."

Boom boom boom.

On the other side, Zhan Bu Du wore the blood-red cape and moved like a flash of red lightning.

Everywhere he went, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were beaten badly.

Qing Chou was already killed by Qi Sea Ancestor's Hu elevation, even if it was revived, it would need to recuperate for a long time in Divine Emperor City, and would not be able to participate in the battle for this period of time.

Without Qing Chou and the fact that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was unable to use her full strength, the bulky Zhan Bu Du once again became a headache for Heavenly Court!

Zhan Bu Du tore through the sky, closing in on Duke Mei.

"Duke Mei, careful!" Duke Tong shouted while hurrying from afar.

Duke Mei shouted with fury: "Junior, don't be arrogant!"

He activated his strongest method, his eyebrows and hair fluttered and grew tens of feet long.

His snow white hair could become hard and soft, it was used for both attack and defense. The skillful series of moves even immobilized the violently charging Zhan Bu Du.

Zhan Bu Du only felt that he could not use his strength. His violent force was diverted and dispelled, it was very stifling.

He immediately opened his mouth and roared, yellow lightning erupted from his roar, destroying the countless hair in his surroundings like they were dry twigs.

A part of the incomplete freedom transformation was thunder rush yellow bird transformation. This move was a fierce and powerful method that shot yellow lightning, its power was magnified several times in Zhan Bu Du's hands.

Zhan Bu Du broke through the obstacles and arrived before Duke Mei, directly punching ahead.

Duke Mei's killer move was broken, the backlash caused him to reveal a weakness. He dodged a second late as the punch broke his head like a watermelon, his brain matter splattering everywhere.

Duke Mei died but his phantom aperture that contained all kinds of Gu worms, immortal essence, and immortal essence stones flew towards the immortal graveyard.

Zhan Bu Du tried to catch it but the phantom aperture passed through his palm like an illusion.

Seeing Duke Mei dying right before him, Duke Tong shouted furiously: "Demon, you will pay with your life!"

His muscles that were bulging and shining with brass luster rained down punches after punches. Every punch broke through the sound barrier and had horrifying momentum.

Zhan Bu Du laughed fiercely: "Come at me."

He charged head-on and fought Duke Tong in close combat without dodging.

Bam bam bam!

Punches and kicks interchanged, Zhan Bu Du just attacked without defending. Duke Tong's punches struck his body, the pain made Zhan Bu Du attack even more wildly.

Soon, Duke Tong was unable to hold on and fell into disadvantage.

Heavenly Court Gu Immortals hurried over to reinforce him, using all kinds of killer moves to attack Zhan Bu Du.

Zhan Bu Du's movements slowed down immediately as he was attacked by lightning, golden spears, and so on.

His robust body shook slightly, he endured it all and grabbed Duke Tong's hand.

"You can't run away!" Zhan Bu Du laughed malevolently, exerting strength in his hand.

Crack, Duke Tong's large and rough arm was broken completely!

Duke Tong shouted in pain, his leg kicked like a whip, creating countless leg shadows that drowned Zhan Bu Du.

Zhan Bu Du's eyes shone with a fierce light as he punched Duke Tong's chest.

The two immortals staked their lives in attacking the other, blood and flesh splattered everywhere.

Duke Tong kicked Zhan Bu Du's two shoulders again and again, Zhan Bu Du's neck and face turned purple from a lack of blood flow. While his rib bones were shattered, his heart that had no protection was also destroyed by Zhan Bu Du!

Duke Tong's heart was destroyed, but he still roared and continued to attack.

Zhan Bu Du gave an evil grin, he stretched out his hands like a bear and clasped Duke Tong's head.

Zhan Bu Du pressed viciously; first, he pressed his thumbs into Duke Tong's eyes, squeezing the eyeballs till they burst. Shortly after, with a crisp crack, Duke Tong's head broke into pieces.

Finally, Zhan Bu Du clenched his fingers, crushing Duke Tong's brains, his face, and the crushed head together.

Only then did Duke Tong's attacks stop, his body fell while his phantom aperture flew away with his Immortal Gu.

Zhan Bu Du's gaze was vicious as he followed the phantom aperture, his gaze landing on the immortal graveyard.

Just as he was about to charge into the immortal graveyard, an Immortal Gu House flew over and blocked his path.

Divine Emperor City!

Zhan Bu Du showed a solemn expression, he restrained his fearless momentum slightly.

After all, Divine Emperor City had the strength of painting path, Zhan Bu Du could not defend against it; if he was careless, he would also be captured and sealed in painting world by Divine Emperor City.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable resisted Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Fang Yuan while observing the whole battlefield, a trace of worry showed up on her face.

Heavenly Court lacked manpower. They could have the upper hand if they just fought Fang Yuan or Longevity Heaven. But when these two sides allied, they were in disadvantage.

Especially now that she was tied up and Heavenly Court lacked pseudo venerable battle strength, Heavenly Court was being beaten back by Zhan Bu Du and the rest's crazed attacks.

Immortal killer move — Humble Reciprocation!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable moved her left palm, a small phantom image of Book Mountain floated on it.

Thousands of killer moves bloomed like fireworks or like a chaotic tidal wave as they poured out in a torrent.

These killer moves had their respective target, each targeting their original owners. Demon Immortal Qi Jue, Qi Sea Ancestor, Zhan Bu Du, and the rest were 'taken care of', they had no choice but to divert their attention and focus on defending.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was also engulfed by golden rays, he was also targeted by humble reciprocation.

Undoubtedly, this move was truly suitable for the current situation.

It was not that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not have powerful methods like Hu elevation, but if she used them, it would trigger Limitless' countermeasures.

And humble reciprocation was only 'returning' the other Gu Immortals' attacks, the power of each move was not high and did not cross Limitless' bottom line.

At the same time, these killer moves targeted their original owners and not the three great worlds. Their owners had to focus on defending instead, this greatly stabilized Heavenly Court's situation.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was holding Book Mountain while pointing with another hand; stardust shot towards Fang Yuan.

She needed to pin down Fang Yuan herself.

Because Fang Yuan's killer moves could not be 'returned' by humble reciprocation.

These killer moves were compound killer moves, only Fang Yuan with his sovereign physique could use them. So, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had to target Fang Yuan herself.

Fang Yuan gave a cold snort, suddenly using the compound killer move wind-light-fire-lightning wheel!

This move was modified from fire-wind wheel, adding in profundities of light path and lightning path.

Five rings surrounded Fang Yuan, the five rings rotated and carried him away rapidly.

Fang Yuan had been secretly inspecting and discovered that the aura of Heavenly Court's immortal graveyard kept on growing stronger, it was extremely odd. With Book Mountain already in Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's immortal aperture, only the immortal graveyard was left outside. It was a vital area of Heavenly Court!

Humble reciprocation burdened the mind and consumed too much thoughts, even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was burdened.

Fang Yuan retreated from the fight and charged towards immortal graveyard, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable immediately experienced what Fang Yuan felt when she ran away from the fight before.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable quickly moved to stop Fang Yuan, but Immortal Zombie Giant Sun noticed this. Even though there had been no communication, he decisively moved to stop Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Fang Yuan's main body charged into the immortal graveyard alone.

"Not good, this demon Fang Yuan is here!"

"He finally discovered the immortal graveyard's secret."

"That's fine, we don't have to keep on hiding here."

Duke Mei, Duke Tong, and others appeared to block Fang Yuan with a decisive and furious expression.

All of them had actually been revived!

Chapter 2192: Invading The Door of Life and Death

Immortal killer move — Year Beast Summoning.

Fang Yuan waved his hand, dozens of immemorial year beasts appeared from the air above him.

To complete the Twelve Zodiac battle formation, he had kept on fishing immemorial year beasts and gathered a complete set after much difficulty. As for these, they were all leftovers.

Immemorial year beasts roared and howled as they streaked across the air towards the immortal graveyard.

Duke Mei and Duke Tong were still blocking Fang Yuan's path.

At the same time, many Gu Immortal figures appeared from the immortal graveyard. They were those who had died in the battle before.

The Gu Immortals moved out, stopping all the immemorial year beasts.

Fang Yuan came to a realization after seeing this: "It seems like the Gu Immortals who revived in the immortal graveyard have intact cultivation and dao marks as well. As for the Gu worms, their phantom aperture brings them back to the immortal graveyard when they die."

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortal revival method was extremely advanced, with almost no flaws.

"Fortunately, Fang Yuan discovered this ambush in time!" Lu Wei Yin felt fortunate. If they were continued to be kept in dark, when the battle fell to a stalemate, and these Gu Immortals attacked, Longevity Heaven and Fang Yuan's side would be caught off-guard.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sighed inwardly.

The reason she concealed these Gu Immortals and did not let them participate in the battle immediately was to ambush at the crucial time, it was also to preserve strength for Heavenly Court.

The expedition to Crazed Demon Cave was not a fight to the death between the three sides, it was a competition to seize the derivation results of the Crazed Demon formation.

In this aspect, the main player was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable herself, others like Fang Zheng and Che Wei did not have the qualifications to take part in this kind of contest.

Moreover, with Heavenly Court weakened to a great degree, they had little manpower. Even if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable obtained the Crazed Demon formation's derivation and governed Heavenly Court in the future, she would need manpower to control Central Continent. She could not be a leader with no followers.

But now, Fang Yuan had discovered these people.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was aware: This demon Fang Yuan was crafty and cruel with not even a little pride, since he found this weakness, he was definitely going to take advantage of it.

People like Reckless Savage Demon Venerable disdained attacking those that were weaker than them.

Although Spectral Soul Demon Venerable slaughtered countless lives, he treated everyone the same. He killed the weak, he killed the strong, slaughter had become his nature and madness had seeped deep into his bones.

But Fang Yuan purposely bullied the weak! He liked attacking and bullying the weak, but if he met someone stronger, he would go into hiding. Before the fate war, Heavenly Court searched for him repeatedly, but he kept on hiding, using wisdom path methods to guard against deductions.

Stardust flew, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had no choice but to move to support the immortal graveyard.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun naturally stopped her with all of his methods.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used the illusion killer move once more, even if Immortal Zombie Giant Sun could find out the real copy, he would need some time to check.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable succeeded in returning to the immortal graveyard.

But in just this short while, Duke Mei and Duke Tong had died miserably at Fang Yuan's hands once again.

Fang Yuan tried to catch their phantom apertures, but did not succeed.

"If the immortal graveyard is not destroyed, these Gu Immortals will still revive with their cultivation level restored. This is a big problem!" Lu Wei Yin also hurried over.

Following Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's movement, other Heavenly Court Gu Immortals also returned to the immortal graveyard.

The situation once again turned into an offense and defense battle. Heavenly Court was still the defending side, but this time, they were not guarding Book Mountain, instead, they were surrounding the immortal graveyard and fighting an intense battle!

"Hmph, once we kill these Gu Immortals and destroy the immortal graveyard, Heavenly Court will only have Star Constellation Immortal Venerable left. Hahahaha." Zhan Bu Du let out crazed laughter filled with killing intent.

However, Heavenly Court seemed to have expected this situation.

This immortal graveyard was already modified, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals flew down and acted as the formation cores, forming an immortal formation.

The immortal formation created fog that quickly spread across the whole battlefield. Inside it, Gu Immortals could not see clearly, like they were inside thick clouds.

Not only this, Gu Immortal figures were still rising from the immortal graveyard.

Zhan Bu Du and the rest fought with these figures, these figures had the same battle strength as their main bodies, but after they were killed, they only broke apart into lumps of fog.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun deduced for a while and said: "This is a painting path formation, but it also contains human path methods. This formation uses Divine Emperor City as the core, Heavenly Court Gu Immortals as supplementary cores, and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable as the main formation core. It will be extremely difficult for us to break this formation, do you have a good plan?"

Fang Yuan shook his head, his expression turned cold.

Once they entered a deadlock, it would be very disadvantageous to him.

Heavenly Court had infiltrated the Crazed Demon formation very deeply, they had a huge lead. If Heavenly Court was allowed to stall for time, when the three great worlds broke down into fuel for the Crazed Demon formation and the derivation of eternal life succeeds, Heavenly Court would have a much higher chance to seize the results than Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun.

Heavenly Court was not a match for Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's alliance in a frontal fight. But under Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's strategic and decisive leadership, Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun were the ones who fell into a passive state.

Fang Yuan was aware of the severity of this situation, immediately replying: "I know a bit about human path methods, but I don't know the first thing about painting path. Giant Sun, you are proficient in painting path, we need to join hands to have a chance at deciphering this formation."

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun nodded slightly, he had the intention of allying as well.

Immediately, the two stopped attacking. They only ordered Lu Wei Yin, Zhan Bu Du, Bing Sai Chuan, and the rest to try attacking the formation, so that they could gain all kinds of clues and test their speculations.

Fifteen minutes went by, Qi Sea, Qi Jue, and the rest continued attacking with no success, their injuries accumulated instead.

Heavenly Court's formation was still standing firmly.

Fang Yuan suddenly made his move, the Human Sea in his sovereign immortal aperture became turbulent, causing the fog in the outside world to fluctuate as well.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun acted as well, spitting out rays of golden light. The golden light spread throughout the whole formation like ripples.

Wherever the golden light went, the fog dissipated, revealing the immortal graveyard.

The two sides' alliance army saw this and cheered.

But this did not continue for long, the golden light dissipated quickly; the fog was restored almost immediately, blocking the sight of the immortals again.

Zhan Bu Du and the rest tried to attack the formation, but they failed. They could not even sense the locations of the formation cores.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was astonished for a moment before smiling bitterly: "This formation should have already broken, but the main formation core is Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. She forcefully used a wisdom path method to stabilize this formation!"

Gu Immortals were the foundation of killer moves, the main part of any methods was still the person. Under Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's control, this formation of Heavenly Court's was forcefully stabilized, firmly obstructing Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's and Fang Yuan's alliance army.

Fang Yuan slowly shook his head: "Looks like we won't be able to break this formation in a short period of time."

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun did not reply, silently agreeing with this judgment.

When he and Fang Yuan attacked just earlier, it was already their strongest method that was allowed in this situation. Since it could not break this formation, they would need half a month or so to deduce and break this formation.

According to the current fusion rate of the great worlds as well as the Crazed Demon formation that was accelerated by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, half a month was enough for the derivation to be complete.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's expression returned to normal, asking brightly: "Good formation! Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, can you tell me the name of this formation?"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's voice came from within the fog: "This formation is called Transient White Cloud City Suppression, it was created by Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable but was not perfected. Only now, after Heavenly Court explored deeply into human path, we managed to fortunately complete it."

Right at this time, Fang Yuan attacked once again, causing the formation fog to turn chaotic.

Fang Yuan continued: "Giant Sun, since we cannot break the formation, we need to weaken Star Constellation Immortal Venerable for the future."

"That is reasonable." Immortal Zombie Giant Sun immediately shot golden light which spread throughout the whole formation.

Wherever the golden light went, the fog disappeared and everything was cleared.

But, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable still stabilized the formation, soon, the battlefield was covered in fog again.

Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun attacked again and again, while Star Constellation Immortal Venerable stabilized the formation every time. Both sides had no other choice.

As this stalemate continued, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's expression changed suddenly, he felt some changes in luck.

After dozens more rounds, Divine Emperor City suddenly shook, an immortal flew out of the painting world.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun took this chance and shot out golden light, instantly, rays of golden light spread like ripples.

Divine Emperor City's shaking caught Star Constellation Immortal Venerable off-guard, the formation was not stabilized, causing the formation to break. Many Heavenly Court Gu Immortals who acted as the formation cores started coughing blood, every one of them was heavily injured!

Zhan Bu Du took the lead to kill his way into the immortal graveyard, shouting towards that Gu Immortal who broke through the painting world: "Shen Shang, ally with us in attacking Heavenly Court!"

This crucial character who broke the formation was the pseudo venerable of Eastern Sea's righteous path who cultivated human path, Shen Shang.

Shen Shang was shocked mentally and physically, but he immediately joined Fang Yuan's side without any hesitation and attacked Heavenly Court.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable heaved a deep sigh as she waved her sleeve. She took all the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals and Immortal Gu Houses, and entered deep into the immortal graveyard.

Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun naturally would not give up. They chased all the way and saw a secluded domain of heaven and earth in the depths of the immortal graveyard.

This secluded domain of heaven and earth was a tall pitch-black door, it emitted an aura of eeriness, deathly silence, terror, and power.

Secluded domain of heaven and earth — Door of Life and Death!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable entered the Door of Life and Death, but Fang Yuan and the rest slowed down.

It was not easy to enter the Door of Life and Death.

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> recorded this in detail, Ren Zu had once asked wisdom Gu for guidance, wisdom Gu told Ren Zu the path to enter the Door of Life and Death was called the path of destiny. Living beings could enter the door through the path of death; if they wanted to exit, they needed to walk through the road of life. The path of death was filled with suffering Gu, while the road of life had three obstacles - Dang Hun Mountain, Luo Po Valley, and Reverse Flow River. Within the Door of Life and Death, there was Pacifying Soul Lake, fairness Gu, and so on.

Not only these, according to Fang Yuan's intel, it was clear that the Door of Life and Death had Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's main body as well as Ren Zu's eldest son Verdant Great Sun's soul!

Now, there was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and the Heavenly Court immortals.

The Door of Life and Death had become a dangerous area.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable entered the Door of Life and Death with no hesitation, there was close to zero possibility of there being no arrangements inside.

Chapter 2193: Spectral Soul's Shocking Awakening

Looking at the Door of Life and Death in front of him, Fang Yuan immediately recalled his previous luck inspection result.

The dark clouds that represented Spectral Soul Demon Venerable were corroded by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's starry clouds.

"Let's look at it again." Fang Yuan willed and used Cooking Luck Pot.

His silver light pillar luck had condensed a bit. The dust around the base of the pillar was getting increasingly thick and solid, as for the three clouds above the pillar, the starry clouds and dark clouds had almost merged into one, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's golden cloud was still suppressed to the bottom.

The starry clouds and dark clouds had become even larger, they were already beginning to corrode Fang Yuan's silver light pillar.

This change clearly indicated a problem.

"Heavenly Court has prepared abundantly in Crazed Demon Cave, looking at this, it seems like Spectral Soul Demon Venerable has actually allied with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable?"

"According to the current state, Heavenly Court has too much of a lead."

"It is very likely that the final victor will be Star Constellation Immortal Venerable."

Previously, there was Thieving Heaven's true inheritance, an external factor, that affected the silver light pillar.

But when Fang Yuan observed his luck now, there was no external factor remaining.

In fact, at his level, there were extremely few external factors that could influence him and this battle in Crazed Demon Cave.

Only factors like Thieving Heaven's true inheritance had the ability to influence it.

"Looks like I will have to rely on myself to resolve this situation." Although the result of the luck inspection was not good, Fang Yuan activated his method decisively.

A finger-thick rainbow of chaotic colors wriggled out of his body.

The rainbow first linked to the Qi Sea clone, granting him a multi-colored radiance that covered his whole body. The rainbow came out again and connected to Zhan Bu Du.

"This move will protect you when you move in the Door of Life and Death." Fang Yuan said to Lu Wei Yin, Shen Shang, and Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue smiled: "I have my own way."

Shen Shang and Lu Wei Yin received this move.

Thereupon, the multi-colored rainbow connected them as well.

At the other side, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun put Calamity Luck Altar in his immortal aperture, his whole body was covered in a barrier of golden light. Right now, he was staring at above Fang Yuan's head.

Ordinary Gu Immortals naturally could not see the hidden Cooking Luck Pot, but Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was its creator, he could somewhat sense it.

Cooking Luck Pot's strong aura astonished Immortal Zombie Giant Sun.

But thinking back to this battle in Crazed Demon Cave and refinement path accomplishments of Fang Yuan, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun did not feel it strange.

Both sides activated their methods and charged into the Door of Life and Death.

They smoothly entered the Door of Life and Death without encountering any setbacks.

Inside the Door of Life and Death was a scene of vast darkness.

When Fang Yuan and the rest entered, it was like many torches were lit in a dark night. In an instant, countless soul beasts were startled, they started howling and roaring.

The soul beasts began to attack frantically, while Fang Yuan and the rest defended.

"So many soul beasts?!" Shen Shang was astonished.

"This is the place with the greatest concentration of soul beasts. The soul beasts here are beyond a hundred million, it is an inestimable number!" Lu Wei Yin said while activating a killer move which formed earthen walls.

"There are too many soul path dao marks here, my killer moves can't even achieve fifty percent of their effects!" Demon Immortal Qi Jue's face paled slightly after he tried several killer moves.

There were all sizes of soul beasts with all kinds of strength. There were countless ordinary soul beasts, as well as an inestimable number of desolate and ancient soul beasts. There were also many immemorial soul beasts.

The soul beasts were like a pitch-black tsunami, endlessly and fearlessly moving towards Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, trying to drown these Gu Immortals.

"What about Star Constellation Immortal Venerable?" Qi Sea Ancestor asked.

"If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable keeps on hiding, how can we find her in this situation?" Zhan Bu Du frowned.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Fang Yuan had not attacked yet, they were activating all kinds of methods to inspect and try to find Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's traces.

But soon, the two gave up.

They failed.

"Since it is like this...." Immortal Zombie Giant Sun snorted, his whole body emitting golden light.

Instantly, it was like a sun had appeared in the dark Door of Life and Death!

The sun rose high, illuminating all the surrounding space!

The light was extremely piercing, wherever it reached, countless soul beasts melted like ice, without even being able to let out a scream.

The immortals were shocked.

"Could this person be?!" Shen Shang's eyes opened wide as he finally recognized Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's identity.

The power of this move was absolutely beyond Qi Sea Ancestor's Hu elevation.

Fang Yuan also could not help taking a few glances, his pupils shrinking slightly.

Since the battle in Crazed Demon Cave began, this was the first time he saw Immortal Zombie Giant Sun taking such an action. In Fang Yuan's hands, luck path was mostly used as support, but when Immortal Zombie Giant Sun used it at this moment, it showed extreme offensive power!

The golden light spread far, even immemorial soul beasts could not resist it. In an instant, there were uncountable casualties.

The battlefield that spanned thousands of li was cleared completely. At the periphery of the battlefield, a lake was revealed.

The lake was calm with no ripples. Even under the illumination of the golden light, it was still motionless like a mirror.

Pacifying Soul Lake!

There was a mountain range beside Pacifying Soul Lake.

The mountain range was majestic, it was so tall and vast that it seemed to touch the sky and spread beyond the range of the immortals' sight.

"Since when is there a mountain here?"

"\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> has no records of it."

"This mountain is so dark, it is bursting with demonic aura. This is too strange!"

"Is Star Constellation Immortal Venerable on this mountain? Maybe this pitch-black mountain range is Heavenly Court's arrangement?"

The pseudo venerables discussed, but right at this time, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun suddenly said: "Found her."

Fang Yuan's gaze also moved over.

Following his gaze, the immortals discovered Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

She was standing at the peak of the mountain. Starlight twinkled around her and her sleeves fluttered in the air, adding splendor to her unmatched elegance.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable looked down at the immortals, saying with a smile: "The enemies are here, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, you should wake up."

Her voice was calm, but it quickly spread and reverberated in this special world, like an echo in an empty valley.

At the next moment, the dark mountain range that spanned across heaven and earth shook, a voice could be heard: "Who... is disturbing my sleep?"

The mountain range shook with increasing intensity, the entire world was shaking, the ground cracked and mountains shattered!

Two blood-red suns suddenly appeared, each was much larger than Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's attack earlier.

These were Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's eyes!

This vast mountain range before the immortals was actually Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's main body!

"Strong enemies? Who are you... Kill, I will kill you!" Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's murmur shook the air, producing a vast whirlwind.

There was something wrong with his condition, he actually did not recognize Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Fang Yuan, as if he had lost his memories.

Bam Bam Bam Bam...

Hands spread out from the mountain range, in an instant, it was like countless giant trees had grown and formed a terrifying forest of arms.

Rumble...

A huge explosion rang as Spectral Soul Demon Venerable changed from an inclined position to sitting cross-legged.

Even when sitting cross-legged, his shoulders still reached high into the sky, the immortals could not even see his head and could barely see most of his chest.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's main body was too huge. Compared to him, Fang Yuan and the immortals were like ants beside an adult.

Lu Wei Yin, Demon Immortal Qi Jue, and the rest were pale with fright.

They could sense that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's main body was not just huge, the aura he emanated almost suffocated them. The soul path dao marks on him were too dense and of an enormous scale, even the current Fang Yuan could not compare.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable opened his eyes, the two blood sun let out ominous light from the dark cloudy fog.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable opened his mouth and breathed out.

At the next moment, dark soul fog moved with the fierce wind and covered the whole battlefield.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

The violent wind howled by their ears, the pseudo venerables' expression changed one after the other.

The dark soul wind was extremely terrifying, it shook them so intensely that they were almost swept away.

The soul wind did not target just their bodies, it also specially attacked their souls.

At the crucial moment, Fang Yuan called out, the multi-colored rainbow suddenly brightened, helping these pseudo venerables stabilize their souls and resist the soul wind.

"Fang Yuan!" Demon Immortal Qi Jue could not hold on, quickly asking for help.

Fang Yuan immediately activated the multi-colored rainbow, linking him as well and helping him resist the wind calamity.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable saw that no one was blown away, he shouted in anger and pressed down with one of his huge hands!

The huge palm seemed to cover the world, it carried ferocious might and wind and lightning roared alongside it. It gave a feeling of being unblockable and unavoidable.

The giant palm's target was Demon Immortal Qi Jue!

Among the auras of the pseudo venerables, his aura was the weakest. He had been sealed for a long time in Divine Emperor City, much of his dao marks were extracted.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue wanted to dodge, but the giant palm had the ability to instill fear, he would not be able to move in a short period, and could only defend passively.

Boom!!!

The earth shook.

The immortals dodged, only Demon Immortal Qi Jue was left in the area.

He frantically used many defensive killer moves, but he was like an ant trying to fell the tree, he was instantly slammed down by the giant palm.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue's aura rapidly fell to rock bottom.

Spectral Soul's giant palm stamped on the ground and did not move. The palm that was stable as mountain roots or towering like a heavenly pillar let out a strange aura.

"One hand of Spectral Soul can suppress a pseudo venerable?" Even Immortal Zombie Giant Sun revealed an astonished expression, saying, "Save him quickly! Spectral Soul is trying to seal Qi Jue!"

Even without his reminder, Zhan Bu Du had already charged forward.

He was like a meteor as he pierced through Spectral Soul's arm with a loud crash.

Zhan Bu Du laughed loudly and was about to turn around to attack again, when another hand pressed down with an incredible speed.

Boom!!!

Another loud explosion rang, Zhan Bu Du was also slammed down on the ground by the giant palm, his aura falling violently.

"Even with such a large size, it is actually so fast!"

"Too terrifying!"

"Save them, we cannot wait anymore."

Qi Sea Ancestor, Lu Wei Yin, and the rest quickly attacked. The two heavenly pillar-like arms began to collapse from the strong attacks.

Right at this time, dozens of arms fell down from the sky.

Immortal killer move —Ten Li Time Wind.

With a cold snort, Fang Yuan raised his arms and pushed forward with his palms.

Immediately, boundless wind rose, blocking the dozens of giant arms.

This move contained the profundities of time path, rule path, and wind path. When Fang Yuan's palms formed into a claw shape, it could confine the enemy and lock the time of the target.

However, currently, Fang Yuan's hands were raised high, he was trying to grip with his fingers using all his strength, but they were trembling hard and he was unable to contract into a clenched shape.

He could only slow these dozens of giant arms, he could not completely lock their time.

"Good job!" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun praised, his figure suddenly transformed and became a soft rain of golden light.

Chapter 2194: Unification of Three Worlds

Immortal killer move — Golden Top Ox Hair!

The drizzle of dazzling golden light increased rapidly, it quickly spread and covered the dozens of giant arms.

Golden light rained down endlessly, penetrating into the pitch-black giant arms.

The giant arms shook, golden flowing veins appeared and moved up the arms while interweaving into an exquisite web.

When the golden web covered over half of the giant arms, the giant arms started shaking extremely fiercely.

The pressure on Fang Yuan reduced sharply, the giant arms could not even budge under the infiltration of the golden web.

This golden top ox hair killer move clearly also had the ability to confine its enemies. But it was different from Fang Yuan's ten li time wind, it infiltrated the target's body and controlled their movement.

When the golden web covered the giant arms completely, these dozens of giant arms came under Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's control. They moved up and attacked Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's main body!

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was furious, at that instant, a thousand or so giant arms came down, destroying these dozens of traitorous arms.

The golden web lost its attached targets, turning back into a drizzle of golden light.

Amidst the golden light drizzle, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's figure appeared slowly.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable gave a shout, his thunder-like voice shook the whole Door of Life and Death.

A grey tornado immediately formed and moved towards Fang Yuan's group.

The grey tornado did not have absorption force, instead it had a huge repulsive force. Wind blades that were sharper than Luo Po wind rotated and cut the souls.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, Fang Yuan, and the immortals quickly retreated. Soul beasts rushed over from afar, but were dismembered by the wind blades.

After these soul beasts died, they were absorbed by the grey tornado, changing into grey soul bombs.

A soul bomb struck and exploded on Lu Wei Yin. Lu Wei Yin's soul was immediately injured heavily, he almost fainted.

He had exceptional defense but faced this situation. Other immortals like Qi Jue and Shen Shang were even more miserable, their souls might have been swept away if not for Fang Yuan's help.

The number of soul path dao marks in the Door of Life and Death was unimaginable.

Before Spectral Soul Demon Venerable awakened, these pseudo venerables could only use fifty percent of their strength because of the dao mark suppression.

Now that he awakened, pseudo venerables could only use twenty percent of their strength. Even Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun could only use fifty percent of their strength!

"What's going on? Spectral Soul is also a supreme grandmaster."

"Although Spectral Soul Demon Venerable lost his physical body, he has already modified himself into gaining a soul beast body!"

"He has almost merged with the Door of Life and Death. With this environment, all his killer moves are amplified greatly, he can easily suppress us. This is the power of a Dao Lord!"

"What now?"

The immortals could not help but hesitate.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's battle strength far surpassed the expectations of many of them.

Another crucial point was that the Door of Life and Death had too many soul path dao marks.

When fate Gu was intact, the soul of every dead being returned to the Door of Life and Death. Even when fate Gu was damaged, most of the dead beings' souls still returned here.

Countless years accumulated, countless souls gathered and broke down to form the current Door of Life and Death.

Among all the secluded domains of heaven and earth, the Door of Life and Death was likely to have the highest number of dao marks!

At the crucial moment, Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun collaborated to destroy the grey tornado and detonate the thousands of grey soul bombs.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable bent over slightly, thousands of giant arms attacked from all sides. It was like the sky was falling, creating a suffocating feeling!

Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun began to use all their strength.

The giant arms were destroyed one after the other. Their fragments fell to the ground, immediately changing into soul beasts that charged forward to fight once again.

Lu Wei Yin and the other pseudo venerables were in charge of killing these soul beasts.

After the soul beasts died, their fragments combined to form new soul beasts.

Moreover, these newly born soul beasts were stronger than the previous soul beasts. They possessed talents and abilities, thus they could counter Lu Wei Yin and the other Gu Immortals.

Fang Yuan, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, and other Gu Immortals were at a disadvantage.

They were struggling to cope with the countless soul beasts and endless giant arms that attacked unceasingly.

Right now, soul path fully displayed its combat advantage by fueling itself through killing!

"Die! All of you, die!!" Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's mind became even more chaotic, roaring like a wild beast.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled, her clear voice was not suppressed by the chaotic battlefield, instead it reached the immortals' ears: "Everyone, your valiance really makes me feel admiration. Fang Yuan, Giant Sun, I'll take a quick leave first."

Saying this, she leisurely retreated. Her body streaked across the dark world like a meteor, easily leaving the Door of Life and Death.

Since the battle began, she had been standing on Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's head, even though she was openly leaving now, she did not attract Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's attention.

This situation was frightening to see.

The grand Spectral Soul Demon Venerable actually became Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's puppet!

Lu Wei Yin suddenly shouted, his face was pale: "Oh no, Lord Fang Yuan! Star Constellation will definitely unite the three great worlds and destroy Paradise Earth's tomb. We must quickly go and stop her!"

However, this was easier said than done.

Spectral Soul's main body was a genuine Dao Lord inside the Door of Life and Death!

A soul path supreme grandmaster.

A complete rank nine venerable!

On the contrary, Fang Yuan was only at rank eight, and though Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was also a Dao Lord, how could he use the outside world's luck path dao marks to amplify himself in the Door of Life and Death?

Heaven and earth travel?

Fang Yuan had already tried it secretly, but it had no effect.

Heavenly Court knew Fang Yuan had fixed immortal travel Immortal Gu, how could they not have prepared for it?

No killer move was invincible. Just like Fang Yuan's ghostly concealment killer move, it showed no effect inside the Door of Life and Death!

The three great worlds were rapidly melting.

The boundaries had already shrunk by thirty percent.

As for the void in the eighth layer, it was originally vast and infinite, but the boundary was now sticking close to the bubbles of the three great worlds.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable returned here and immediately set up a formation.

The formation activated, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals split and invaded Savage Wilderness Great World and Yellow Earth Great World.

These two great worlds' main forces had almost all died in battle. Only a few remained, they were the old and weak Gu Immortals with no battle strength left, or elite Gu Masters.

Be they the former or latter, they had no ability to block Heavenly Court's advancement.

Heavenly Court continued to push in, setting a sub-formation after occupying each territory.

These sub-formations resonated with the main formation which was personally controlled by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. The sub-formations let out grand lights that shot towards the sky and shone on the surroundings, making the vast and desolate Savage Wilderness Great World, and the hilly Yellow Earth Great World bloom with green.

Weeds and tree saplings grew at a visible speed, quickly forming a dense forest.

This was only the visible phenomenon, the true essence lied in Green Lotus Great World expanding continuously as it absorbed the other two great worlds into its territory!

If looked from above, the green color that was like moss spread from the Green Lotus Great World and slowly covered the other two great worlds.

After covering them, the lush green became even deeper in color.

At first, it was only light green, many areas with the sub-formations turned into deep green. The deep green then turned into dark green.

The three great worlds finally merged!

After reaching a certain extent, a storm started brewing indescribably.

The storm was not large, but its range was astonishing, covering the whole world.

Wind blew like the qi tides of five regions, it quickly merged the primeval energy of the great world and distributed it evenly.

"Limitless Demon Venerable's heaven and earth refinement method has already reached the peak. If I am not wrong, this wind will continue to grow until it becomes the winds of assimilation!"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable controlled the main formation, she personally took part and helped the great worlds unite, so she gained many insight from this.

In fact, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable accounted for almost half of the heaven path research results in the Crazed Demon formation!

Why did Limitless Demon Venerable go to Heavenly Court in his later years and play this game with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable?

The reason was simple.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had merged with heaven's will of her own accord. The killer move human executing heaven's work was extremely profound, while she altered heaven's will, she was also comprehending heaven path.

So, Limitless Demon Venerable competed with Star Constellation to extract the heaven path mysteries, he also received the help of this wisdom path supreme grandmaster, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, to deduce new heaven path research results.

Limitless Demon Venerable cultivated rule path, only by cooperating with the creator of wisdom path, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, could he realize the insane concept of Crazed Demon Cave!

Limitless Demon Venerable achieved his goal, while Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also gained many benefits.

The three avatar fairies' method of influencing the emotions of many mutant Gu Immortals and making them join Heavenly Court was a result of heaven path.

Being able to control Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was also an embodiment of heaven path research results. Naturally, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable took advantage of this situation. Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's main body already had flaws.

"The three worlds have merged, the outcome has been decided." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable let out a breath of air, her eyes shining with starlight.

She had succeeded.

Fang Yuan and Longevity Heaven's alliance was very powerful. But she relied on her incomparable wisdom path attainment to take a lead step by step, maintaining her advantage and not letting the other two sides surpass her.

Although Heavenly Court was weak, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used Book Mountain, Primordial Domain, the Crazed Demon formation, and the Door of Life and Death, she used everything that could be used to help claim victory.

This was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

This was the power of wisdom path!

Heavenly Court had already infiltrated the Crazed Demon formation, now that they united the three worlds and got hold of massive clues and fuel, it was like letting half of the Crazed Demon formation falling into Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's hands.

"It is your turn now, Paradise Earth." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's eyes shone coldly.

She did not like Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable.

Even though Paradise Earth had the name of Immortal Venerable and had extremely high reputation, he loved and defended variant humans. Paradise Earth left Merman Imperial Court in Eastern Sea and also Mushroomman Paradise in Southern Border.

What repulsed Star Constellation Immortal Venerable even more was Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's identity.

Paradise Earth had gone through many fortuitous encounters in his life that could have allowed him to change his fundamental identity to that of a pure human. But he did not do so, he was always a mixed blood which could never be accepted by Heavenly Court.

Immediately, sub-formations buzzed and tore the earth.

Ground crumbled, deep ravines spread quickly from all sides to Paradise Earth's tomb.

Paradise Earth's tomb was broken apart.

Afterwards, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gave a cry, her gaze looking at the distant sky.

Soon, endless starlight condensed and solidified in the sky, turning into meteors that fell to the ground.

Like a rainstorm, the meteors smashed onto Paradise Earth's tomb.

Bam bam bam...

The explosions rang, starlight and rock fragments flew everywhere.

After a few minutes of time, Paradise Earth's tomb was leveled and turned into ruins.

Chapter 2195: Paradise Earth's Revival

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's gaze crossed through thousands of miles and landed on the ruins of Paradise Earth's tomb. She checked carefully before giving a satisfied nod.

She collected the main formation, while Heavenly Court's immortals were in charge of collecting all the sub-formations.

Heavenly Court members gathered in one place and moved with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

After Primordial Domain disappeared, the eighth layer and ninth layer could be easily traveled to and fro.

They left the eighth layer and entered the ninth layer.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable personally pointed the way forward. Qin Ding Ling, Che Wei, Fang Zheng, and the rest stepped into the Crazed Demon formation one after the other, they each stopped on a truthful floating ice piece.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable told them the control method of the truthful floating ice in detail, she then went towards the center of the formation and faced the central truthful floating ice.

"Lady Star Constellation, what are you going to do?"

"If you insist on forcing your way, we will immediately activate practice Gu and destroy this truthful floating ice!"

Not Immortal was alarmed. Pang Shan and Secret Schemer immediately appeared, they tried to threaten Star Constellation.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled: "Truthfully, you three being able to control practice Gu was beyond my expectations. I had already sealed Limitless' will, I did not expect him to still be able to bring you three here. However, the reason why I sealed Limitless' will was just as an additional layer of assurance."

"I am going to use all my strength to accelerate the Crazed Demon formation. This formation that Limitless set up back then is indeed astonishing and extraordinary, reaching the peak of the world. But he is still a rule path Gu Immortal and not of wisdom path. He naturally realized this, if not, why would he invade Heavenly Court and bet with me?"

Pang Shan and Secret Schemer looked at each other. The latter thought for a bit and mustered his courage to ask: "Since Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has the same thought as us, why not come in? We are willing to hand over practice Gu."

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled: "That is not necessary. This area is the Crazed Demon formation's core, it is easy to enter but difficult to exit. It also concerns the final deduction results, if I forcefully break out, I may destroy this truthful floating ice, ruining the million year derivation."

"I am already in control of half the Crazed Demon formation, and only with me leading my Heavenly Court's immortals outside to prevent any unexpected situation, can I safely push this Crazed Demon formation to the limit."

"I am already aware of your ambitions. No need to hesitate, go carve the truthful floating ice."

Pang Shan and Secret Schemer gritted their teeth. Right now, Fang Yuan was missing, and it probably bode ill rather than well. Since Heavenly Court had already controlled the situation, and these three immortals were unable to go out, even if they could go out, they definitely were not Heavenly Court's match. They could only continue to drill the truthful floating ice and resume their work.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable began to activate the formation step by step.

Under her influence, the Crazed Demon formation's form started changing again and again, the derivation efficiency also continued to rise.

Many of Heavenly Court's members were controlling a truthful floating ice piece each, they listened to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's arrangements as they controlled their respective truthful floating ice.

The melting speed of the eighth layer's great world sped up by several times.

Many peripheral truthful floating ice pieces were starting to thaw and shrink. But the central truthful floating ice piece was continuing to expand in size.

There would only be one truthful floating ice piece left in Crazed Demon formation at the end.

If Limitless' arrangements succeeded, then the one who obtained this truthful floating ice could gain eternal life!

Because the truth of eternal life would already be carved.

"Worthy of Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. Under such a bleak situation, she fought one battle after another and made Heavenly Court emerge victorious." Qin Ding Ling was moved.

"With such a person leading Heavenly Court, our deaths would be without regrets." Duke Mei and the rest conversed happily.

"No one else is more suitable than Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to obtain eternal life! With her leadership, our Heavenly Court will definitely become a supreme existence once again, we will unite the five regions just like Crazed Demon Cave's three worlds." The immortals were looking forward to a beautiful future.

When Heavenly Court did not have an Immortal Venerable in charge, there was the tradition of having a wisdom path Gu Immortal lead them.

Past experience proved the sensibility of this system.

Now that the creator of wisdom path, a wisdom path supreme grandmaster, the number one person in wisdom path, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, was controlling Heavenly Court, no one in Heavenly Court had any objection!

Even if Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable and Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable were to revive, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would still be much more suitable than them to obtain eternal life.

Inside the Door of Life and Death.

"All of you must die... why are you still not dead?" Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was sitting cross-legged. Pacifying Soul Lake was only a puddle in comparison, while Fang Yuan and the immortals were like insignificant ants.

But this group of ants made Spectral Soul Demon Venerable extremely angry.

Boom boom boom!

Countless giant arms attacked these ants.

Lu Wei Yin, Demon Immortal Qi Jue, and the rest used all their strength to counterattack. They were only second to peak level battle strengths like that of Fang Yuan, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, but they were in an extremely miserable situation here.

If not for Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun helping them time and again, some of them might have already perished.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's main body was at rank nine, after transforming into a soul beast body and his attainment level having been raised to supreme grandmaster level, he had become a Dao Lord.

Originally, a venerable that had just become a Dao Lord was still not invincible, they had to refine dao marks of their path in the outside world and raise their strength.

But it just so happened that this Door of Life and Death was Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's territory, he had occupied it since long ago.

And the Door of Life and Death had the highest number of soul path dao marks in the world, even Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun were in a disadvantage.

The longer this dragged on, the more disadvantageous it would be for them. Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was aware of this, so they fought while finding an exit path.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun made deductions and smiled bitterly at Fang Yuan: "This is not good. When Star Constellation Immortal Venerable left, it was Spectral Soul Demon Venerable who took the initiative to open a path. He has already completely refined the Door of Life and Death and become this place's master. It is impossible for us to leave like Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!"

Fang Yuan fixed his gaze on Spectral Soul Demon Venerable: "Who could have expected Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to turn Spectral Soul Demon Venerable into a puppet. Giant Sun, you should know that in the five hundred years of my previous life, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable possessed the sovereign immortal body and became the greatest mastermind behind the five regions chaotic war. He infiltrated Heavenly Court and made them a mere figurehead. Now, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable can be considered to have taken revenge for Heavenly Court."

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was solemn: "There is no use in saying these things now. Our hope lies with you."

Fang Yuan nodded: "I know, I have already begun deducing!"

He knew what Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was pointing towards.

Back then, when Ren Zu tried to leave the Door of Life and Death through the road of life, he encountered three obstacles; Dang Hun Mountain, Luo Po Valley, and Reverse Flow River.

Ren Zu failed when he was in Reverse Flow River, if not for this, he could have escaped the Door of Life and Death.

And now, Fang Yuan was the Gu Immortal with the most secluded domains of heaven and earth. In fact, he had Dang Hun Mountain, Luo Po Valley, and Reverse Flow River!

As long as these three obstacles were used to create the road of life, they could escape the Door of Life and Death through it and return to fight Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Fang Yuan had a bitter expression: "Deductions need time and clues. I have no clue about this road of life, I just have these obstacles. And this Door of Life and Death has long been modified by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and merged into himself, there is a huge difference between it and the records in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>. Furthermore, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable does not have a clear mind, I need to split my attention to guard against his mad attacks."

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun heaved a sigh: "Spectral Soul Demon Venerable has astonishing attainment in soul path, he made the Door of Life and Death much more exceptional than before! Even though the situation is already like this, I still hope you will give your best effort."

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's expression changed suddenly: "It is here again, follow me!"

He suddenly threw out Calamity Luck Altar.

Immortal killer move — Luck Changing Golden Light Path!

A dazzling path of golden light formed instantly.

The immortals knew the situation, quickly stepping on the path of light and letting it bring them away.

At the next moment, countless soul bombs, each the size of a mountain, shot down while having tadpole-like tails.

The giant tadpole soul bombs detonated with horrifying strength, the path shook intensely from the explosion and dimmed rapidly.

But the immortals managed to escape from the soul bombs.

They had already suffered once, Shen Shang and Demon Immortal Qi Jue had gotten heavily injured from the explosion. Fortunately, Shen Shang cultivated human path and was an expert in treating these injuries, he displayed human path's superiority, healing the immortals quickly.

After that time, every time the soul bombs attacked, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun used luck changing golden light path and moved the immortals away.

This move was extremely profound, it could forcibly create a survival route in a hopeless situation.

Soul beasts attacked and soul bombs detonated around the light path, many of their attacks canceled each other which instead kept the light path safe.

If it was before, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun could have already escaped with this move. But this Door of Life and Death was different, it was extremely troublesome; even if Immortal Zombie Giant Sun used luck changing golden light path multiple times, he could not succeed.

"Careful!" Qi Sea Ancestor alerted.

After all the soul bombs detonated, a soul river crashed down.

Countless wronged ghosts formed a black river. The ghosts cried and howled, the tragic and furious sounds slightly slowed the immortals' thoughts.

The soul river was extremely huge, covering thousands of miles!

The immortals could not evade it, so they used all kinds of methods. For a moment, they were carried up and down by the soul river, being tortured physically and mentally.

Profound light surrounded and protected Fang Yuan. Multi-colored rainbow bound other pseudo venerables, preventing them from getting washed away.

Under this perilous situation, once the pseudo venerables left the group for some time, they would die a miserable death.

The crucial point was that if they died here, their souls would be used by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to target the remaining people.

This was what Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was good at.

So, Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun were helping themselves by saving these people.

"I can hardly look after myself, how can I quickly deduce the road of life in this situation?" Fang Yuan showed a difficult expression as he looked at the tumultuous soul river.

The situation was bad, as time passed, Fang Yuan's chance of victory would be increasingly low.

If they were delayed for a long time in the Door of Life and Death, if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable obtained eternal life, she might come back to finish them with greatly increased strength.

At that time, if there was no improvement, Fang Yuan would not just be defeated but might even lose his life!

Right at this time, in the great world in Crazed Demon Cave's eighth layer, a yellow light shone.

The yellow light covered the ruins.

This was Paradise Earth's tomb!

The yellow light erupted, shooting towards the sky, before changing direction towards the Door of Life and Death.

A Gu Immortal appeared in the yellow light.

"Buried in the earth for a hundred thousand years,

Brushing dust off my clothes as I rise once more.

Wishing for all lives to be equal,

May all living beings compete in harmony."

After the recital, the Gu Immortal said: "Spectral Soul, please open the door. Paradise Earth... is here to pay a visit."

Chapter 2196: Spectral Soul Versus Paradise Earth

For an instant, the fighting in the Door of Life and Death suddenly stopped.

The furious Spectral Soul Demon Venerable stopped roaring, countless giant arms stopped moving like space had frozen.

"What happened?" Qi Sea Ancestor was puzzled.

At the next moment, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable opened his huge mouth, letting out an earth-shattering roar.

The roar contained anger, hatred, as well as excitement towards meeting a great enemy!

"You revived..."

"You revived as well!"

"I finally meet you. Since you are here, come in."

"So that I can... kill you!!"

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable did not remember Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, but he seemed to have a deep impression of Paradise Earth.

Suns of blood color rose in the sky, these were Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's eyes.

He had three heads; only one head had awakened in the previous battle, now the remaining two heads also opened their blood colored eyes!

The entrance of the Door of Life and Death opened, forming a huge vortex that let out a terrifying suction force.

The entrance opened and closed in an instant. When Fang Yuan and the rest came to their senses, a Gu Immortal was pulled into the Door of Life and Death.

He had a shiny bald head and wore plain clothing.

He had a kind expression and his entire body let out a faint radiance.

"Paradise Earth!" Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun called out.

"Lord Paradise Earth, you succeeded in reviving!?" Lu Wei Yin was surprised and happy. He suddenly shouted, "Careful!"

Bam bam bam...

Hundreds of giant arms repelled the air as they ruthlessly charged towards Paradise Earth while producing thunderous rumbles.

Battle erupted once again!

The Crazed Demon formation turned chaotic.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were heavily injured, their expressions were pale and bewildered.

This was all caused by Paradise Earth's revival.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable revealed an astonished expression.

Ever since the battle in Crazed Demon Cave started, this was the first time she showed such an emotion.

The reason was that although Paradise Earth revived, his revival method was beyond Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's expectations.

"I thought you would revive as an earth path venerable, but to think you would take another path."

"I underestimated you."

"You actually converted to heaven path, Paradise Earth's tomb was only a target. Only through its destruction could you revive."

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable let out a breath of air, but did not move towards the Door of Life and Death. At the moment, the Crazed Demon formation was rotating like a tornado, she could not get away easily.

Moreover, although Paradise Earth revived, he had converted to heaven path and the tomb was destroyed much earlier by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, so his current cultivation was only at pseudo venerable level.

If Yellow Earth Great World had annexed the other two great worlds and Paradise Earth's tomb was destroyed along with the great world, the revived Paradise Earth might have venerable cultivation!

Right now, the main focus was still on the Crazed Demon formation. The sensible Star Constellation would never abandon the larger goal for smaller gains. Moreover, even if she returned to the Door of Life and Death, her battle strength would also be suppressed greatly, it would not be worth the effort.

Inside the Door of Life and Death.

"Careful!" Lu Wei Yin's shout had just landed.

A giant web appeared in front of Paradise Earth.

The milky white web was extremely thick, every thread of the web had the size of an elephant, giving a monumental and majestic feeling.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's attacks were completely blocked by this giant web.

"What kind of killer move is this, it actually has such defensive prowess!?"

"This aura, I have never felt it before..."

"Wait a moment! Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable does not have rank nine cultivation, he is only at rank eight level like us!"

Demon Immortal Qi Jue, Zhan Bu Du, and the rest were greatly shaken.

"This is a heaven path killer move! Paradise Earth converted to cultivating heaven path, he revived but did not regain his venerable cultivation, this might be the price!" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was somewhat aware.

Fang Yuan's emotions were slightly complex.

He had also once considered progressing in heaven path.

Who could have expected Paradise Earth's scheme to be deeper than his, he had even greater progress. Through this revival, he directly became a pseudo venerable in heaven path!

Using heaven path's advantage, the suppression of the Door of Life and Death on Paradise Earth was the smallest.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was roaring in fury, he half-squatted from his cross-legged position!

Thousands of giant arms attacked, the five fingers of every hand were placed together like a drill, and the sharp nails stabbed like spears.

Countless giant hands stabbed the web of light, Paradise Earth's expression did not change, but the heaven path giant web that did not even budge before was shaking slightly.

"Although he cultivates heaven path, he is only a pseudo venerable. Reinforce him." Fang Yuan immediately saw through the situation and alerted others.

Lu Wei Yin was the first to charge forward, but was blocked by giant arms midway.

Fortunately, Fang Yuan and the rest followed closely to reinforce Paradise Earth.

After Spectral Soul Demon Venerable adapted, the giant arms changed shape, a large number of spikes extended from the fingernails, his action changed from poking to tearing.

Slash, slash... countless giant arms tore layers of webs of light, continuously breaking them.

Although Paradise Earth only had pseudo venerable cultivation level, his defensive method was exceptional and was at Immortal Venerable level. It was just that when Spectral Soul Demon Venerable used his full strength, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had to retreat even after obtaining the reinforcement.

The immortals' situation was still as perilous as before.

After blocking for a while, Paradise Earth transmitted his voice: "Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's condition is strange, his mind is not clear, his emotions were probably tampered with by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. I have a method that can dispel all emotions and make someone's rationality as calm as ice."

Wisdom path had three main elements; thoughts, wills, and emotions.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was definitely at the peak in these three aspects.

Fairy Feng Ya deduced Limitless' arrangements, always being ahead of others. This was the attainment of thoughts.

Limitless' will was sealed by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, this was a method of will.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's emotions were agitated and in disorder, he did not have even a trace of rationality. This showed Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's might in terms of emotions!

Regarding this, Fang Yuan, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, or other pseudo venerables had all made an attempt.

However, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's condition was the same, never showing a sign of regaining his sanity.

The immortals' attempts failed, they agreed that it was because Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's method was exceptional. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was a wisdom path supreme grandmaster, the number one in the world in this path, since she left confidently, she naturally had full confidence in her method, she believed this method would not be broken for a short period of time.

Right now, although Paradise Earth mentioned this idea, the immortals did not object, they cooperated with him quickly.

Spectral Soul's attacks were extremely fierce, Paradise Earth's appearance had agitated his state even further.

All kinds of soul path killer moves were used one after the other; some were sinister, some were weird, some were domineering, and some were unrestrained. The immortals were too busy dealing with them.

Paradise Earth was protected at the center, but he was disturbed again and again. The killer move's activation progress was minimal.

After a long while, Fang Yuan snorted coldly: "All of you, move aside!"

The immortals quickly retreated.

Fang Yuan's face was indifferent but his eyes shone as he faced the tsunami-like wave of soul beasts. He opened his arms and roared towards the sky.

Along with his roar, specks of light flew out of his immortal aperture.

The specks were of all kinds of color, they rapidly collided in the air, turning into dragons, wolves, tigers, fishes, and other beings.

These were all totem killer moves!

Countless totems of all kinds and shapes charged forward. Wherever they went, soul beasts cried out miserably as they were torn into shreds, burned into ashes, drowned, cleaved by lightning...

In an instant, Fang Yuan released hundreds of totems that he had gathered on his body.

These killer moves were all at rank eight, that was to say, Fang Yuan used hundreds of rank eight killer moves in an instant.

Peerless might!

The immortals immediately felt the pressure on them reducing sharply.

Countless soul beasts were slaughtered, even when the giant arms attacked, ten or so totems attacked one giant arm and destroyed them.

"Thirty percent of my immortal essence was used up!" Fang Yuan let out a breath of air, returning to the group.

The immortal essence expenditure of releasing so many totem killer moves was extremely terrifying.

According to Fang Yuan's current immortal essence reserves, he could only use this move three times at most.

Among the present Gu Immortals, the lowest cultivation was at pseudo venerable. Yet. when they looked at Fang Yuan, their expressions were all shaken and even contained vague fear.

Totem killer moves were quick and convenient, but Fang Yuan released so many totems at once, which was the thing that really shocked them.

Ignoring anything else, with just this method, Fang Yuan could exterminate almost any super force in the world!

Even Immortal Zombie Giant Sun stared at Fang Yuan for a while.

He knew of totem killer moves, so he understood the advantages and weaknesses of this kind of killer move.

Totem killer moves were indeed quick and convenient, but they were difficult to nurture.

However, Fang Yuan had actually nurtured so many rank eight totems, this made Immortal Zombie Giant Sun shocked at Fang Yuan's wealth.

"Good method!" Paradise Earth praised before concentrating on preparing his killer move.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's three heads opened their mouths and breathed out a vast soul river.

Three soul rivers converged into a soul river of an unprecedented scale. It crashed down like dark clouds covering the sky.

Totem killer moves flew and charged into the soul river as they fought.

The soul river's speed of descent fell, while these totems' radiance was extinguished one by one.

Thoughts moved rapidly in Fang Yuan's mind, all kinds of thoughts sparked as he madly dispatched the totems and coordinated their actions.

His immortal essence was expended rapidly, his mind was beginning to overheat as it reached the limits of his wisdom path capability.

Totem killer moves were far superior to immemorial desolate beasts because they could coordinate with each other and be controlled casually. More importantly, each of them possessed extreme prowess, comparable to immemorial desolate beasts that had wild Immortal Gu, or even immemorial desolate beasts that grasped immortal killer moves.

These totems gained twenty-two breaths of time for Paradise Earth.

Finally, Fang Yuan heaved a sigh as he collected the remaining twelve totems in his immortal aperture.

These totems survived fortunately but they were in an extremely damaged state. The other hundreds of totems had all died in battle.

Naturally, accompanying their deaths were countless soul beasts and dozens of Spectral Soul's giant arms.

Fang Yuan retreated to the depths of the group, he had to rest his mind and it seemed difficult for him to battle for some time.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun stood up and took his place.

He had already prepared his killer move, using it with no hesitation.

Immortal killer move — Unforeseen Disaster!

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun grabbed at his head repeatedly with his palms that were covered in a layer of light.

The pure gold light around his palms was rapidly dyed black and red.

Every time Immortal Zombie Giant Sun grabbed, he threw them as well.

The dark-red bad luck flew in the air, turning into lumps of dark-red clouds that flew everywhere.

Each lump of dark-red cloud was not large; wherever they went, soul beasts within a hundred li howled for a few breaths of time before losing their lives, giant arms broke, large segments of the soul river also broke apart.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun repeatedly grabbed his bad luck and threw them at his enemy.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's body itself was becoming unstable after being hit by this method. His left head shouted as it used burning soul bursting luck, his luck immediately rose and offset Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's method.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun attacked for a while before stopping.

It was not that his immortal essence was not enough or his mind got tired, it was because he had used up all his bad luck.

Chapter 2197: Killing Spectral Soul?

"This method is really good." Fang Yuan was slightly moved as he observed Immortal Zombie Giant Sun.

If he could use all of his bad luck to attack, then his own luck would always remain at the highest level.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun had an excellent combat system, this method definitely had high importance in this combat system.

With Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's help, Paradise Earth got the time to prepare and activate his killer move.

Immortal killer move — Emotionless Heaven and Earth!

White waves of light spread from between Paradise Earth's brows, the light waves immediately spread towards the whole battlefield and covered Spectral Soul Demon Venerable completely.

Waves of light activated one after the other, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable did not feel anything at first, but he soon showed a response. The killing intent in his blood-red pupils decreased rapidly as they revealed flickers of rationality.

But at this time, the silhouette of a figure showed itself on Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's stomach.

The immortals heard this figure speak: "Heaven and earth is emotionless, that is correct, but humans have emotions."

Saying so, this figure laughed.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's pupils were filled with killing intent once again, the trace of rationality just earlier had vanished without a trace.

"Who was that?" The immortals were astonished.

Clearly, this figure had caused Paradise Earth's killer move to fail.

"Is it Verdant Great Sun?" A thought emerged in Fang Yuan's mind.

According to Spectral Soul's memories and the records in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, Ren Zu's eldest son Verdant Great Sun's soul lay on the shores of Pacifying Soul Lake.

But right now, there was nothing around Pacifying Soul Lake.

It was very likely that Verdant Great Sun's soul was devoured by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

But for some reason, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable who cultivated soul path and food path could not 'digest' Verdant Great Sun, he was instead controlled.

It was very likely that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had played a crucial role in this.

Paradise Earth revealed a troubled expression at seeing his killer move have no effect.

Spectral Soul attacked once again, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Fang Yuan glanced at each other as the former said: "Fang Yuan, have you gained any comprehension?"

Fang Yuan shook his head, his expression was solemn: "There is no progress."

"I have an idea." Shen Shang suddenly said, "Since the fate war, I have been lurking inside Divine Emperor City while cultivating human path. Besides the gains, I also pondered on how to get out of difficult situations, so I thought of a human path method. Right now, I have already deduced ninety percent of this method, only the final ten percent remains. When I saw Lord Paradise Earth activate the human path killer move, my intuition told me that this is the final ten percent I require. With it, I can complete this killer move."

"This..." The other Gu Immortals murmured softly.

Shen Shang's intention was to ask for Paradise Earth's heaven path research results, this was quite an impudent request.

There was an example here, despite Fang Yuan having three crucial secluded domains of heaven and earth, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun had never asked to borrow these secluded domains of heaven and earth to deduce the road of life to escape from the Door of Life and Death.

But in the current situation, Shen Shang's overbearing request had some reason behind it.

The crucial point was that he and Paradise Earth had a peculiar relationship.

Shen Shang was an Eastern Sea Gu Immortal, he secretly committed many sins to cultivate human path. After Paradise Earth learned of it, he immediately took action.

Shen Shang could not even take one strike from Paradise Earth, but instead of killing or confining him, Paradise Earth gave him a chance to atone for his sins.

Thus, Shen Shang entered the blue dragon whale and cultivated bitterly.

After obtaining Paradise Earth's help, Shen Shang made progress time and time again, advancing stably.

With heal injury Immortal Gu as the foundation, he developed and created saving dead healing injuries, light injuries, heavy injuries, fatal injuries, sensory injuries, seven laborious injuries, and other killer moves. Later, he created the killer move countless injury marks, from which he deduced the Immortal Gu recipe of injury mark Immortal Gu. Finally, he refined injury mark Immortal Gu, and changed it to his vital Gu.

When Fang Yuan explored the blue dragon whale's aperture, he released Shen Shang.

Shen Shang cooperated with Fang Yuan according to Paradise Earth's instructions and participated in the fate war. At the crucial moment, he played a key role and set the crucial foundation for Fang Yuan's victory over Heavenly Court.

Shen Shang's and Paradise Earth's relationship could be said to be extremely close.

Back then, when Shen Shang cultivated human path in blue dragon whale, he had received Paradise Earth's guidance.

The connection between the two was very deep, second only to the relationship between Lu Wei Yin and Paradise Earth.

Thus, Shen Shang made this seemingly impudent request. Because back then, Paradise Earth guided him, there was a high chance of him guiding Shen Shang again now that he had revived.

The only difference was that it was human path before, and now it was heaven path.

Sure enough, like Shen Shang expected, Paradise Earth directly imparted the information of emotionless heaven and earth to him without any hesitation.

"I thank lord's guidance!" Shen Shang bowed with his hands cupped before him, his voice slightly shaking from excitement.

Paradise Earth nodded, saying with a smile: "Shen Shang, your appearance here can be considered a fortune. Whether we can leave here or not will depend on your talent."

"Junior will do his best to not let down lord's expectation!" Shen Shang was even more excited.

He was a grand pseudo venerable, but in front of Paradise Earth, he positioned himself as a junior and was extremely humble and respectful.

He was indebted to Paradise Earth!

In fact, many people and forces were indebted to Paradise Earth.

Everyone knew Paradise Earth was the most popular among the ten venerables, even many people of Central Continent respected him.

The amount of good deeds Paradise Earth had done over his life and the number of people he had helped was inestimable!

After receiving Paradise Earth's approval and encouragement, the other Gu Immortals were slightly expectant of Shen Shang.

Most of them were still placing their hopes on Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had made crucial breakthroughs during battles before, he had created reverse flow protection seal, he was the person who defeated Heavenly Court. There were precedents for this.

Moreover, at present, Fang Yuan's position was higher than Shen Shang's.

The immortals fought and evaded Spectral Soul's attacks.

Another head grew on Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

This was because Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, Paradise Earth, and Fang Yuan's joint attacks had cleaved one of his heads into two.

However, the halved head split, one turning into two, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable gained another head.

Not only the head, no matter how many of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's arms were destroyed, they quickly grew again.

His arms were increasing in number, becoming even more sturdy and strong.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's strength was still continuing to grow!

The fiercer Fang Yuan's group counterattacked, the faster the speed of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's growth.

Nurturing strength through battle!

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was already a special venerable, but he could still grow. Compared to the full strength he used before, his strength had clearly risen a lot.

The immortals were not able to estimate his limits, which firmed up their decision to leave.

It was too disadvantageous to fight Spectral Soul Demon Venerable inside the Door of Life and Death.

There were endless soul beasts, there was no use no matter how many were killed.

All kinds of soul path killer moves covered the world, forcing the immortals to defend with all their strength and concentration.

"Hmm?" Fang Yuan suddenly showed a peculiar expression.

This change in expression immediately attracted the gazes of the immortals.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun asked with hope: "Fang Yuan, you made some progress?"

Fang Yuan nodded before shaking his head: "Yes, there is progress, but it is not the road of life. Let me try this!"

The moment he said this, Fang Yuan's aura turned eerie and dark.

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture, Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley started buzzing and shaking slightly as they resonated with each other, emitting an increasingly bright radiance.

After the preparation was complete, Fang Yuan's aura became restrained. He pushed his palm, from which a lump in the form of a grey-white square seal flew out.

The square seal's speed was slow, but wherever it passed by, all the souls disintegrated into ashes.

A large area of the soul beast army was immediately cleared up, even immemorial soul beasts did not have a trace of resistance against this grey-white square seal, they were thinner than even paper!

The vast soul river that had been shrouding the sky also crumbled apart.

Most of the soul path killer moves were greatly suppressed and weakened in front of this grey-white square seal.

The immortals surrounding Fang Yuan were also terrified, a bone-chilling cold feeling spread from the depths of their soul.

The whole battlefield was silent, even Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's breath turned rough when he guarded against this square seal.

Since the battle started, this was the first time he was breathing roughly and stopped his tsunami-like attacks!

Immortal killer move — Dang Hun Luo Po Seal!

"Strong... too strong..." Shen Shang was shaken.

Even Paradise Earth's eyes opened wide, turning speechless!

"This move is terrifying, it can be considered as soul path's nemesis!" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was stunned for a bit before complimenting. He saw the grey-white seal rise up, a hundred of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's giant arms that were in its path were destroyed.

Even though the grey-white square seal was finally destroyed, the areas where Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's hundred or so giant arms were destroyed still remained empty for a while as if the regenerative ability was exhausted.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's unforeseen disaster killer move was similar to Dang Hun Luo Po Seal, but these soul beasts could still resist unforeseen disaster killer move for a while. However, against Dang Hun Luo Po Seal, they had no ability to resist.

Fang Yuan heaved a sigh: "I am ashamed, I did not manage to deduce the road of life, but gained this instead."

"This move is called Dang Hun Luo Po seal, it uses the two sacred lands as the cores, its foundation is the Luo Po seal I created before."

"Spectral Soul had once said that Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley were sacred lands for soul cultivation. My killer move was developed from the foundation of soul path and suppresses it fundamentally. It is a pity that I only have the two sacred lands, if I had Pacifying Soul Lake as well, I might be able to restrain all soul path methods completely."

Demon Immortal Qi Jue's eyelids twitched, from Fang Yuan's tone, it seemed he was still not satisfied with this killer move?

"Great!" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun praised again, encouraging, "Fang Yuan has already combined the two obstacles now, if you can add in Reverse Flow River as well, you should be able to deduce the road of life."

Zhan Bu Du gave another suggestion while pointing towards a direction: "No, from what I see, as long as we put this move to good use, with us supporting my main body, there is a huge chance of killing Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. Take a look!"

Following Zhan Bu Du's finger, the immortals immediately discovered: It was deathly silent in the areas destroyed by Dang Hun Luo Po Seal, they did not restore quickly like before.

As for Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, although the hundred or so giant arms destroyed were regenerating, the speed was very slow.

Dang Hun Luo Po Seal was a pure soul path killer move, it was amplified in the Door of Life and Death. The soul path dao marks that this move left behind were like the winds of Luo Po Valley and the vibration force of Dang Hun Mountain, they made it difficult for soul beasts to condense into being.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun frowned, analyzing: "Although Spectral Soul Demon Venerable is a Dao Lord and can control the soul path dao marks here to amplify himself while suppressing Fang Yuan's Dang Hun Luo Po seal, his state of mind is not clear, he only has a Dao Lord's instincts, so Dang Hun Luo Po seal can also receive amplification here!"

The immortals' eyes shined as they saw a new possibility —

Killing Spectral Soul?

Chapter 2198: Star Constellation Versus Giant Sun

Thoughts began to surge rapidly in the immortals' minds!

Dang Hun Luo Po Seal was truly amazing, it was a killer weapon against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, who had lost his sanity.

Zhan Bu Du was correct. In the current situation, there was indeed a possibility of relying on Dang Hun Luo Po Seal to kill Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

"Barring unexpected surprises, it is feasible indeed..."

"It will be very difficult to find an escape route under Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's crazed attacks. However, directly eliminating Spectral Soul Demon Venerable is also an option!"

"This place is controlled by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, there is small hope of finding a way out. But going against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and killing him will definitely be a life and death battle!"

They were all speculating.

Qi Sea Ancestor's expression sank: "The fact is, don't we need to step past the obstacle, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, to leave the Door of Life and Death? Even if we shake him off and leave the Door of Life and Death, what if he chases us? At that time, we will have to deal with both Star Constellation and Spectral Soul! It is better to use this chance when Star Constellation Immortal Venerable is busy with infiltrating the Crazed Demon formation to kill Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!"

The immortals' minds jolted.

"Indeed." Lu Wei Yin mumbled, "We will need to go against Heavenly Court to fight for the eternal life research results. If we can kill Spectral Soul Demon Venerable now, Heavenly Court's threat will immediately be halved."

"Hmph!" Zhan Bu Du snorted coldly, "What are you still hesitating for? Everyone, the longer we delay, the deeper Star Constellation's infiltration becomes, she will be closer to the eternal life research results. Regardless of which plan we choose, we need to decide now."

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, however, frowned, saying in a heavy tone: "It is not that simple, Fang Yuan. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable is the number one expert in wisdom path, will she leave behind such an obvious loophole? Right now, I am worried that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's control over Spectral Soul Demon Venerable has a time limit. Once the time limit is up, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable might get out of this predicament by himself. At that time, we will have Spectral Soul Demon Venerable as an ally."

"If we really attack Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, whether we win or Spectral Soul Demon Venerable wins, even if it is a draw, both sides will be injured, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable will still be the biggest winner."

The immortals were silent.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun made sense, since this was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, there was no such thing as overestimating her planning.

"Giant Sun, when do you think Spectral Soul Demon Venerable will leave the control and gain his rationality?" Fang Yuan asked with a sharp gaze, "Let's take your speculation a step further. Suppose Star Constellation Immortal Venerable intentionally left this loophole and lured us into thinking this way, in fact, even if Star Constellation can only control Spectral Soul Demon for some time, if she were to obtain the eternal life research results during this time, what do we do?"

"Then, Fang Yuan, you are intent on fighting to the death? Under this situation?" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun fixed his gaze on Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan did not yield, matching his gaze.

The atmosphere between the immortals suddenly became tense.

Right at this time, Shen Shang shouted: "I succeeded, I succeeded. My killer move is complete!"

Paradise Earth said with a heavy voice: "Shen Shang, what are your chances?"

"Eighty percent!" Shen Shang was excited, "This move was incomplete before as it lacked heaven path results. But the lacking part is not the crucial core. My intuition is telling me strongly that this move has an eighty percent success rate. There is still room for improvement, but it is already complete now and can be used."

Fang Yuan and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun retracted their gazes.

Fang Yuan said: "Then, let's protect Shen Shang while he attempts it."

Previously, Fang Yuan and the rest succeeded in protecting Paradise Earth. With Dang Hun Luo Po Seal, there was no problem in protecting Shen Shang.

Immortal killer move — Heaven Always Leaves A Way Out For People!

After a while, amidst the tidal wave-like offense of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, Shen Shang activated the killer move, creating a narrow path.

The path was long and winding, it could not compare to luck changing golden light path. But it pierced through the Door of Life and Death, the immortals even saw the vague scene of the outside world at the end of the path.

The immortals were surprised and joyous.

Shen Shang laughed heartily, calling out with his arms raised: "It succeeded."

Paradise Earth smiled: "I was right about you."

"Hundreds of years eastern immortal leader, with half of a venerable's talent, your reputation matches your abilities indeed." Qi Sea Ancestor cupped his fists.

"We all owe you a favor for getting out of this predicament." Demon Immortal Qi Jue did not stint on praising.

"Let's go." Zhan Bu Du still took the lead, he was very suitable in opening up a path.

The immortals did not have any hesitation, they protected each other as they stepped on the narrow path.

Shen Shang's killer move was unique, even the Door of Life and Death could not stop these Gu Immortals from escaping successfully.

When the immortals got out of the Door of Life and Death, they prepared for a fight.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's mad roars came from the Door of Life and Death, the whole giant door shook constantly.

But in the end, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable did not step out of the Door of Life and Death!

"So it was like this, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable is not able to exit the Door of Life and Death for some reason."

"No wonder Star Constellation Immortal Venerable lured us inside."

"Maybe Spectral Soul Demon Venerable can come out, but Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's method of control is most effective inside the Door of Life and Death."

The Gu Immortals let out sighs of relief as they made guesses.

"Quick, let's go to the Crazed Demon formation. So much time has passed, who knows how much progress Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has made?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue reminded.

Before the immortals left, they used their methods to try to destroy the immortal graveyard.

However, the killer moves were all absorbed by the Door of Life and Death.

"No use. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's arrangements are exquisite, this immortal graveyard is closely connected with the Door of Life and Death. If we want to destroy the immortal graveyard, we need to destroy the Door of Life and Death first." Immortal Zombie Giant Sun sighed and left.

It was because they saw through this, he and Fang Yuan had chosen to invade the Door of Life and Death.

Naturally, there were also many other reasons.

"This method can be broken, and we can separate the immortal graveyard from the Door of Life and Death. But we don't have time. Let's go, onwards to the Crazed Demon formation!" Fang Yuan also turned around and left.

The immortals did not delay as they followed closely behind.

After the destruction of Primordial Domain, the eighth and ninth layer could be easily traveled to and fro.

When Fang Yuan, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, and the rest once again arrived before the Crazed Demon formation, only thirty percent of this formation remained.

A large number of truthful floating ice pieces were already melted, the remaining truthful floating ice pieces had expanded several times their previous size.

Bam.

Right at this time, a truthful floating ice piece suddenly detonated, turning into countless ice fragments.

Most of the ice fragments dissipated on the spot, and a small portion floated towards the formation, joining other truthful floating ice pieces.

"In this battle, Primordial Domain was lost, Giant Sun, Star Constellation, and even Spectral Soul have already become supreme grandmasters. If these eternal life research results derived by the Crazed Demon formation for over a million years are also seized by these people, that would truly be a crushing defeat!"

"If I cannot compete for it, I might have to destroy the final truthful floating ice piece and let no one gain anything."

Fang Yuan's gaze was icy as he charged towards the formation.

The other Gu Immortals also charged forward.

This group contained the strongest people of the current world; Fang Yuan, Giant Sun, Paradise Earth, Qi Sea, Zhan Bu Du, Shen Shang, Qi Jue, and Lu Wei Yin. This lineup was truly horrifying and suffocating.

"Terrifying!" Gu Yue Fang Zheng's face was pale, he felt the intense killing intent even inside Demon Judgment Board.

"Don't even think of it!" Even under the huge pressure, Heavenly Court Gu Immortals still walked forward.

It was Duke Mei!

Not only Duke Mei, Duke Tong, Golden Hooped Great Immortal, and others moved forward to block the path.

"Get lost!" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun shouted coldly. Golden light bloomed, turning into a giant palm that sent several people flying.

Hu Land appeared above Qi Sea Ancestor, qi waves surged and turned into a qi wall that blocked Ruan Dan and Fairy Maiden Soul.

Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch attacked while riding on Shabi Ninety-five, Shen Shang and Demon Immortal Qi Jue were stopped by the killer move, their momentum stopping immediately.

"Damn it!" Demon Immortal Qi Jue furiously activated the killer move Xi Xi, suppressing Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch.

Shen Shang attacked in coordination with a cold expression.

Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch held on for a few breaths of time before he was killed by Qi Jue and Shen Shang. Shabi Ninety-five was also hacked into two, dying on the spot!

Although Heavenly Court's members were strong, they were too weak in front of Fang Yuan's group, of which the weakest was still at pseudo venerable level.

Moreover, they did not have the help of immortal formations or Immortal Gu Houses in this fight, they were using their lives to delay the enemies.

In just a short while, Heavenly Court's side suffered huge casualties.

However, they also achieved their goal; Fang Yuan's group's momentum slowed down.

"Heavenly Court has the Door of Life and Death and the immortal graveyard, so what if these Gu Immortals died? They will revive soon without any loss to their battle strength."

"If we want to fight our way into the formation, we need to control a part of it."

Lu Wei Yin and Zhan Bu Du called out.

Starlight appeared, before Lu Wei Yin and Zhan Bu Du could react, they were sent flying by the starlight.

Starlight specks shone as Star Constellation Immortal Venerable revealed herself. She looked around and sighed: "You are all too anxious, Crazed Demon formation's derivations are at the final juncture, you cannot act recklessly. What will we do if Limitless' painstaking efforts of over a million years are destroyed?"

Fang Yuan's expression was cold, while Immortal Zombie Giant Sun smiled and said with his gaze fixed on Star Constellation Immortal Venerable: "Since that is the case, I might as well wait for them. But we cannot waste time now. Star Constellation, let us settle this once and for all!"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's gaze lingered: "I would like to see your skills too. Please go ahead and make your move."

The moment she finished speaking, the void fluctuated, stardust flew, creating vertical and horizontal starry paths, forming a grand chessboard.

At the center of the chessboard was the Crazed Demon formation, while Heavenly Court, Fang Yuan, Longevity Heaven, and other Gu Immortals were all inside the chessboard.

"Star Constellation Chessboard!" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's eyes shone sharply.

Paradise Earth smiled as he came to realization: "So Star Constellation Chessboard was an Immortal Gu House as well as an immortal formation. But there are no records of this transformation."

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable answered Paradise Earth: "This was modified by me after I regained my Dao Lord status. Please do critique it."

Qi Sea Ancestor attacked directly without waiting for her to finish speaking.

Qi surged and shook the surroundings.

For a moment, starry paths vanished and stardust was swept away.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable threw down a chess piece.

The chess piece turned into Nine Spiritual Fairy in midair. Nine Spiritual Fairy had already activated her transformation path killer move to turn into a kingfisher, she shot towards Qi Sea Ancestor with an astonishing speed.

Qi Sea Ancestor fought with her. After three to four rounds, there was still no clear victor.

Nine Spiritual Fairy was clearly strengthened by the formation.

After five to six rounds, Nine Spiritual Fairy had already transformed three times, but was starting to fall into danger.

But right at this time, chess pieces fell down; Wan Zi Hong, Bai Cang Shui, Jun Shen Guang, Zhou Xiong Xin, and other immortals attacked. The battlefield instantly turned chaotic.

After just a few rounds, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun saw the ingenuity behind this.

These Heavenly Court members were formation cores of Star Constellation Chessboard Formation. Under Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's control, their coordination was extremely good.

As more and more Gu Immortals entered the battle, the situation became increasingly chaotic, and Heavenly Court's advantage got bigger.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun snorted coldly, he broke free from the chaotic battlefield and charged directly towards Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not evade this time, she met Immortal Zombie Giant Sun head on.

A fight between two venerables could be said to be unprecedented!

Starlight flickered strongly, golden light spread, the whole battlefield was dyed golden and blue.

The aftermath of the two venerables' fight created a vast qi tide that was much worse than the past qi tides.

On one end, there was a wisdom path supreme grandmaster, the second generation Immortal King of Heavenly Court, an unmatched strategist with dazzling achievements. On the other end, there was the number one person in luck path who changed the luck of countless lives, he controlled Northern Plains and spread his bloodline widely.

They were evenly matched!

Chapter 2199: Star Constellation's Difficulty

All kinds of killer moves and methods were activated endlessly by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun.

Some killer moves were domineering, spanning across heaven and earth. Some methods were exquisite and dazzling, splitting the universe.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was like a golden meteor, charging forward bravely.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's body flickered as she moved around in Star Constellation Chessboard Formation, leaving behind starlight shadows that attacked Immortal Zombie Giant Sun.

Moreover, even when fighting, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was still controlling Star Constellation Chessboard Formation to help Heavenly Court members.

Prince Feng Xian used phoenix flames, Bai Cang Shui let out a large blue river, flower petals rained down below Wan Zi Hong... All kinds of killer moves were used repeatedly, and under Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's support, the conflicts between them were greatly reduced, forming waves of attacks that followed one after the other with short gaps between each other. Lu Wei Yin and others got a feeling of Heavenly Court's attacks being continuous and unending.

Fang Yuan frowned, commenting in his mind: "Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has astonishing wisdom path attainment, even though Immortal Zombie Giant Sun is fighting her, he is not able to force out her limits. She still has the energy to support others and control the whole battlefield."

"So, from another angle, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun also hasn't used his full strength?"

The two venerables were fighting, although there were huge explosions and countless methods used, their power did not go beyond Qi Sea Ancestor's Hu elevation killer move.

Be they Star Constellation Immortal Venerable or Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, they were wary of triggering Limitless' countermeasures.

A venerable's foundation was unfathomable, if any one side were to trigger Limitless' countermeasures, the other side would gain an advantage.

Naturally, the important thing was that both venerables wanted to obtain the eternal life research results!

The value of this research was enormous to the point of being inestimable.

In the deadlock between venerables, if a venerable could obtain the eternal life research results, they could likely break the balance and become the strongest among the venerables!

Even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun were coveting the eternal life research results, so they had to restrain themselves right now. If they destroyed this formation in the midst of the intense battle, that would be a huge problem.

They were not Limitless, these truthful floating ice pieces were nurtured for over a million years. If any one of them was destroyed, the venerables would not be able to substitute it.

"Since it is so...." Fang Yuan's eyes shined brightly for a while, he suddenly commanded, "Qi Sea!"

Qi Sea Ancestor received the main body's voice transmission, he immediately used a killer move without hesitation.

Immortal killer move — Hu Elevation!

The terrifying qi path killer move descended once again.

The immortals evaded immediately.

Even the allied group of Qi Jue and Lu Wei Yin was the same.

"Are you insane?'

"Aren't you afraid of triggering Limitless' retaliation again?"

"No, maybe this is Fang Yuan's intention. Truly... amazing!"

The Gu Immortals were bewildered for a while before coming to a realization.

Lu Wei Yin's group was joyous, while the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were worried.

Sure enough, at the next moment, chains appeared from thin air and bound Qi Sea Ancestor.

But the thing was, Qi Sea Ancestor was currently on Star Constellation Chessboard Formation.

Limitless' countermeasures attacked Qi Sea, they naturally would not leave Star Constellation Chessboard Formation out.

Fang Yuan wanted to get the help of Limitless' countermeasures to break Star Constellation Chessboard Formation!

But at the next moment.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable suddenly got away from Immortal Zombie Giant Sun: "Fang Yuan, your scheme is wonderful, but how could I have not prepared for such a huge flaw? Please take a look."

The moment her words landed, starlight bloomed, many of the horizontal and vertical starry paths moved and attached on Limitless' chains.

After a few breaths of time, Limitless' chains were bound by starry paths and were under Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's control now.

Star Constellation Chessboard Formation was not disturbed by Limitless' countermeasures, instead, it made use of them. The strength of these chains were used to make Star Constellation Chessboard Formation even firmer.

"How could this be?!" Demon Immortal Qi Jue's expression changed.

Lu Wei Yin said through gritted teeth: "Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has prepared too well, her infiltration of Crazed Demon Cave is too deep."

This was not strange.

After all, when Crazed Demon Cave was just constructed, Limitless Demon Venerable attacked Heavenly Court and made a bet with Star Constellation's will.

That was to say, Heavenly Court had begun infiltrating Crazed Demon Cave the moment it was established.

This infiltration lasted over a million years!

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun obtained Savage Wilderness Great World, his infiltration of Crazed Demon Cave was about three hundred thousand years or so, it was not even half the time of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's infiltration.

Moreover, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable cultivated wisdom path, which excelled in infiltrating.

And Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's Yellow Earth Great World was only established over a hundred thousand years ago.

As for Fang Yuan, he was the most miserable one.

Although he came in touch with Crazed Demon Cave about ten or so years ago, his infiltration time of the Crazed Demon formation was almost zero.

If the Door of Life and Death was Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's home ground. Then Crazed Demon Cave was over fifty percent the home ground of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, while Immortal Zombie Giant Sun only had less than half the home ground advantage. Fang Yuan was like a guest, his understanding of Crazed Demon Cave mostly came from Paradise Earth's information.

Star Constellation Chessboard gained Limitless' chains, becoming even more powerful.

Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were unafraid of death, they used their lives to tie down the pseudo venerable opponents.

After all, an Immortal Venerable was helping them.

Naturally, they could not obstruct Fang Yuan's main body!

Fang Yuan's main body moved towards the sky and joined Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's battle.

As for Qi Sea Ancestor, he was bound by the chains. He could not even be put back into the sovereign immortal aperture, and could only leave his protection to Zhan Bu Du and others.

"Then, let's try this move." Fang Yuan took a deep breath, his gaze shining brightly.

Immortal killer move — Five Restriction Profound Light Qi!

Five colored light qi rapidly spread from around Fang Yuan. Be they Heavenly Court Gu Immortals or Lu Wei Yin's group, they all retreated.

They would suffer backlash every moment they fought in this five restriction profound light qi.

Five regional walls were manifesting once again through Fang Yuan's hands!

"This move again!" Prince Feng Xian and others gritted their teeth.

This move came from Tao Zhu, it had repeatedly made things difficult for Heavenly Court during the fate war and in Thieving Heaven's true inheritance space.

Right now, it became Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's issue!

Five restriction profound light qi was spreading in Star Constellation Chessboard Formation, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable immediately felt its effects as she started suffering backlash.

Those chains of Limitless on starry paths began to shake, eager to take action.

"Five restriction profound light qi is suppressed in this formation. But it looks like Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has not been able to find a way to break it."

"However... this method will trigger Limitless' countermeasures."

Fang Yuan observed carefully.

It was not strange for it to trigger Limitless' countermeasures. Five restriction profound light qi was the nemesis of Gu formations and Immortal Gu Houses, the Crazed Demon formation was also restrained. Inside five restriction profound light qi, the Crazed Demon formation would also suffer backlash, breaking apart eventually.

Limitless' arrangements would naturally detect this threat, so it was normal for five restriction profound light qi to trigger the countermeasures.

This was why Fang Yuan did not use five restriction profound light qi earlier.

As for the Door of Life and Death, there were too many soul path dao marks, even five restriction profound light qi would be suppressed. Moreover, even if the light qi became dense and formed five regional walls, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and the rest would also be endangered, it was not worth it.

But the current situation was different.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's methods were amazing, she actually used Star Constellation Chessboard Formation to forcibly merge Limitless' chains. At this stage, Fang Yuan suddenly used five restriction profound light qi to oppose it!

In an instant, the amount of things Star Constellation Immortal Venerable needed to calculate increased by over ten times.

She had to deal with Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, help Heavenly Court members fight the pseudo venerables, forcibly control Limitless' chains, and also accelerate the Crazed Demon formation to quickly produce eternal life research results.

Now, Fang Yuan activated five restriction profound light qi in Star Constellation Chessboard Formation, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had to endure the backlash as well as suppress Limitless' chains.

Fang Yuan's five restriction profound light qi was of extreme threat to the Crazed Demon formation, Limitless' chains were doing everything they could to shackle him. But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable must suppress it, if she did not suppress it and let it take effect freely, it would severely interfere and ultimately destroy Star Constellation Chessboard Formation.

Once the formation was destroyed, just these Heavenly Court Gu Immortals, even if they had the immortal graveyard, could not block the bloodthirsty pseudo venerables.

At that time, even if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable blocked Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Fang Yuan, she would not be able to guard the eternal life research results, and the pseudo venerables would gain them.

There were no two ways about it, Heavenly Court had too little manpower after all.

Even though Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had revived, her enemies were too numerous!

"Five restriction profound light qi, what an amazing move!" Shen Shang praised as he saw through the situation.

Even he felt bad for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!

Chapter 2200: Luck Gamble!

Fang Yuan activated five restriction profound light qi which inflicted backlash to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable at every moment. But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable needed to suppress Limitless' chains and control them, she was basically protecting Fang Yuan.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable heaved a deep sigh.

Even if she was the number one person in the wisdom path, she had more problems than she could cope with.

From her point of view: Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was the strongest enemy in her life, she had to pay enough attention to him. Comparatively, Fang Yuan's threat was lower, but he could not be ignored. After all, many venerables had invested in him, even Star Costellation's will had invested in him when Spectral Soul refined sovereign immortal fetus Gu.

Fang Yuan could not be left alone, if he was allowed to act as he pleased, he would give her huge problems!

Having this understanding, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable suddenly took out Book Mountain.

A chess piece flew out, it was Zhou Xiong Xin!

Zhou Xiong Xin landed on the middle of the mountain and controlled it with all his strength.

Book Mountain let out golden light, they were actually Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's luck path killer moves.

These luck path killer moves attacked Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, stopping him temporarily.

Almost at the same time, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable attacked Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan did not activate Dang Hun Luo Po Seal.

This method was amplified by his countless dao marks, it was far stronger than Hu elevation. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could disregard the cost to retrieve Star Constellation Chessboard Formation and release Limitless' chains.

Adding on the previous accumulated 'hatred' towards five restriction profound light qi, Fang Yuan would be fiercely shackled by Limitless' chains, his situation would be even worse than Qi Sea Ancestor's.

At that time, Fang Yuan would lose his battle strength, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could take out Star Constellation Chessboard again and make the situation greatly advantageous for Heavenly Court.

Naturally, in the process of Star Constellation Chessboard being stored and taken out, it would be damaged, and even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would suffer damage.

But how great would this damage be?

According to Fang Yuan's estimation, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could endure it.

So, Fang Yuan did not attack, instead he retreated into the five restriction profound light qi.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled.

Fang Yuan's action was within her expectations.

Information about Dang Hun Luo Po Seal had already been transmitted from the Door of Life and Death. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was slightly disappointed that Fang Yuan did not use this method.

But, Fang Yuan retreating into the five restriction profound light qi made it convenient for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to take her next action.

At the next moment, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gave a cry. Hundreds of vertical and horizontal starry paths twisted and turned like water waves, they quickly gathered and weaved an azure sphere, covering all the five restriction profound light qi and Fang Yuan inside.

Fang Yuan was actually sealed.

Five restriction profound light qi was still continuing to spread, but the space inside the azure sphere was vast. It would take a long time to fill it completely.

"An excellent response." Fang Yuan praised.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used wisdom path and star path to imitate space path. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not break five restriction profound light qi, but found a way to restrain it.

This response was amazing, not only did she use Star Constellation Chessboard Formation to a whole new level, there were extraordinary methods like dao embroidery used as well.

Fang Yuan was trapped, but he was not hurried.

He waited for Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's performance.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was extremely shrewd, he definitely realized Heavenly Court's weakness and his side's advantage.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable took the risk to deal with Fang Yuan, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun had a good chance of success over on his end. On the contrary, if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable dealt with Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, Fang Yuan could make some arrangements. Although the strength of these cheap tricks was small, they would definitely cause great annoyance to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. If they were not resolved immediately, these cheap tricks would become the key to suppressing Heavenly Court!

Sure enough, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun shouted, a giant wave of golden light pushed Book Mountain aside as it charged towards Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Book Mountain was sent flying like a meteor.

Zhou Xiong Xin, who was on the mountain, was already smashed to a pulp. This was the price of forcefully controlling Book Mountain!

This rank eight expert used all his strength but only stopped Immortal Zombie Giant Sun for a few breaths of time. This was the case even when he had Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's help, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun had also restrained his strength to prevent damaging Limitless' formation.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun managed to get some free time, he immediately began preparing a method.

This chance did not come easily. When he fought with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable earlier, they attacked constantly, he had no such chances.

However, at the next moment.

"This killer move is finally complete." Golden Hooped Great Immortal suddenly appeared, "Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, you fooled me, I invited you to Heavenly Court as a guest, but you took the chance to make your arrangements. During the fate war, Heavenly Court headquarters was ambushed by your Longevity Heaven!"

The moment he finished speaking, Golden Hooped Great Immortal used his life and all his cultivation to activate a killer move.

The mysterious light shone down and fell on Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's head, turning into a golden hoop.

The golden hoop bound Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's forehead, causing his mind and body to turn slightly sluggish.

A female immortal appeared behind Immortal Zombie Giant Sun.

It was Qin Ding Ling!

"Giant Sun, I am repaying you for all the humiliation you have given me back then!!" Qin Ding Ling shouted, slamming her hands on Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's back.

Immortal killer move — Luck Gamble!

A black and white Gu worm resembling a die flew out of Qin Ding Ling's phantom aperture, it rolled rapidly before coming to a stop.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun — Three!

The die Gu worm rolled once again before coming to a stop, revealing a number on its surface.

Qin Ding Ling — Five!

Bam!

In an instant, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's vast luck was transferred to Qin Ding Ling.

Qin Ding Ling's body shook, her face reddened, and her teeth clattered together. She could only endure with all her strength and had no strength to fight for the moment.

"Back then, when I forcibly took away a portion of Crazed Demon Cave's Thieving Heaven true inheritance, a mysterious Immortal Gu escaped, I could not catch it in time. It seems like it was obtained by you in the end." Immortal Zombie Giant Sun came to a realization.

Qin Ding Ling perspired profusely as she took in the endless luck while replying with hatred: "To deal with you, I gave up on metal path, I sealed and buried myself deep under the earth in a metal coffin, cultivating in seclusion as I comprehended luck path. During these three hundred thousand years, this gamble Gu was attracted to me and came to the metal coffin one day. From that moment, I realized this was the backlash of you forcefully taking Thieving Heaven's true inheritance, it is also my fortuitous encounter to take revenge. Gamble, gamble, let us gamble with our lives!"

The intense golden light around Immortal Zombie Giant Sun dimmed rapidly.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's expression turned solemn.

The foundation of his combat system was based on powerful and prosperous luck. He had all kinds of killer moves that helped him to maintain positive and powerful luck, for instance, the unforeseen disaster killer move he used in the Door of Life and Death, to extract his bad luck to deal with the enemy. Although it reduced the size of his luck, his luck path methods quickly restored it, on the whole, his luck became even better.

Once Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's positive luck was stronger than the enemy's, his defense, offense, healing and other aspects would also rise based on the difference, always being higher than his enemy's.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's methods were extremely powerful and exquisite. Under the support of such a combat system, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was invincible.

His luck path methods had never been spread, how could other Gu Immortals seize his luck?

Most Gu Immortals' luck would fall to rock-bottom within ten or so rounds, while Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's strength would continue to rise.

While it looked like Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was in a stalemate with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, the fact was that he had already accumulated a huge advantage in terms of luck. At the final juncture, when the Crazed Demon formation stops and the eternal life research results emerge, without Limitless' retaliation anymore, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun could erupt with extreme strength.

But now, Qin Ding Ling dug at his foundation!

Qin Ding Ling had almost performed a miracle!

Just based on gamble Gu, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's retaliation would not be able to accomplish this.

Just Qin Ding Ling alone also could not accomplish this.

Even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's arrangements and schemes alone could not dig at Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's foundation.

But these three factors joined to achieve a miracle-like achievement!

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun immediately activated a killer move, his thoughts increased and collided rapidly: "I fell for Star Constellation's scheme."

"She had already prepared this trump card to deal with me, but just did not have a chance before."

"When Fang Yuan used five restriction profound light qi, she saw the chance."

"She intentionally left to deal with Fang Yuan, even throwing out Book Mountain, it was just to show me weakness."

"She succeeded after all!"

Book Mountain was a secluded domain of heaven and earth, but in Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's eyes, it was only a chess piece that could be casually thrown.

In fact, many Heavenly Court members on Star Constellation Chessboard Formation were all Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's chess pieces.

Even Fang Yuan was used by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to lure Immortal Zombie Giant Sun!

Just like how Immortal Zombie Giant Sun took Heavenly Court as his enemy, Heavenly Court also considered Longevity Heaven and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun as an obstacle.

Fang Yuan?

Although Fang Yuan was very strong, even destroying fate Gu, he was selected by heaven's will and received the help of venerables. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used Fang Yuan, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable also made arrangements for Fang Yuan...

Fang Yuan was a chess piece.

Even if Fang Yuan's ambition was huge, wanting to become a refinement path venerable, turning into a player from a chess piece, Primordial Domain was already destroyed, how could he become refinement path Demon Venerable?

If he could not become venerable, even if he had more dao marks, he would only be a pseudo venerable.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had already returned to being Dao Lords!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable left Fang Yuan and returned to fight Immortal Zombie Giant Sun.

"Go." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable pointed at Qin Ding Ling, Star Constellation Chessboard Formation activated, the chess piece Qin Ding Ling immediately disappeared on the spot and appeared at the edge of the battlefield.

The killer move luck gamble was already activated, Qin Ding Ling had completed this crucial part!

Luck gamble!

After Qin Ding Ling recovered, she activated the killer move again.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun — Three!

Qin Ding Ling — Two!

Boom...

At this time, Qin Ding Ling's luck surged out and transferred back to Immortal Zombie Giant Sun.

Luck gamble killer move's power was like this, it could not be controlled by people. The numbers determined victory or defeat, but the outcome was determined randomly, even Qin Ding Ling, who was the user could not influence it.

Chapter 2201: Damn You, Fang Yuan!

Back then, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had expended his own theft path dao marks to refine this gamble Gu!

Gamble Gu gave random results that could not be influenced by anyone.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was special, he was an otherworldly demon who possessed otherworldly dao marks. Thieving Heaven's space was founded on the basis of his otherworldly dao marks. Meanwhile, gamble Gu was refined with his otherworldly theft path dao marks.

Gamble Gu did not have any offensive power by itself, it was powerless no matter what the result was. But the luck gamble killer move that used it as the core was extremely dangerous.

Whether it succeeded or failed, there was no way to predict it.

But it was because of this characteristic, even Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's luck could not interfere with it.

The probability of winning the luck gamble was equal for both Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Qin Ding Ling.

Qin Ding Ling won the previous time, now, it was Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's win.

However, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun did not feel any joy.

Because whether she lost or won, Qin Ding Ling would only profit.

The reason?

It was due to the profundity of luck path.

Luck was essentially categorized into two types: good luck and bad luck. The size of luck varied from person to person; in general, the higher the cultivation, the larger the luck.

Comparing Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's and Qin Ding Ling's luck.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's luck was extremely vast, it was at Dao Lord level. There was little bad luck, while good luck occupied the majority of it.

And Qin Ding Ling?

Qin Ding Ling's luck was far smaller than Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's. Bad luck occupied most of it, while good luck was little.

Qin Ding Ling was only a rank eight expert, her luck would naturally be smaller than Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's.

Luck was a variable! She was against a powerful enemy like Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, with the luck of all living beings influencing each other, even if she had good luck, it would be affected and turned into bad luck.

Thus, firstly, Qin Ding Ling's luck was far smaller than her opponent's. She was basically gambling with a smaller chip, this was a huge advantage in itself.

Secondly, Qin Ding Ling had a lot of bad luck, when it was transferred to Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, it would contaminate his luck as well.

The basis of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's combat system was positive and powerful luck. This had two crucial points, one was he needed to have vast luck, the other was that his luck needed to be positive, which meant the more good luck he had, the better.

If Qin Ding Ling won more and lost less in the luck gamble, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's luck would greatly decrease. If Qin Ding Ling won less and lost more, even though Immortal Zombie Giant Sun would obtain her luck, it would mostly contain bad luck.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun fell into a dilemma.

He had many methods to transform his bad luck into good luck. But this process would spend immortal essence and mental energy, he would be sacrificing many opportunities when he battled Star Constellation Immortal Venerable again.

Even worse was that once he turned his bad luck into good luck, and he lost to Qin Ding Ling in the next luck gamble, what would he do?

Would he not be reinforcing the enemy?

Bam bam bam...

There was a chain of self-detonations, over thirty truthful floating ice pieces were destroyed.

There was only ten percent or so remaining of the Crazed Demon formation!

The Crazed Demon formation's power continued to weaken, there was also only about forty percent remaining of the great world in the eighth layer. Everything was used to nurture the central truthful floating ice piece.

The three Crazed Demon Eccentrics continued to carve the truthful floating ice, their expressions becoming fanatic.

The strength of Limitless' countermeasures originated from the Crazed Demon formation. If not for this, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable or Immortal Zombie Giant Sun would have already destroyed the source of Limitless' countermeasures.

Back then, Limitless Demon Venerable had deliberately arranged it as one whole to make others hold themselves back if they wanted to obtain eternal life research results. They had to accept the threat and be indistinctly restricted by the countermeasures.

As the Crazed Demon formation continued to disappear, the upper limits of strength in the Gu Immortals' fight continued to rise.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun used more powerful methods.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable similarly raised the strength of her skills.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was being hindered by Qin Ding Ling, he unavoidably fell into a disadvantage.

"We must kill Qin Ding Ling!" This became a general consensus.

Not only Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, other pseudo venerables also attacked.

But this was Star Constellation Chessboard Formation, since Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's painstaking scheme against Immortal Zombie Giant Sun succeeded, how could she let Qin Ding Ling be attacked easily?

"The situation is not good, we need to reinforce Giant Sun Immortal Venerable!"

"If we want to support Giant Sun, we need to kill Qin Ding Ling. At worst, we need to disturb and break her killer move."

"But Star Constellation Chessboard Formation can transfer her anywhere instantly, so we still need to destroy this formation first!"

After back and forth discussions, it still returned to the starting point.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

Stars shot forward one after the other, destroying the protective golden light, and forcing Immortal Zombie Giant Sun to retreat.

Guh.

He coughed out cold, dark corpse blood. Starlight shone on his chest, no matter how his golden light spread, the starlight was still shining brightly. His injuries were very heavy!

Because of Qin Ding Ling impeding him, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's battle strength had fallen sharply. He was actually showing signs of defeat in the battle with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!

Looking at Immortal Zombie Giant Sun coughing blood, the expressions of Lu Wei Yin and the others changed.

Was Immortal Zombie Giant Sun going to lose in the battle of two venerables?

The previous battle situation already proved that Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was the strongest battle strength in the allied forces, second was Gu Yue Fang Yuan. If Immortal Zombie Giant Sun were to be defeated, that would mean the allied forces lost!

However, no matter how unwilling Lu Wei Yin and the rest were, they were aware that it was normal for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to have such an advantage.

There were many factors that influenced a fight between Gu Immortals.

One was cultivation level and number of dao marks. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun were equal in this.

Second was immortal essence and Immortal Gu. Both sides were about the same.

Third was battle experience. It was a draw between Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun.

Fourth was external environment, whether it could be used or not. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable exceeded Immortal Zombie Giant Sun in this aspect, at least, it was true for the moment.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun used Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace, Calamity Luck Altar, and Savage Wilderness Great World. He then allied with Fang Yuan, deliberately destroyed Primordial Domain, then allied with Fang Yuan again to explore the Crazed Demon formation and the Door of Life and Death.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable fought many battles using the strength of Book Mountain, Primordial Domain, Crazed Demon formation, immortal graveyard, Door of Life and Death, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, Green Lotus Great World, Star Constellation Chessboard, and Limitless' countermeasures.

Fifth were combat methods. Gu formations, battlefield killer moves, Gu houses, and all kinds of killer moves. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Immortal Zombie Giant Sun were both excellent beyond doubt in this aspect, it was hard to tell who was better.

Sixth was combat system.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's combat system contained extremely powerful potential for later, but it was miraculously cracked by Qin Ding Ling.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also possessed an exceptional combat system which she had been using all along.

This combat system was the combined combat systems of Ming Hao, Yu Xiu, and Feng Ya.

In the offensive aspect, the main method was Fairy Ming Hao's flying star killer move.

Wisdom path Gu Immortals often used exquisite killer moves because of the superiority of their path. These killer moves usually contained many Gu worms and had complicated procedures for activation. This was why the calculation ability of wisdom path Gu Immortals was extraordinary, only then could they control their killer moves properly.

But in Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's combat system, the flying star method was almost the only method in the offensive aspect, it could be said to be extremely lacking and unvaried!

Was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable intentionally throwing away the obvious advantage of wisdom path?

That was not the case.

First of all, the killer move flying star looked simple but that was not true. If it was used repeatedly one after the other, every move would be a consecutive move. Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was hit by so many stars that by now, the injuries caused by the stars had reached the point of inflicting serious injuries.

Secondly, the deficiency in the offensive aspect was exactly Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's ingenuity.

Looking at the whole combat system, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable took out the calculation requirement from the offense aspect and transferred it onto herself, letting her have an immense grasp over the battle situation at all times!

It was because of this grasp over the situation that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could use all the surrounding resources to the limit, even as the weak side, she could win against the strong, against the strong alliance army that had high numbers, she actually led Heavenly Court to the height of victory.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's combat system could use the environment to suppress enemies and use emotions to affect them. Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was one of the victims.

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable were equal in many aspects. However, in this deadlock, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's combat system was obstructed, while Star Constellation Immortal Venerable continued to maintain her combat system and her advantages.

These advantages were insignificant alone, but they stacked together until Immortal Zombie Giant Sun fell into the danger of losing!

"Fang Yuan, it is time to stake our lives and fight, what are you still hesitating for?!" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun suddenly shot towards the azure sphere.

Luck path killer moves erupted like a rainstorm, attempting to break the sphere and release Fang Yuan.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was already guarded against this. She immediately attacked, star shadows flickered, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun suffered a heavy attack again, his killer move was also destroyed halfway.

"We must help Fang Yuan, he will reinforce Giant Sun Immortal Venerable." Lu Wei Yin called out.

Paradise Earth sighed: "Sigh, if my tomb had not been destroyed, I would have venerable cultivation level now and be able to resolve this predicament."

"These damned fodder!" Zhan Bu Du waved his punch, killing another Heavenly Court member. However, these Heavenly Court Gu Immortals would revive shortly afterwards, there was no way to kill them completely.

What's more, there was still Qi Sea Ancestor behind Zhan Bu Du.

Half of the Limitless' chains on Qi Sea Ancestor had already disappeared.

On one hand, other Gu Immortals were helping him, on the other hand, the Crazed Demon formation itself was shrinking. The upper limit of strength in the Gu Immortals' fights was continuously increasing, there was now a much higher tolerance for the killer move Hu elevation.

However, Qi Sea Ancestor still did not have the strength to protect himself, he required Zhan Bu Du's constant protection.

"Everyone, protect me!" Paradise Earth shouted, retreating to the center of the group.

The other immortals protected him and gave Paradise Earth precious time to use his killer move.

Heaven path killer move — Heavenly Summary Earthly Norm.

A mysterious aura spread from his body and charged towards the azure sphere like an air wave.

This killer move was extremely profound, it could restore heaven and earth to its normal state, it was the nemesis of battlefield killer moves.

It was perfect to break the encirclement!

The azure sphere was already enduring the pressure from Fang Yuan, now that the killer move heavenly summary earthly norm hit, it immediately collapsed.

Fang Yuan gave a loud shout, as he flew out like a tiger let out of its cage.

"Paradise Earth, I hope you can lend me a hand again!" Fang Yuan sent out a multi-colored rainbow, taking Paradise Earth as he charged towards Qin Ding Ling!

Heaven path killer move — Heavenly Summary Earthly Norm!

Paradise Earth took in a deep breath, after using the killer move, his orifices started bleeding, his face became pale as paper.

Formless air currents moved forward, everywhere they went, starry paths broke down, turning into nothingness.

Without the starry paths, it was difficult for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to move Qin Ding Ling.

Her eyes flickered with cold light, she immediately gave up on rescuing Qin Ding Ling and fiercely attacked Immortal Zombie Giant Sun instead.

"Damn you, Fang Yuan!" Immortal Zombie Giant Sun roared, his chest was torn from the attack and his soul was heavily injured.

At this time, Qin Ding Ling was killed by Fang Yuan.

However, Immortal Zombie Giant Sun could not turn the situation around. Thousands of stardust shot towards him, he destroyed most of them but several hundreds still struck his body.

So much starlight accumulated in Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's injuries that they were already intense like fire!

Immortal Zombie Giant Sun was close to death.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable continued to attack him ruthlessly.

The final fatal attack!

Chapter 2202: Chu Du's Danger

Northern Plains.

Chu tribe headquarters.

"First supreme elder is still in closed cultivation? Today is the day of the battle." Chou Lao Wu continued to rub his hands together. He was thin with a slightly humped back, his naturally sad face looked even more depressed right now.

"Relax, since first supreme elder agreed to Black Moon's challenge, why would he retreat just before the fight? We just need to wait patiently." Hao Zhen was leaning on a wall with arms crossed in front of him, he showed a composed expression.

He was a middle aged bearded man, he was tall and muscular. He and Chou Lao Wu were good friends, the two could activate a signature killer move called wind thunder roar together.

Because of this, Chou Lao Wu and Hao Zhen were called the wind and lightning demons. After siding with Chu Du, they became second only to Chu Du as the strongest battle strength of Chu tribe!

"Actually, avoiding the battle is also an option." In another direction, Immortal Wang suddenly said softly.

He had a short stature, he had a red nose and small triangular eyes, he was a transformation path Gu Immortal who was proficient in transforming into dog breeds.

"What did you say?!" Hao Zhen was infuriated, he quickly approached Immortal Wang, staring at him with furious eyes, "Is first supreme elder someone who avoids a battle? He is the mighty Chu Du, are you trying to defame first supreme elder?"

Hao Zhen held Immortal Wang by his shirt and raised him to the air.

Immortal Wang was immediately furious, shouting: "Let go! You brute, if you don't let go, don't blame me for attacking you!"

Seeing the situation getting out of hand, Chou Lao Wu quickly pulled Hao Zhen away, while Li Si Chun held Immortal Wang.

Li Si Chun had a square face with thick eyebrows and huge eyes, his nose bridge was very tall, his chest had thick black hair that was exposed, he was a man but he wore a flowery skirt.

He tapped his fingers together and said in a feminine voice :"Come on, don't argue, okay? I am already agitated, if we have an internal fight now, then our Chu tribe will really face a crisis."

Immortal Wang snorted coldly, flinging away Li Si Chun's hand: "This is Chu tribe's crisis. We should deal with it cautiously! If first supreme elder was still a lone force, it would not matter to us if he battled or not. But he is not, he is our Chu tribe's first supreme elder. Do you know what the consequences will be if he loses? You brute!"

Hao Zhen snorted, not saying a word.

Because he knew Immortal Wang was not wrong.

Chu Du established a sect called Chu Sect. He used his connections and methods to invite many immortals to go against Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, but he allied with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu later and forced these Gu Immortals into joining him to form Chu Sect.

His actions turned the situation around.

After establishing Chu Sect, Chu Du used his charisma and tricks to subdue the people's hearts.

But good times did not last long. Under the pressure of Longevity Heaven and the Huang Jin tribes, Chu Du was forced to change Chu Sect into Chu tribe.

Thus, Chu Du took in his trained strength path Gu Immortals as his adopted children, removing the sect system and using the tribe system to rule.

Even so, Chu tribe was still being doubted and pressured because Chu Du had no children of his own.

Thereupon, Chu Du took the initiative to participate in the fate war, this decision helped to stabilize Chu tribe's status.

The situation changed again now.

Fate Gu was destroyed, the rumors of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's revival kept on growing larger. Longevity Heaven sent a command to Northern Plains' righteous path to subdue lone and demonic immortals, attempting to unite Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

Lone and demonic immortals were extremely resistant towards this, they felt disgusted towards the Huang Jin tribes.

Because of this, Bai Zu tribe and Chu tribe became much more attractive to join.

Many of the lone and demonic immortals were solitary. They would rather choose to join Chu tribe and Bai Zu tribe than join the Huang Jin tribes.

Chu Du was of lone cultivator origin, Bai Zu tribe's Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was too.

These two tribes benefited from this and expanded quite a lot.

As a result, they were being watched secretly by Longevity Heaven.

"Sigh, where did this Fairy Black Moon come from? Her origin is mysterious, it is like she came out of a rock, we cannot investigate her background at all."

"Northern Plains is such a large region, there are many hidden experts, what is so strange about Fairy Black Moon? But she actually challenged first supreme elder, she is just asking for humiliation!"

"Not necessarily. Objectively speaking, this person is extremely strong. After she appeared, she continuously challenged many experts, but has yet to face a defeat. In the most recent challenge, she even defeated Liu Chang. Fairy Black Moon revealed new methods in almost every battle. Her totem killer move is her trump card, and she is even rumored to be an inheritor of Reckless Savage."

Chou Lao Wu and the group discussed.

Currently, Hei Lou Lan had a huge reputation, she won repeatedly, displaying peak rank seven battle strength that was comparable to rank eight strength! And also because of the rumors of being Reckless Savage's inheritor, her overall prestige suppressed Chu Du.

"I can already see Fairy Black Moon's aims. She has huge ambitions, she gathered so many people around her, challenging people to gain reputation. Right now, she has already become a symbol and banner of the demonic path and lone cultivators. It was an inevitable matter for her to challenge Lord Chu Du. Even if she did not challenge him now, she would have to challenge sooner or later. Because once she wins, her reputation will double at least, and she will have authority to lead Northern Plains' lone and demonic immortals!" Hao Zhen analyzed.

Under the pressure, lone and demonic immortals who were willing to surrender to the righteous path had already surrendered.

The remaining ones were recalcitrants.

And these recalcitrants had a few tricks up their sleeves. After all, without strength, they had no qualifications to be stubborn.

And to these recalcitrants, Chu Du, who had established a righteous path tribe and worked with the Huang Jin tribes, even having participated in the fate war, was clearly Longevity Heaven's dog. To them, he was even more hateful than the Huang Jin tribes.

If Fairy Black Moon defeated Chu Du, she would definitely win their hearts. Her gains would no doubt be much more remarkable than when she defeated Liu Chang.

On the contrary, Chu tribe was already being suppressed by Longevity Heaven, it had to fully rely on Chu Du.

Chu tribe was not tied together using blood relationship, the master-disciple system also could not be openly established. The tribe was mostly maintained by Chu Du's charisma alone.

Chu Du was the spiritual banner of Chu tribe, should this banner collapse, Chu tribe would definitely suffer heavily. Their progress would be severely obstructed, they would lose their grasp of the people's hearts, they would start to decline rapidly.

People like Chou Lao Wu were worried. Right now, they had already become Chu tribe's core members who enjoyed the benefits.

They did not want Chu tribe to decline.

"Sigh, if we could ask for darling, Lord Fang Yuan's help, that would be great." Li Si Chun sighed.

Immortal Wang shook his head: "No, that is too risky. Lord Fang Yuan's demonic might is indeed awe-inspiring, maybe even Longevity Heaven will show restraint. But what if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable revives in the future? Although Fang Yuan is strong, he is not a match for a venerable. If we do this, it will just be a short term pleasure. But it is actually a stupid way to isolate ourselves from Northern Plains' righteous path."

"Keep quiet. They are here." Chou Lao Wu suddenly reminded.

More than ten Gu Immortals came this time.

Half were Chu Du's adopted sons, they cultivated strength path and had ordinary cultivation level.

The rest were those lone and demonic immortals that Chu tribe had recruited recently.

Although their strength was higher than the adopted sons, their loyalty was unable to be verified for the moment, so it was rather troublesome to use them.

"External elders, where is lord father?"

"First supreme elder?"

"It is already the appointed time, why has first supreme elder not appeared yet?"

These people asked all kinds of questions.

"Who allowed you to come?" Hao Zhen walked forward, Chou Lao Wu, Immortal Wang, and Li Si Chun stood behind him, coldly watching these newcomers.

At this moment, the four immortals restrained their internal conflict and stood up as one.

"External elders, please don't blame us, we are really concerned about our adopted father's safety."

"Yes, since we joined Chu tribe, Lord Chu Du is our leader. Is it wrong for us to feel concerned?"

It became noisy again.

Their anxiety was clear as day.

Hao Zhen was just about to berate them when an aura spread, which made the immortals turn around.

The closed bronze door of the secret room opened. Chu Du walked out slowly with an indifferent expression.

"First supreme elder."

"Lord father!"

"Hmm." Chu Du nodded slightly, smiling as he looked around, "Since you are here, hold the line for me."

Chu Du's mood was heavy.

The actual situation was much more serious than what Li Si Chun and the rest discussed.

These recently recruited lone and demonic immortals were opportunists, there might even be spies among them.

The adopted sons looked respectful and humble, but in fact, they already held resentment towards Chu Du. On one hand, they blamed Chu Du for cultivating them into strength path that had uncertain prospects, on the other hand, when they underwent immortal ascension, Chu Du used them to absorb Reckless Savage's true meaning, causing them to suffer huge losses.

Chu Du was aware: Chu tribe seemed to be united, but it was already at the juncture of declining!

If he could win against Fairy Black Moon, Chu Du could still maintain the original state. If he were to be defeated, Chu tribe would definitely decline, and it would likely be a disastrous decline. People would look down on them, no one would join, they would keep on growing weaker until Chu tribe members became cannon fodder in the five regions chaotic war.

"Lord, with so many people leaving, what about our territory's defense?" Chou Lao Wu asked.

Chu Du waved his sleeve, saying with a carefree tone: "It doesn't matter. How many resource points do we have that are truly valuable? As for the headquarters, Gu Immortals need to be stationed, draw sticks to settle it."

Although Chu tribe was established, they had few resource points and were of poor quality. It could be said they were lacking resources to develop.

Like this, a few unlucky Gu Immortals were selected to guard the headquarters. Chu Du took almost all the Chu tribe Gu Immortals towards the appointed battlefield.

Chu Du was not even a little panicked, moving leisurely.

On the way, Gu Immortals of the Huang Jin tribes appeared and joined Chu Du's group.

These Gu Immortals might exclude Chu tribe and Bai Zu tribe secretly during normal times, but they naturally stood beside Chu Du when facing an outsider like Fairy Black Moon.

When they were halfway through the journey, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu appeared.

Only then did Chu Du truly let out a sigh of relief.

Chapter 2203: Blood Sea Clone

It was only Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's clone, but it was still at rank eight, the immortals quickly paid their respects.

Chu Du was satisfied.

Although Heavenly Lord Bai Zu did not personally come to back him up, Chu Du knew Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had an exquisite method that could let the clone and main body switch places instantly. Thus, with this clone here, it was no different from Heavenly Lord Bai Zu personally being here.

At this crucial moment, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was a reliable partner for Chu Du.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had been paying a lot of attention to the impending battle of Chu Du and Fairy Black Moon.

After all, with Longevity Heaven above them and the unity of the Huang Jin tribes, Bai Zu tribe and Chu tribe had to stay allied and endure the immense pressure together.

It was just that he had a really urgent mission at this time.

The only one that could summon him was naturally Longevity Heaven.

Currently, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was in Longevity Heaven, beside him was the current generation South Desolation Immortal — Yao Huang.

Seeing Heavenly Lord Bai Zu slightly out of sorts, Yao Huang understood inwardly, smiling: "Bai Zu, who do you think will win in the fight between Chu Du and Black Moon?"

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu retracted his consciousness, smiling bitterly: "From my angle, I naturally hope Chu Du can win. However, Fairy Black Moon is no small character, her strength is hard to estimate. This will definitely be a fierce battle!"

"Lord Bai Zu is correct."

"Both cultivate strength path, one has been renowned for a long time, while the other's reputation is rising rapidly. It is indeed hard to tell who is stronger, only the fight will determine the winner and the loser."

"That Fairy Black Moon seems to have inherited Reckless Savage's true inheritance, her strength path attainment cannot be underestimated."

"In my view, Chu Du still has a higher chance of winning. After all, he is a legendary person who had once pressured the whole of Liu tribe!"

The moment these words came out, Liu tribe Gu Immortals snorted coldly with displeased expressions.

A large group of Gu Immortals had gathered around Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Yao Huang, they were all from Huang Jin tribes.

As the Gu Immortals were discussing, Five Elements Grandmaster suddenly flew over: "Alright, the formation is set, please enter the formation."

A large formation was set up in front of the immortals.

Beautiful blood-red lines were all over the formation.

The Huang Jin tribes' Gu Immortals stopped talking as they entered the formation, among them was Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, who brought Hei tribe's Gu Immortals.

Soon, only Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Yao Huang remained at the periphery of the formation.

Yao Huang looked at the formation, saying suddenly: "It is good if Chu Du wins, but if he fails, Black Moon might really rise to power. Did you secretly help Chu Du?"

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu shook his head: "I won't lie to you, I had suggested this to him, but it was rejected. He only wants to use his strength path attainment to fight this battle. To him, this strength path battle holds extraordinary significance."

Yao Huang thought to himself, smiling inwardly: "Chu Du will lose, and it is a certain loss. Hei Lou Lan was nurtured by our Ancestor, her strength is beyond her peers, and with effort Gu helping her, her cultivation level, killer moves, and other aspects are progressing rapidly. Meanwhile, Hei Lou Lan already knows the information regarding Chu Du. With this win, Hei Lou Lan will become a leading character in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world. Later on, she will be able to lead lone and demonic immortals with her every action."

Right at this time, the sky of Longevity Heaven suddenly changed, warning alarms started ringing!

This was the arranged signal!

"How could it be so early?" Yao Huang's expression changed greatly, as he shouted, "Quickly activate the formation!"

Even without his reminder, Five Elements Grandmaster, who was in charge of the formation, was already activating it.

The formation buzzed loudly as blood-red light bloomed.

The

This formation was actually a rank eight blood path immortal formation!

The blood path formation produced a mysterious strength that quickly disappeared from the formation and transferred to a mysterious place.

At this time.

Crazed Demon Cave, ninth layer, in Star Constellation Chessboard Formation.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made the fatal move!

Whoosh.

Suddenly, the near-dead Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's body burned with blood-red flames.

Countless Gu worms shone and flew around inside Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's aperture, forming a killer move that drew in the blood path divine power from Longevity Heaven!

Among them, familial emotion Gu was the first core, next to familial emotion Gu was imitation Gu. This time, imitation Gu had already transformed into blood relation Gu, which was the second core.

The blood path divine power quickly spread throughout Immortal Zombie Giant Sun's body. His ice-cold immortal zombie black blood burned intensely like boiling water.

Golden rays shot out from the black blood and spread rapidly like water. After a few breaths of time, all the blood in Immortal Zombie Giant Sun turned into the color of gold.

His dry black skin, like that of a withered tree, became filled with vitality as it regained a white luster.

Thorn-like hair quickly grew and draped down to his shoulders.

His eyes that were dark and dim earlier started shining in golden light now.

His entire body began to grow taller, he had a slightly hunched back earlier, but was now standing tall with bulging muscles, he became a middle aged man of over nine feet in height.

Boom!

Blood colored radiance spread, causing winds and clouds to stir.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had completely revived!

The whole revival process was extremely short. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable found that she was not able to break the blood-red barrier of light around Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, and even sensed hints of a trap around Immortal Zombie Giant Sun, so she watched from the side.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's gaze was deep: "As I expected, Blood Sea Ancestor was your clone."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled, showing his white teeth: "Star Constellation, you cultivate wisdom path primarily with star path as your secondary path. Genesis Lotus cultivates wood path and painting path. Thieving Heaven cultivates theft path primarily with space path as the secondary path. With one main and one specialty path, us venerables can compete with each other on equal grounds. And in my case, I chose blood path."

"It is just that the timing was not right when I was alive. Only after countless years past my death was there enough foundation for my Blood Sea clone to create blood path. And talents emerged in Heavenly Court as well, there first were Gu Immortal Fei Shuang and Ning Xue, this master and disciple pair who hunted down my Blood Sea clone. Later, refinement path great grandmaster Lian Shen Ke refined blood relation Immortal Gu which almost destroyed my plan. Fortunately, I had backup methods."

Heavenly Court had already felt something strange about Blood Sea Ancestor.

Thus, they constructed Demon Judgment Board to suppress blood path.

Although Immortal Zombie Giant Sun succeeded in reviving, the progress of blood path was seriously impeded, it did not develop into a mainstream path and was always treated like a detestable path. Even though super forces researched it, they only did it behind closed doors.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's original plan was to keep luck path a secret while borrowing the strength of the world to perfect blood path, but blood path ended up being obstructed.

If blood path had been prosperous, the current Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's strength would have risen much more.

"Forget it, how can everything go as one wishes?" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable heaved a sigh, his gaze moving past Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, past the formation, towards the distance.

There were only a few truthful floating ice pieces left in the Crazed Demon formation.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable solemnly gathered her concentration.

In front of her was a fully revived Giant Sun Immortal Venerable with no trace of injuries, and although his strength had not been restored to the peak state, it was similar to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's.

And Qin Ding Ling was still in the process of revival. Luck gamble was already used before and would be difficult to use again with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable already on guard against it.

Star Constellation and Giant Sun's fight was definitely going to be an uncontrollable battle of life and death.

However, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable felt troubled if she had to fight without any considerations. The current situation was not simple, she had various misgivings.

At this time, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable suddenly sighed: "Star Constellation, the eternal life research results are right before our eyes, let's hold off our fight for the moment. How about we join hands and get rid of these irrelevant people first?"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was dazed for a bit before nodding with a smile: "That is appropriate, we should do that."

These two venerables were still fighting a life and death battle earlier, but they were actually working together now!

This was undoubtedly a wise move.

It would be a shame if bystanders got benefits when two tigers fought.

Thereupon, the sensible Star Constellation and Giant Sun were naturally going to get rid of the weak ones first!

Boom!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable directly charged towards Fang Yuan, countless golden light rays shot at Fang Yuan like spears or swords.

This was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable showing his sincerity to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Fang Yuan was with Paradise Earth, and he had killed Qin Ding Ling not long ago.

"You defend while I attack." Fang Yuan said to Paradise Earth.

Paradise Earth hesitated for a bit before nodding.

Heaven path killer move — Heavenly Web Protection Veil.

Milky white light web appeared once again, the heavenly web was pure without any dust. There were large gaps but they did not allow anything in.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's golden light rays were completely blocked by the heavenly web.

This was the void, there were no outside world's luck path dao marks to amplify Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. On the contrary, they were also under the threat of Limitless' countermeasures. It was not like in the Door of Life and Death where Spectral Soul Demon Venerable obtained amplification from countless soul path dao marks and could also use his full strength without any restraints.

Five restriction profound light qi!

Fang Yuan attacked from afar, five colored smoke spread rapidly.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not slow down, he kept on charging closer.

Golden light constantly flowed around his body, when Giant Sun Immortal Venerable entered the five restriction profound light qi, the five colored smoke flowed away from him.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable closed in on Fang Yuan and used a killer move.

A golden hand quickly flew out and grabbed at Fang Yuan's head.

The giant hand was about to pluck Fang Yuan's luck, but at the next moment, Cooking Luck Pot showed itself. It shook fiercely as it blocked the giant hand.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used another move, the golden hand was reinforced and strengthened greatly.

But as it tried to pluck with more force, Cooking Luck Pot's retaliation became even stronger, even directly flicking away the giant hand.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable already knew Fang Yuan had Cooking Luck Pot and that it was quite strong. But this attempt still shocked him: "How many rank eight Immortal Gu did he use to raise Cooking Luck Pot to this level?"

Even Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was feeling troubled right now.

With the protection of such a strong Cooking Luck Pot, most of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's luck path methods were useless against Fang Yuan.

Normally speaking, the reason Gu Immortals could hardly fight Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was because it was difficult for them to guard against Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's luck path methods. Once Giant Sun Immortal Venerable attacked their luck, they had few methods to block it, and there was furthermore a low chance of blocking it.

But Fang Yuan's situation was different.

Chapter 2204: Two Venerables Versus Fang Yuan (Double Chapter)

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's attacks were blocked. Fang Yuan took the chance to counterattack, but at this time, a ray of starlight landed on Fang Yuan's forehead with an incredible speed.

Fang Yuan's head leaned back slightly from the attack. Seeing his defensive methods weakened by thirty percent, he quickly moved away.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable flew over and coordinated with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to pincer attack Fang Yuan!

At this moment, Fang Yuan was facing the attacks of two venerables!

All the immortals were tongue-tied.

No matter how strong Fang Yuan was and how much reputation he had, was he worthy of being targeted by two venerables?

But thinking about it carefully, the immortals understood why.

After all, among all the pseudo venerables, Fang Yuan possessed the greatest threat! Besides Fang Yuan's main body, Qi Sea Ancestor and Zhan Bu Du were also Fang Yuan's clones. Thus, he also had the largest force here.

And the seemingly lone Demon Immortal Qi Jue had already made a secret deal with Fang Yuan back during the pursuit battle against him, they had cooperated for a long time.

With the sharp increase in pressure, Fang Yuan prioritized on evading. He defended against the two venerables' attacks while shouting to Paradise Earth and the other immortals: "We must join hands and unite. Otherwise, with the eternal life research results right in front of us, the two venerables will not let you gain benefits easily. They will definitely kill us first!"

Without much hesitation, Shen Shang, Paradise Earth, Demon Immortal Qi Jue, and others agreed, attacking one after the other.

It was just that their efforts could not lift the pressure off Fang Yuan.

In Star Constellation Chessboard Formation, the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals tied down the pseudo venerables even if they had to sacrifice their lives.

Fang Yuan was beginning to flee everywhere, falling into a passive state.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable suddenly mobilized Star Constellation Chessboard formation to slow down Fang Yuan's flying speed. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable took the chance to attack, a ray of golden light shot out from his hand.

Fang Yuan could not dodge in time and was illuminated by the golden light.

At the crucial moment, Fang Yuan had to activate his renowned defensive method.

A long robe appeared on him. This long robe had wide sleeves, it was white like snow. On the surface of the robe, there was slow flowing water, it was the same appearance as Reverse Flow River earlier.

Not just that, the surface of the long robe had faint mist surrounding it. There was also a strip of light that was deep azure, it was curvy and wavy, resembling a long sash, it coiled around Fang Yuan's arms, the back of his neck, and around his waist again.

Immortal killer move — Reverse Flow Protection Seal!

Reverse flow protection seal was outstanding, it immediately reflected Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's golden light and the flying stars that followed closely behind.

Fang Yuan finally gained a slight respite, but he did not dare to relax.

His hands opened wide.

His left hand released five colored smoke, it was five restriction profound light qi!

His right hand pressed down towards the starry paths, activating a sinister and baleful compound killer move, rotting poisonous dark ash!

This move contained the profundity of wood path, poison path, dark path, and fire path. It could corrode everything and destroy their internal structure. As time passes, its damage would become even fiercer. Even when this killer move was canceled, there would still be continuous corrosion, but the corrosion would become weaker.

Fang Yuan had once tried this move on an immemorial year beast.

He had stopped this killer move in just a few breaths of time.

But the struck immemorial year beast cried miserably for three days and three nights before it finally turned into a pile of rotten grey ash. Fang Yuan blew it away with just a light breath.

Fang Yuan was not using this move to target Star Constellation Immortal Venerable or Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

He was targeting this Star Constellation Chessboard Formation!

He must first destroy this formation!

Heaven path killer move — Heavenly Summary Earthly Norm!

On the other side, Paradise Earth activated his killer move again. He had the same intention as Fang Yuan; great minds thought alike, he wanted to first dismantle this formation as well.

The heaven path killer move's power was beyond ordinary, everywhere it went, starry paths vanished and starlight dissipated, restoring it to the original void.

"Paradise Earth..." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable frowned as she threw out numerous stars. Most of them still targeted Fang Yuan, but a small portion attacked Paradise Earth.

Even though Paradise Earth only had pseudo venerable cultivation, he had converted to heaven path. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was unable to ascertain his methods for the moment, so she had to be on alert against him.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable controlled the whole situation and was always calm. As long as there was something odd, she would suppress it immediately.

With Star Constellation Immortal Venerable targeting him, Paradise Earth also had to be on guard.

"This reverse flow protection seal is indeed difficult to deal with, but Fang Yuan, how long can you hold on for?" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used powerful killer moves one after the other.

These killer moves were all reflected back, but Reverse Flow River's water level also fell sharply.

Fang Yuan's reverse flow protection seal was renowned all over the world, it was not that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had not prepared for it. It was just that he had not personally dealt with Fang Yuan's reverse flow protection seal, and after Fang Yuan modified it later, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could only choose the method of consuming it.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable frowned slightly.

With a shift of her mind, starry paths shook, a grand rank eight Immortal Gu House followed the starry paths and entered the battlefield.

It was Divine Emperor City!

Inside Divine Emperor City, Genesis Lotus' will was solemn as he activated a method that he had prepared for a long while.

Painting path killer move — Scenic Portrait!

Instantly, Fang Yuan's portrait appeared inside Divine Emperor City's painting world.

Fang Yuan's portrait stood in front of Genesis Lotus' will, he was motionless with his eyes closed, he had no expressions.

After Genesis Lotus' will used this killer move, his form began to turn unstable.

He clenched his teeth as he activated another painting path killer move called ink slicing thread.

Thin lines of ink suddenly flew out of the hands of Genesis Lotus' will, they started slicing the cheeks of Fang Yuan's portrait.

Almost at the same time, Fang Yuan, who was fighting Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, suddenly shook.

His left cheek was cut, the injury was a thin line from which black ink flowed out from.

"What's going on?!" Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk, and almost immediately, his sharp gaze fell on Divine Emperor City.

"This is a painting path method, it is definitely Divine Emperor City's doing and very likely involves Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable!" Fang Yuan's thoughts moved like lightning.

He was right.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable planned before taking action. Since she could prepare the killer move luck gamble against Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, she would not neglect Fang Yuan.

Although Fang Yuan had not used reverse flow protection seal for a long time, it did not mean he had no way of using it.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's plan would never forget Fang Yuan's reverse flow protection seal!

The killer move scenic portrait was already created by Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable. Later, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable worked together with Genesis Lotus' will to modify it, to target Fang Yuan's reverse flow protection seal.

Fang Yuan had just stabilized his footing with the help of reverse flow protection seal when Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used this method.

Reverse Flow River could essentially reflect everything, however, reverse flow protection seal was created by Fang Yuan. Fang Yuan had almost no understanding of painting path, his attainment level in it was blank.

Fang Yuan was aware of this flaw, so he had already gathered some painting path mortal Gu. However, it was far out of its depth against a painting path method at this level.

As such, Fang Yuan was hit by the killer move scenic portrait.

This was also the reason why most venerables cultivated two paths.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable cultivated wisdom path and star path, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable cultivated wood path and painting path, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable cultivated luck path and blood path, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable cultivated earth path and heaven path, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable cultivated transformation path and strength path, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable cultivated theft path and space path...

Venerables often cultivated one main path and one specialty path.

The first path would be the primary one which could be widely spread. The other path would be kept secretive and mysterious, information about it would be sealed tight.

For instance, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable cultivated wisdom path as the primary, with star path as her specialty. Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable cultivated wood path as the primary, with painting path as his specialty.

Fang Yuan's current situation showed the advantage of doing this.

Fang Yuan could reflect wood path methods, but he was a stranger to painting path, so painting path methods were effective on him.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's situation was slightly special, he had planned to take blood path as the primary, and luck path as his specialty.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable created luck path when he was alive, he was the only one to possess luck path. Thus, he kept luck path a secret, but to help Fang Yuan and his ambitions, he left a portion of the luck path true inheritance in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and with Lang Ya land spirit.

After he died, he tried all ways to use his clone to create blood path. He had planned to make blood path the most common path, thus the Blood Sea clone spread blood path everywhere. He wanted to get the help of others to help him perfect and promote blood path.

Inside Divine Emperor City, Genesis Lotus' will used another painting path killer move, brush stroke.

A painting brush swept past Fang Yuan's portrait, leaving ink traces wherever it brushed.

At the same time, ink-black injuries appeared on Fang Yuan's body. The injuries deepened quickly.

Compound killer move — Man as Before!

Fang Yuan activated a killer move again to heal himself constantly.

But with this, he had no choice but to cancel the rotting poisonous dark ash killer move, which only left five restriction profound light qi for his counterattack.

Simultaneously activating multiple killer moves did not surpass Fang Yuan's wisdom path limits. But Fang Yuan had to leave some capacity for thinking to deal with any sudden event.

Otherwise, once an unexpected situation occurred, and Fang Yuan's reaction was slightly late, it would give the enemy an opportunity.

After all, his enemies were venerables, they were not the likes of Qin Ding Ling and Bing Sai Chuan.

Moreover, these two venerables had allied!

Pressure, immense pressure that was like a mountain pressed down endlessly on Fang Yuan, it would not stop until it killed him.

Fang Yuan was in a disadvantage all along, his situation continued to be more troublesome.

This was the hardest battle of his life!

Comparatively, the battle in the fate war was not so heated.

"Fang Yuan is in danger!" Paradise Earth and the others wanted to help, but were always blocked by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

The two venerables' attacks were concentrated on Fang Yuan, they only used the remaining small portion of energy to block the other pseudo venerables.

Finally, Fang Yuan's Reverse Flow River was expended, he had no choice but to cancel this move.

Without the obstruction of this move, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable laughed as he activated an already prepared killer move.

The killer move was formless, Fang Yuan was instantly hit.

Sovereign immortal aperture shook violently, lightning flashed as tribulation clouds gathered.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled: "Fang Yuan, the core of this move is Calamity Luck Altar, it can change fortune to misfortune. Your sovereign immortal aperture has too many resources, and it has developed extremely well. How large of a tribulation will form once such a deep fortune turns into calamity?"

Fang Yuan's expression changed.

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Mini Northern Plains.

Sacred Eagle City.

Tribulation clouds billowed. At the previous moment, it was still a scene of blue skies and white clouds, now the world had turned dark.

"What's going on?" The residents of the city looked at the sky.

Shortly afterwards, noisy sounds rose from Sacred Eagle City.

"Tribulation clouds, there are tribulation clouds again!"

"What is happening?"

"Quick, go ask the City Lord for help."

The city residents were terrified and panicked as they ran towards the City Lord Manor.

Sacred Eagle City's residents were mostly humans who came from the former Beast Calamity grotto-heaven.

In this life, Fang Yuan had secretly accelerated Beast Calamity grotto-heaven's calamities and tribulations to subdue it. This caused tribulation clouds to cover the whole of Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, creating a huge number of casualties.

These residents had such a painful experience, so when they saw the tribulation clouds that was almost the same as in their memory, they immediately acted like spooked cats, screaming and fleeing madly.

Inside the City Lord Manor, a transformation path rank seven Gu Immortal looked at the sky, a bitter expression was on his face too.

He was the recently promoted Sacred Eagle City Lord. He was originally only at rank six, but he received Fang Yuan's help, and his cultivation advanced to rank seven. After accepting a mission, he became this Sacred Eagle City's City Lord.

"This tribulation is so huge, Sacred Eagle City only has three Gu Immortals. We might not be able to stop it, it is better to ask for reinforcements from Triple Sacred Mountain!" Sacred Eagle City Lord immediately sent a request for reinforcements.

Triple Sacred Mountain was the center of Mini Northern Plains, it was the gathering area of snowmen, and was the most developed area. It was looked after by Fang Yuan's fiancée, Xue Er.

Different from the five regions, humans lived peacefully with other variant humans the inside sovereign immortal aperture, helping each other without any discrimination.

Sacred Eagle City's residents were very isolated and ignorant. When they first moved into the sovereign immortal aperture, they were helped extensively by Xue Er and the snowmen, so they had good feelings towards the snowmen.

As for Sacred Eagle City's Gu Immortals who came from Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, these Gu Immortals were also vastly different from the five regions' Gu Immortals in regards to their philosophy of life. They took the duty of protecting mortals as their glory.

Adding on Fang Yuan's rule and management, all the races in sovereign immortal aperture lived unitedly.

The human Sacred Eagle City Lord did not have any mental barrier in asking for reinforcements from the snowmen. At the same time, he had a lot of faith in Fairy Xue Er's help.

Mini Western Desert.

An enormous pitch-black city was standing in the depths of the desert.

It was Inkman City.

Inkman City Lord Mo Tan Sang's cultivation had also advanced to rank seven. He had around eight Gu Immortals under him, but they were just rank six.

"The scale of this tribulation is so huge, its power will definitely be unprecedented." Mo Tan Sang's expression was solemn, he felt heavy pressure.

He reacted almost immediately and sent out commands.

Two Gu Immortals were dispatched to maintain the security and prevent the residents from taking vicious actions, like rioting or stampeding.

Additionally, four Gu Immortals were dispatched out of the city to look after white steel bowl valley, rotten swamp, hibiscus trees, and other resource points. If the situation became urgent, these Gu Immortals could immediately retrieve as many of these resources as possible and temporarily place them in Inkman City's storage.

Mo Tan Sang's status was similar to Xue Er's. He was almost like the person in charge of Mini Western Desert, he governed not only Inkman City, but also many other locations.

Mini Blue Heaven.

A grand city was on a continent above cloud soil.

In the heart of the city was a mountain-like hall made from a star snail.

This hall was in uproar at this moment.

A rank eight elderly man was sitting inside solemnly as he listened to the reports from various Gu Immortals.

He was the old Combat Beast King, he was appointed as Star Collection City Lord by Fang Yuan and was in charge of overseeing the internal affairs of the sovereign immortal aperture.

"This tribulation is too sudden!"

"It is even more terrifying than the one in Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, it is much larger and covers the whole sovereign immortal aperture!!"

"City Lord, what should we do?"

"Master has taken away almost all the rank eight Gu Immortals and the strong rank sevens for the fight at this time. Although most of them have revived, they are at Gu Master level. Our manpower is too few, how do we deal with such a tribulation?!"

"Even if there were no casualties, could we deal with such a tribulation by combining our strength? That is impossible! Only an existence like master can protect our home from such a tribulation..."

Combat Beast King raised his hand, the hall gradually quietened: "Master is wise and mighty, he will definitely make a move when he should. But right now, we should remember our responsibility — to protect our home! Even if we die, it cannot crumble our will. Everyone, this is a difficult test, master is watching us, our clansmen are watching us. As Gu Immortals, if we cannot protect them, if we are afraid of dying, how can we raise our heads in pride later on?"

"We are willing to fight with all our strength!" The Gu Immortals shouted together with surging morale.

Death was not terrifying.

Even if they died, they could revive through Human Sea.

The terrifying thing was escaping in the face of danger and leaving a bad impression on Fang Yuan.

There was no doubt that Fang Yuan's will was paramount in the sovereign immortal aperture, he ruled everything.

In Crazed Demon Cave.

Dazzling and vast golden light flowed like a sea wave.

Fang Yuan retreated rapidly with a solemn expression.

He no longer had reverse flow protection seal. Facing the two venerables, his situation was perilous, almost like walking on a steel rope between cliffs.

What was even worse was the trouble in the sovereign immortal aperture.

"This is a method of all living beings luck..." Fang Yuan looked at Giant Sun Immortal Venerable with a malevolent killing intent.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's gaze was eerie, he observed the tribulation aura on Fang Yuan's body becoming denser before he put his mind at rest.

Fang Yuan possessed Cooking Luck Pot which could indeed stop most of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's luck path methods, however, Fang Yuan still could not compare to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable in terms of luck path foundation.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable sighed lightly: "Fang Yuan, you have such talent and aptitude, I really don't want to kill you. It is such a pity that your character determined your outcome. I have to get rid of you. If you are really allowed to keep on developing, there will be a day when you comprehend all living beings luck and heaven and earth luck through the self luck true inheritance. It is much easier to get rid of you now."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable appreciated Fang Yuan's talent, but was even more wary of him!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable continued to attack while speaking.

Fang Yuan was forced to retreat again and again.

Although he had cooperated with Fang Yuan time and again, when they truly fought, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable seemed to be even happier than Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to get rid of Fang Yuan!

Fang Yuan's expression was solemn, his eyes shone sharply as he kept silent.

He continuously activated all kinds of compound killer moves, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had never heard of or seen these killer moves before.

Because of this, it was rather troublesome for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to deal with them.

Fang Yuan relied on this to barely maintain his footing.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled: "I am getting more and more amazed by you, such brilliant and numerous compound killer moves have really broadened my horizons. A pity, it is a pity that these killer moves are unsystematic, you still don't have your own combat system!"

"But this is not your fault."

"I used close to one thousand years to perfect my current combat system back then."

"Moreover, making a combat system is not just about time, it also needs plenty of worthy opponents to be created successfully."

"Fang Yuan, how many years have you lived even after adding up all your lives?"

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled, while speaking, he inflicted another deep injury on Fang Yuan's chest.

Fang Yuan did not speak.

Comparing foundation, he was indeed inferior to venerables.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had a smile on his face as he saw Fang Yuan's tribulation aura increasing by double in just a short while: "You already felt it, right? The greatest profundity of my move lies in the number of calamities and tribulations. As many resource points, Immortal Gu, Gu Immortals, desolate beasts, and so on as are there in the sovereign immortal aperture, there will be an equivalent number of calamities and tribulations."

"Those who are struck by this move need to resolve countless calamities and tribulations at the same time. Difficult, this is extremely difficult. Fang Yuan, I won't give you an opportunity to save yourself."

Saying so, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable attacked once again.

His attacks were unceasing and majestic, Fang Yuan could only block them, and was unable to do anything to the sovereign immortal aperture.

It was a scene of an abyss in the sovereign immortal aperture.

Mini Central Continent.

Flower mist extreme marsh.

Large meteorites dragged long tails as they smashed on the ground.

Bam bam bam...

The meteorites erupted and flames spread, burning the mist, marsh, and extreme marsh flowers around them. Only dry land was left behind.

From the inferno, tall flame monsters stood up.

As the flame monsters wreaked havoc, a Gu Immortal streaked across the sky.

It was Fang Yuan's dragonman clone — Wu Shuai.

With a thought from Wu Shuai, ant groups flew out and fought with the flame monsters.

Mini Southern Border.

There was a downpour on the whole dark inkstone mine.

The corrosive rain inflicted heavy damage on the dark inkstones.

A rockman Gu Immortal was stationed here, he used all his strength to activate his killer moves but could only protect a small part of the mine.

Star Collection City was in chaos.

"Every resource point in the mini five regions and mini nine heavens is being attacked by different types and scales of calamities and tribulations."

"The Gu Immortals on Fire Bird Mountain are requesting for reinforcements!"

"Ghost fire is burning pin tree snowfield, if we don't stop it on time, the ghost fire will destroy the whole snowfield."

"The Hairy Man continent is being bombarded by lightning, one of the cities is already drowned by a tsunami!"

"A terrifying beast calamity has appeared in Mini Black Heaven, thousands of green claw ghost winged lions are hunting down soul beasts!"

Bad news came one after the other.

Combat Beast King subconsciously clenched his fists. Despite already being prepared mentally, when the calamities and tribulations really broke out, the severity of the losses made him unable to maintain his calm for some time.

But from start to finish, he maintained his solemn expression.

At this time, when all the Gu Immortals were panicking, as their backbone, he could not panic!

He sent out various commands, Star Collection City began to operate frantically. Manpower and resources were dispatched to every place as they began to deal with the calamities and tribulations.

But there were too many calamities and tribulations, not only was their range huge, they were of various types. Every calamity and tribulation needed to be dealt with using different methods.

This was an extremely difficult challenge to the Gu Immortals stationed in the sovereign immortal aperture.

Chapter 2205: Black Fire

News of the first Gu Immortal to be heavily injured and near death arrived.

Combat Beast King's heart immediately tensed: "So quickly?"

His mood became even heavier.

The more casualties the Gu Immortals suffered, the lower the resistance the sovereign immortal aperture could put up. If this continued until a certain extent, the situation would be irredeemable, like an unstoppable avalanche.

Combat Beast King gritted his teeth: "Send the orders, Mini Black Heaven does not need to be saved, give up on rescuing any desolate beasts, ancient desolate beasts, and even immemorial desolate beasts! We will protect the large cities first, second are the important resource points. How are the results of the wisdom path Gu Immortals' deductions?"

Star Collection City naturally had wisdom path Gu Immortals.

"We have not even deduced half of them, there are too many calamities and tribulations." A wisdom path Gu Immortal said with sweat all over his head.

"Take out whatever results you have to deal with this situation first!" Combat Beast King almost stamped his foot.

The results were soon obtained, Combat Beast King made the decision on the spot, Star Collection City began to mobilize Gu Immortals.

"Oh?" Wu Shuai was the first to receive this command.

A strange expression flashed by his face before he slowly retreated.

In the short while of his fight with the flame monsters, flower mist extreme marsh was already completely destroyed, while the majority of the flame monsters still remained.

There were too many of them, even though Wu Shuai used all his strength, he could only eradicate a small portion of them.

These flame monsters' target was already destroyed, so their hostility gathered on Wu Shuai.

Seeing Wu Shuai retreat, the flame monsters immediately chased after him.

Wu Shuai led them to the west and met another Gu Immortal midway. A group of qi monsters were chasing after this Gu Immortal.

The two Gu Immortals were in the center, but the flame monsters and qi monsters fought with each other.

"It is feasible indeed!"

"These calamities and tribulations are not formed naturally, but were created because of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's killer move."

"Since they are only formed through luck path and is not controlled by heaven's will, they are like an army without a leader. We can use calamities and tribulations to deal with calamities and tribulations."

Wu Shuai was slightly happy.

This was the deduction result of the wisdom path Gu Immortals.

Some Gu Immortals gathered acidic rain, while some Gu Immortals directed the heavenly river towards the desert...

Under such operations, the sovereign immortal aperture's situation finally eased.

"We have stabilized the situation!" Combat Beast King let out a breath of air. In just a short period of time, his face was covered with sweat.

Calamities and tribulations came too fiercely, if their reaction had been slightly slow, it might have resulted in destruction. Fortunately, they used every moment, seized the initiative, and stabilized the situation.

But this was far from enough.

Calamities and tribulations were still playing out in many places, those that could consume each other were only a small portion.

The whole sovereign immortal aperture was still being destroyed by calamities and tribulations, losses increased at every breath of time.

"The tribulation clouds above the flower mist extreme marsh have disappeared completely."

"Most of the tribulation clouds above the pin tree snowfield have dissipated!"

"The dark inkstone mine is completely destroyed, but the tribulation clouds are also destroyed!"

"Something is wrong!!! There is an abnormal situation."

"Reporting! Over twenty tribulation clouds all over the mini five regions are showing identical changes."

"This is the... earth shaking heavenly light tribulation!"

Combat Beast King had just relaxed, when he heard the devastating news.

"This is bad!" His expression turned pale. From combining the information, in the map of the mini five regions in his mind, earth shaking heavenly light tribulations were appearing in crucial areas.

Bam bam bam...

Yellowish brown pillars of light shot out from tribulation clouds, the light pillars struck the ground and continued to pierce down into the ground.

A large amount of tribulation clouds swarmed into the yellowish brown light pillars. They suddenly lit up, and this light flowed down the light pillars into the depths of the ground.

Boom—!

Explosions rang, the earth shook fiercely.

Boom—!

Boom—!

Boom—!

Earth shaking light pillars in the mini five regions were continuing to exert power, earthquakes were becoming even more intense.

Terrifying shockwaves continued to expand. Everywhere they passed by, earth shook, mountains crumbled, rivers changed courses, and seas roared.

"This luck path method targets the resources in the immortal aperture. Now that those resource points are destroyed or damaged heavily, earth veins became the conspicuous target!"

"That's why there are so many earth shaking heavenly light tribulations, they just happen to cover all the earth vein nodes and are seeking to destroy them."

Wu Shuai's face was cold as ice.

Although these calamities and tribulations triggered by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not have heaven's will to control the overall situation, there would be this kind of change at the later part. It greatly made up for the lack of commands.

"However, you think the earth veins we constructed painstakingly can be destroyed so easily?"

Wu Shuai sneered, activating a formation.

Earth vein formation was activated, thick and grand aura spread rapidly. The powerful tremors underground were forcefully suppressed.

Next, the Gu Immortals dispatched by Star Collection City reached the tribulation areas, and began attacking earth shaking heavenly light pillars.

The huge heavenly light pillars began to break down one after the other. The sovereign immortal aperture's Gu Immortals coordinated to get past this difficulty.

The tribulation clouds changed again. This time, they formed beast calamities in various areas. Immemorial desolate beast level golden steel earth rats emerged from everywhere and besieged the earth vein nodes.

Seven to eight earth vein nodes were destroyed before these golden steel earth rats were eradicated. A small portion of the earth rats were enslaved by Wu Shuai.

Tribulation clouds changed again, but they were still targeting earth veins.

The immortals defended the earth veins strongly using all their strength, they cooperated tightly.

Although earth vein nodes continued to decrease in number, the situation was turning for the better.

The calamities and tribulations were of all kinds, but their targets were still earth veins. This was a controllable factor, which brought a lot of convenience to the immortals.

Over ten or so calamities and tribulations targeted earth veins, but after they were repelled by the immortals, the tribulation clouds that covered the whole sovereign immortal aperture had mostly disappeared.

However, when the immortals thought the tribulations had finally passed, an aura that made the hearts of all living beings in the sovereign immortal aperture shake appeared all of a sudden!

At first, this aura was extremely small.

But soon, the aura grew rapidly in the deepest part of the tribulation clouds.

Amidst the immortals' puzzled and terrified gazes, a fire burned in the depths of the tribulation clouds.

The fire was black!

The black fire had just appeared, when it burned all the remaining stubborn tribulation clouds.

The black fire grew rapidly, and started falling down. Wherever it passed by, be it ground or the air, they were all burned into nothingness.

The immortals breathed in sharply, the power of the black fire was horrifying, it was like the nemesis of all existences!

"Isn't this black fire like the one in the dragon whale grotto-heaven? It actually appeared here! Giant Sun Immortal Venerable is truly formidable!" Wu Shuai's heart jumped. Even an expert like him felt extreme threat from the black fire.

There was nothing else to say, the immortals used their methods to defend against the black fire.

However, all the methods were of no use.

Even when Fairy Miao Yin and Lady White Rabbit used all their strength, they could only extinguish a little of the black fire.

Moreover, once the black fire was destroyed to a certain extent, it would change form, transforming into black water, black lightning, and so on, killing many Gu Immortals who were caught off guard.

At the crucial moment, He Chun Qiu took action.

"Don't panic! The main body also expected this scene, and taught me a countermeasure." He Chun Qiu said as he activated a human path formation.

The human path formation had the thousand wish tree, and also the secluded domain of heaven and earth, Human Sea.

Bam bam bam...

Lumps of white light flew out from the formation.

These lumps of light were extremely large, they flew everywhere in the mini five regions. As long as the black fire spread, the white light would pounce on it.

The black fire was quickly dissipating, it changed its form again. But no matter what form it took, it was still continuing to be extinguished by the white light.

The white light's effect was excellent, but the black fire continued to gather and grow.

"It will be really dangerous if this continues!"

"Human path killer moves are effective, but they cannot compare to the black fire's growth."

"What should we do?"

The immortals panicked.

"Oh no, black fire has appeared on Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley!"

"The earth vein formation is also being burned!"

The situation worsened rapidly, He Chun Qiu, Wu Shuai, and the rest were pale.

The situation was out of control!

The human path formation left behind by Fang Yuan was also implicated.

What to do?

These Gu Immortals had already tried their best, but they could do nothing.

They could only depend on Fang Yuan's main body!

Fang Yuan's main body was continuing to dodge, his whole body was bathed in blood, his hair were disheveled, and his arm was broken. He was in a miserable state.

He simply could not counterattack and gain any initiative against the two venerables. Five restriction profound light qi was forced to stop, one phrase could be used to describe the current Fang Yuan — hanging onto his last breath.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's methods were truly terrifying and dealt with Fang Yuan's methods by destroying their foundation.

The Gu Immortals left behind to guard the sovereign immortal aperture could do nothing more, their only hope lay with Fang Yuan.

But Fang Yuan did not have such an opportunity.

The two venerables attacked like a storm, arriving one after another, not giving him the chance to catch a breather.

"I must resolve the black fire!" Fang Yuan clenched his teeth. If he ignored the black fire, his sovereign immortal aperture would be as good as destroyed.

Immortal killer move — Hu Elevation!

Suddenly, a qi path killer move descended, temporarily blocking a venerable.

Qi Sea clone had made his move, he was finally freed from the shackles.

"Here I come!" Zhan Bu Du roared. He was freed from the responsibility of protecting Qi Sea, he rampaged and fought his way to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Fang Yuan's main body took the chance to retreat.

Immortal killer move — Humanly Flame Smoke!

He activated his method to save the human path formation first. Then, he coordinated with the human path formation to deal with the black fire that was scattered everywhere.

Burning white flames shrouded the black fire, and started tearing it apart.

The main body's abilities were indeed extraordinary, the black fire's growth was immediately impeded.

However, Zhan Bu Du and Qi Sea Ancestor were being beaten back.

"Paradise Earth!" Fang Yuan retreated towards Paradise Earth.

Paradise Earth took a deep breath, as he activated heavenly web protection veil once again.

With his help, Fang Yuan obtained a brief respite. When the two venerables broke the heavenly web, Zhan Bu Du and Qi Sea Ancestor arrived to reinforce him.

The battle had lasted until now, but the two venerables were unable to take Fang Yuan's life. Both frowned.

Crazed Demon formation was shrinking rapidly, the limit on the venerables was being released.

Their attacks became increasingly terrifying, Fang Yuan could only flee miserably.

Immortal Gu House — Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress!

Fang Yuan hid inside the Immortal Gu House and activated a killer move. This move used ability Gu as the core, it had the effect of absorbing the black fire!

The deadlock inside the sovereign immortal aperture finally began turning for the better.

Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress protected Fang Yuan for a while before it was broken by the combined strength of the two venerables.

"Die!" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable suddenly used a vicious killer move.

"Protect me!" Fang Yuan cried out in alarm, he was unable to dodge in time.

At the crucial moment, Zhan Bu Du flew over and used his body to block the killer move.

Boom!

A huge explosion rang, Zhan Bu Du was torn into pieces, dying immediately.

Chapter 2206: Fighting Over Eternal Life

Fang Yuan's eyelids twitched.

The other pseudo venerables' hearts sank heavily.

On the contrary, the morale of Heavenly Court's immortals surged.

Fang Yuan lost Zhan Bu Du, one of his main clones. Zhan Bu Du's immortal aperture was also quickly absorbed by the Crazed Demon formation.

But fortunately, under the control of Zhan Bu Du's will, his various Immortal Gu were sent in time to treasure yellow heaven.

However, black fire was still wreaking havoc in the sovereign immortal aperture!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable attacked once again.

Fang Yuan clenched his teeth as he ordered the Qi Sea clone to block the calamity.

Qi Sea clone did not have tough body like Zhan Bu Du, his death was certain against Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's attack. But Fang Yuan could only choose to sacrifice this clone to protect himself.

However, at the next moment, starry paths shook and twisted, forming an azure sphere that trapped Qi Sea Ancestor.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was caught unprepared, his killer move bombarded the starry path sphere and destroyed it instantly.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable turned around to look at Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, the latter heaved a sigh.

Lu Wei Yin and the rest's spirits shook. This was the first lapse in the cooperation of the two venerables!

This was really fortunate!

Qi Sea clone managed to escape death, he continued to protect Fang Yuan by his side.

The situation in the sovereign immortal aperture had only turned slightly better. As long as Fang Yuan let go of his control by even a slight bit, the situation would erupt again, and the whole immortal aperture would face destruction.

A huge sound rang as the void shook.

Crazed Demon Cave's eighth layer disappeared completely, the final merged great world turned into nothingness, and countless living beings became sacrificial offerings.

The Door of Life and Death with the immortal graveyard flew away, they were stored by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable in her immortal aperture.

Crazed Demon Cave had a total of nine layers. The first seven layers were swept clean by Fang Yuan, the eighth layer was completely gone, only the final ninth layer remained.

And in the Crazed Demon formation in the center of the ninth layer, only the final truthful floating ice piece remained.

The three Crazed Demon Eccentrics were on the floating ice, they were activating practice Gu together, like they were carving the final part.

Seeing this scene, the immortals felt their mind shake, while Fang Yuan silently let out a sigh of relief.

The danger had passed!

He had finally passed the most difficult time.

Indeed, like Fang Yuan expected, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not attack him anymore. Both stopped on their spots, looking at each other.

The atmosphere changed subtly.

The two venerables had allied to get rid of the pseudo venerables. But Fang Yuan used every method he could to hold onto his last breath.

The venerables' plan had failed.

Right now, the eternal life research results were already close to completion. The most important thing now was to seize these results!

Whoever tangled with those pseudo venerables would be giving the other venerable a chance.

"Success, we succeeded!" The three eccentrics slumped on the ground, shouting hoarsely and excitedly.

Immortal killer move — Luck Gamble!

The two venerables' stalemate lasted for a while, when Qin Ding Ling came out of the starry paths.

She used the killer move once again, targeting Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Almost at the same time, Golden Hooped Great Immortal appeared again, using his golden hoop to trap Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Compared to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable clearly held the upper hand.

As long as Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was struck by these methods, his combat system's foundation would be hit, and he would fall into a disadvantage. Even if he were to not be hit, he would have to slow down for a while to deal with Qin Ding Ling and Golden Hooped Great Immortal.

With just those few minutes of advantage, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable might be able to last until the end and seize the eternal life research results.

However, right at this time, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled: "Star Constellation, you have good methods, but you seem to have forgotten something?"

At the next moment, a rank eight Immortal Gu House suddenly shone brightly. Most of the void in the ninth layer was filled with this light.

It was Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace!

This Immortal Gu House was already placed in the Crazed Demon formation by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had used this to break out of the trap, Fang Yuan and others had also escaped alongside him.

From that moment onwards, this Immortal Gu House had been comprehending the Crazed Demon formation's workings until it was shaken off.

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace was not a piece of truthful floating ice after all. After it was thrown out, it hid deeply, and even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable seemed to have failed to sense it.

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace was not simple, it had comprehended Crazed Demon formation's workings and was compatible with this world.

Right now, it was activated by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. It immediately affected the Crazed Demon formation and caused unrest in Limitless' chains.

The Star Constellation Chessboard Formation that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable arranged had forcefully merged with Limitless' chains and also restrained the various pseudo venerables, including Fang Yuan. It was already at its limits.

Right now, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable suddenly made his move, allowing the chains of Limitless to break free from the starry paths, thus causing the whole Star Constellation Chessboard Formation to collapse.

Guh.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable coughed out blood, she had suffered a terrifying backlash.

Using this chance, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable rushed forward, rapidly closing the distance between him and the Crazed Demon formation.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not have time to heal her injuries, she took out that mysterious secluded domain of heaven and earth once again.

This secluded domain was like a lantern and also like a bird cage.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable aimed the lantern-like secluded domain of heaven and earth at Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's back and shook it lightly.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was immediately disturbed by immense emotions, his speed fell sharply.

Starlight specks shot out around Star Constellation Immortal Venerable as she gave chase.

Bam bam bam...

The two venerables fought, storms blew from the aftershock, the world shook intensely.

Fortunately, this was the void, otherwise, nothing would be left!

The two venerables held each other back, reaching that final mountain-like large truthful floating ice at almost the same time.

The two venerables suddenly stopped, their expressions were strange.

Pang Shan of the three eccentrics woke up at this time. He was extremely fat before, but was now skinny, as if all his essence had been drained.

"What happened?"

"Why are there still no eternal life results?!"

"We were just a little short!"

"But we don't have any strength left..."

Pang Shan's gaze was dim, he was not in the right condition. He seemed to have become crazy, murmuring to himself.

His voice awakened the other two immortals.

Secret Schemer's expression was unsightly. He was slumped on the ground, and was barely able to cup his fists towards the two venerables: "Venerables, the eternal life research results are just lacking a step, no, half a step. As long as either of you activate practice Gu for a little while, this truthful floating ice will be carved successfully!"

The two venerables were silent.

This final truthful floating ice was not a small matter!

Whoever went in would not be able to come out for some time. If they wanted to come out, they needed to completely carve this truthful floating ice.

But was it that easy?

The eighth layer was destroyed, there were no more great worlds to provide fuel and clues to the Crazed Demon formation.

That was to say, they needed to contribute their own strength to carve this truthful floating ice.

The contribution amount was very crucial. If they needed to contribute too much, even if the venerable who entered the truthful floating ice held the lead, their battle strength would fall. Finally, they might play into the hands of the other venerable who was in a perfect state!

Be it Star Constellation Immortal Venerable or Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, they both had scruples. They stood silently for some time.

On the other side, the fight between the pseudo venerables and Heavenly Court Gu Immortals was still continuing.

"Duke Tong, don't you like stopping me?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue smiled fiercely as he pointed with his finger.

Boom boom boom!

Qi spheres burst, Duke Tong exploded into pieces with not even a bone remaining.

"Endless spears!" Che Wei shouted, countless spears shot out from around him like a dense forest.

Lu Wei Yin charged through the spear forest and grabbed.

A yellowish-brown giant hand flew out and grabbed Che Wei.

"Without Star Constellation Chessboard Formation, even if you have unparalleled talent, how can you block me?" Lu Wei Yin sighed. The yellowish-brown giant hand clenched, forcefully pressing Che Wei into meat paste.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were inferior to the pseudo venerables after all.

Previously, even inside Star Constellation Chessboard formation, these Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were hard pressed to block the pseudo venerables, they died constantly on the battlefield.

They relied on the immortal graveyard to revive and participate in the battle again, balancing their weak battle strength.

Now, without Star Constellation Chessboard formation and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to control the overall situation, these Heavenly Court Gu Immortals immediately got outmatched. They were slaughtered one after the other, unable to block the pseudo venerables.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted coldly when she saw this, immediately making a move to help.

How could Giant Sun Immortal Venerable let go of this chance, he immediately acted to block Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

The two venerables fought once again!

Both venerables had equal strength. Using the brief respite, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable opened his immortal aperture and let out Calamity Luck Altar.

At the same time, he transmitted his voice: "Bing Sai Chuan, go!"

Calamity Luck Altar quickly charged towards the truthful floating ice, Bing Sai Chuan received Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's command and flew into it.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted as she shook the lantern again.

Calamity Luck Altar's movement stopped immediately. Bing Sai Chuan, who was in charge of Calamity Luck Altar suddenly grasped his chest, he knelt down and started crying.

He blamed himself endlessly, sobbing: "It is all my fault, it is all my fault! I am wrong, I am to blame. If I was slightly stronger, I could have assisted master in defeating Heavenly Court and obtaining the eternal life research results. What is the point of my life? I have let down master. Sob sob sob... I should just die!"

Saying so, Bing Sai Chuan actually activated a killer move to kill himself!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable sighed, he endured Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's attacks while summoning Calamity Luck Altar to his side.

Golden light flowed and entered Bing Sai Chuan's body and mind.

With Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's help, Bing Sai Chuan broke free from the guilty emotions.

His head was covered in cold sweat, he felt lingering fear: "If not for master, I would have killed myself! This is Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's method? Master has been enduring such terrifying emotional torture all along?"

As he thought of this, fear rose in Bing Sai Chuan's heart.

His face was pale as he slumped on the ground, his body shivering intensely.

He opened his mouth and breathed heavily, but still felt suffocation.

His heart was filled with fear, he was scaring himself to death!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable took action and saved Bing Sai Chuan once again.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled. She got a hold of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's weakness, she also bullied him for not having an excellent method to revive his subordinates.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had to avoid colliding with her, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable opened her immortal aperture, letting out Qin Ding Ling and the other immortals.

These Gu Immortals were killed by Lu Wei Yin's group, but had revived shortly after in the immortal graveyard.

The moment these people exited Star Constellation's immortal aperture, they spread out and flew towards the truthful floating ice.

Chapter 2207: Limitless' Revival!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable coldly activated various methods and killed all these Heavenly Court members.

The two venerables held each other back, exchanging moves one after the other, not letting the other's subordinates enter the truthful floating ice.

The situation was at a deadlock once again. While the battle continued, a figure suddenly closed in on the truthful floating ice.

It was Shen Shang!

"Seeking death!" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable shouted, golden light shooting out of his eyes.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also attacked Shen Shang at the same time.

Shen Shang shouted and quickly retreated, Paradise Earth and Lu Wei Yin used all their strength to protect him.

The two venerables' attacks broke past layers of defense and reached Shen Shang.

Shen Shang cried out, fainting immediately from the attacks. His injuries were so terrifying that he was only lingering on a single breath.

After fighting for so long, the two venerables were filled with anger, and also knew the limits of the strength they could use now. Shen Shang's attempt triggered the two venerables's nerves, he was immediately attacked by both venerables!

Shen Shang's miserable state caused the pseudo venerables to feel their hearts shaking.

The two venerables used action to tell them that if they wanted to fish for profits right under their eyes, this would be their outcome!

The situation continued to be at a deadlock. The two venerables held each other back, their attention focused on each other, letting the pseudo venerables watch from the sidelines.

And it was an extravagant wish for the pseudo venerables to try to charge into the truthful floating ice. Once they showed any movements, they would be attacked by both venerables.

After Shen Shang's attempt, Paradise Earth, Qi Jue, and others tried to grab onto opportunities during the fight between the venerables, but it was all in vain.

Lu Wei Yin was heavily injured, while Paradise Earth was lightly injured and was panting heavily.

Soon, Shen Shang woke up, his injuries were severe and were difficult to heal in a short period of time.

When Demon Immortal Qi Jue noticed something wrong, he immediately retreated and gave up on the chance. Thus, his condition was quite good.

As for Fang Yuan, he did not make many moves. He just observed the fight while saving his aperture.

He had finally resolved the black fire!

But he paid an astronomical price.

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture, every large and small resource point was damaged. Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley were burned by black fire, they were in a ruined state.

Many Immortal Gu were also destroyed by the black fire, even more Gu Immortals died.

Sixty percent of the Gu Immortals were dead, including the old Combat Beast King.

Fang Yuan was almost back to his original state due to this tribulation, his foundation had fallen by seventy to eighty percent!

"Only twenty percent of my immortal essence is remaining." Fang Yuan inwardly calculated.

He had time path methods to accelerate the immortal essence production as well as the help of Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, but his expenditure was too huge.

Let alone the immortal essence expenditure when constructing resource points and refining Immortal Gu, just the repeated large battles caused the immortal essence reserves to fall sharply. Fang Yuan's calculations were of no use, he had no room to save them.

Using just twenty percent of his immortal essence to face the two venerables who were in their optimum states was extremely dangerous.

Boom boom boom!

The two venerables attacked, the power of their killer moves continued to increase, surpassing the previous limit.

The Crazed Demon formation was continuing to operate, Limitless's chains emerged out of thin air and shot towards the two venerables.

The two venerables blocked Limitless' chains, while attacking even more fiercely!

At first, the two venerables were rather restrained. But as the stalemate continued, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable broke the limit and triggered Limitless' chains.

He defended against the chains while attacking Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, quickly gaining the upper hand.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was forced to raise the power of her killer move as well to deal with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. Like this, she also provoked the attacks of Limitless' chains.

The situation was gradually going out of control. The two venerables fought and competed fiercely with each other, gradually using stronger killer moves.

At first, there were only hundreds of chains, but soon, the number increased by several times as they mixed into the venerables' fight.

The pseudo venerables had to retreat again and again, almost forced to the edge of the ninth layer.

"The two venerables are really going all out!"

"No, more accurately speaking, they have no way to hold back. Even though they are aware that this is not optimal, they cannot do anything about it. The vicious competition has already started."

"What should we do? We won't be able to hold on for long if this continues!"

"So this is a venerable's true strength. Us pseudo venerables don't even have the qualifications to observe the battle closely."

These pseudo venerables conversed.

Paradise Earth looked at Fang Yuan: "Fang Yuan, do you have a good plan?"

Fang Yuan's face was pale, his aura was extremely weak. He smiled bitterly and shook his head.

However, a change occurred right at this moment.

The two venerables' killer moves collided and exploded, but the leftover power of the moves hit the truthful floating ice.

The truthful floating ice was heavily damaged. Crack, crack, countless cracks appeared on the floating ice.

The three eccentrics were also heavily injured, Pang Shan even died immediately!

"Floating ice, the floating ice!" Secret Schemer coughed blood, but was still shouting in worry. His face was twisted, there was not even a slight bearing of a wisdom path Gu Immortal.

"What are you doing? You idiots. These are the eternal life research results, we just need a person to continue activating practice Gu. But you are actually destroying it!!" Not Immortal hit his chest and stamped his foot, scolding and pointing at the two venerables. He had fallen into a hysterical frenzy.

The pseudo venerables' expressions looked unsightly, but the two venerables did not listen.

The damage to the eternal life research results shook their hearts.

But they could not stop.

By now, the battle had come to such a state that whoever stopped would be suppressed by the other side, they would suffer a huge loss.

The two venerables had equal strength. Once one side suffered a huge loss, it would influence victory and defeat.

The victory and defeat here was not just about eternal life research results, but also the overall situation of the five regions. Be it Giant Sun Immortal Venerable or Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, the winner would influence Longevity Heaven's and Heavenly Court's prestige, even determining who the five regions would come under!

Naturally, retreating might be an option too.

But if one retreated, the other side would quickly interfere and obtain the eternal life research results, they could just send someone to complete the final step and obtain the eternal life research results!

Thus, they could not retreat.

Although some of the eternal life research results were destroyed, the main part was still there.

But if they continued to fight like this without anyone willing to retreat, if they were unable to determine victory or defeat, the eternal life research results might really be completely destroyed.

The two venerables were naturally aware of this.

But they could not step back.

Even if everything was destroyed in the end and no one obtained it, it was still better than letting the enemy obtain it!

"Fang Yuan." Under such a situation, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable suddenly shouted, "Heavenly Court is our common enemy, lend me a hand, I will split the eternal life research results with you, just like Primordial Domain."

The immortals were astonished.

Not long ago, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had been trying to kill Fang Yuan. But now, he actually took the initiative to request for an alliance.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was actually so shameless?

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable reacted immediately, shouting: "Fang Yuan, Heavenly Court always had the intention of recruiting you, we had tried to recruit you in the past. Now that fate Gu is destroyed, why can't our sides join hands?"

All the immortals were astonished once again.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable acted like this, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also did the same, did all venerables behave like this?

But soon, the immortals accepted this seemingly absurd fact.

A venerable's strength surpassed pseudo venerables, but Fang Yuan was different. Not long ago, the two venerables had joined hands to attack him, but he held onto his last breath!

Currently, the two venerables were in a stalemate. Fang Yuan had enough strength to participate, whichever side he joined, the other side would immediately fall into a disadvantageous position.

Just based on the current situation, a slight disadvantage might be enough to decide victory and defeat. Even if the venerables still had spare strength and safety nets, if they could recruit Fang Yuan to get rid of the other side's trump cards, there would be no loss.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Venerables, you both have good plans! It is not impossible to get my help. But can you pay the price?"

Fang Yuan had no fear!

His aura had fallen to rock-bottom, the tribulations had ruined his sovereign immortal aperture, but the situation was already different.

No venerable was foolish enough to find trouble with him, because it was not worth it.

Even if the two venerables joined hands again, Fang Yuan was not tied down by the black fire tribulation, he could hold on for some time. What's more, it was impossible for the two venerables to join hands anymore!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable fell out with Fang Yuan, but he took the initiative to make up for it. It was because Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was strong, and Fang Yuan was weak.

The similar reason applied to the relationship between Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Fang Yuan. Despite Fang Yuan's and Heavenly Court's deep enmity, with the eternal life research results right in front, they could work together indeed.

Why not?

Fang Yuan was never a person who was blinded by emotions.

But the falling out between the two venerables could not be easily patched. They were extremely wary of each other. They would only work together if an even stronger force appeared, in which they believed it was more advantageous to do so!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled: "Fang Yuan, I can give you all of my Primordial Domain!"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable bid right after: "I can also give all of my Primordial Domain to you, we can also transact my wisdom path true inheritance and Genesis Lotus' wood path true inheritance. Not only you, Fang Yuan, this invitation goes to Paradise Earth, Lu Wei Yin, Shen Shang, Qi Jue, and everyone as well, my Heavenly Court's bearing is known to all. I am willing to swear in the name of Star Constellation..."

Crack crack.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had yet to finish speaking when everyone heard a crisp sound.

Secret Schemer and Not Immortal stared at the truthful floating ice with wide eyes.

Cracks spread and filled the truthful floating ice.

"Did that attack from earlier completely destroy this truthful floating ice?!" Not Immortal shouted while holding his head.

The immortals stared at the truthful floating ice.

If the truthful floating ice broke down completely, what would they be fighting for?

Bam.

At the next moment, a soft sound rang. The truthful floating ice completely broke down, the crystal fragments flew everywhere before gradually dissipating.

Only a human shaped ice was left in the middle.

The form and outline of this human shaped ice were very vague at first. But in just a few breaths of time, it became lifelike. And in another few breaths of time, it was filled with flesh and blood.

Finally, under the immortals' stupefied gaze, the human shaped ice turned into a Gu Immortal.

"Forever been the Dao-Seeking Crazed Demon,"

"Looking up towards life, death, and the universe."

"Through a million years of planning and accumulation,"

"On this day, Limitless achieves true eternal life!"

This immortal recited and slowly opened his eyes. His expression was plain, but it shocked Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, and Paradise Earth.

"Limitless?" Paradise Earth could not believe it.

"Limitless!" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable frowned tightly.

"Limitless Demon Venerable, how could you revive? This is impossible!" Star Constellation Immortal Venerable cried out involuntarily.

Chapter 2208: True Eternal Life

The most shocked person was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

She had penetrated incredibly deeply into Crazed Demon Cave and Limitless' formation. Even after countless investigations, she did not notice that Limitless' revival method was in this Crazed Demon Cave.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had the same investigation results as her.

Precisely so, the two venerables fought so intensely earlier.

But the truth was in front of them, Limitless Demon Venerable had actually managed to revive.

"Don't tell me, when the final piece of truthful floating ice was successfully carved, Limitless Demon Venerable revived and attained eternal life in one step?" Fang Yuan was also shaken.

Fang Yuan could also sense acutely that the current Limitless Demon Venerable's aura far surpassed the other two venerables.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could feel this difference even more deeply.

Facing Limitless Demon Venerable, they seemed to be up against towering mountains and vast oceans.

"This is not in line with historical records, did Limitless Demon Venerable really surpass the venerables and attain eternal life?" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's eyes flickered with golden light.

"His current condition is extremely strange, his aura is so strong that even master cannot compare to him." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was shocked and suspicious.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable looked at each other and moved at the same time, attacking Limitless Demon Venerable with fierce methods.

Limitless Demon Venerable smiled lightly, chains flew around in a spiral, easily resolving the methods of the two venerables.

The two venerables were shocked internally but their fighting spirit soared, they launched even stronger killer moves in response.

Limitless Demon Venerable only defended instead of attacking, even after a few rounds of barraging, they did not manage to harm a hair of Limitless Demon Venerable.

Limitless let out a soft sound as he waved his hands, at once, space rippled, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable retreated immediately.

Paradise Earth and Fang Yuan did not dare to linger either, they quickly dodged.

At once, around a thousand steps of Limitless Demon Venerable, other than Not Immortal and Secret Schemer, there was nobody else.

Giant Sun had a grim expression.

Star Constellation had a deep gaze that flickered with starlight, she seemed to be making deductions with her full strength.

Limitless Demon Venerable smiled: "I do not wish to be enemies with all of you. The fruit of eternal life has been obtained after a million years, but I have not truly tested it yet."

"How do you want to test it?" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable asked.

"Watch." Limitless Demon Venerable turned around slightly.

All the immortals stared fixedly.

At the original spot that Limitless Demon Venerable was in, a tiny hole appeared.

Through this hole, the Gu Immortals could see a vast sea of — Chaos!

It seemed like black, yet it was not black. It seemed like white, yet it was not white.

If one said it was light, it would be light. If one said it was darkness, it would be darkness.

Almost no descriptive word in the world could accurately describe it.

Because chaos was just chaos after all.

Chaos was the greatest calamity!

"You lunatic, you actually broke the world boundary again, aren't you afraid that the entire world will be destroyed?" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable called out.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also added in with a solemn tone: "Limitless, I know about your aspiration. But if you intend to go ahead with this and destroy the five regions and two heavens, even if I have to sacrifice my life alongside Heavenly Court, we will exterminate you!"

"Both of you, calm down. The hole is not big, I merely want to test the result of this eternal life. Us venerables are invincible in the world, yet we are plagued by tribulations that originate from this chaos."

"Of the venerables here, who has not gotten injured from the chaos? Who has not suffered an ordeal because of it?"

"Crazed Demon Cave has been active for a million years, there is one most clear indicator if we want to know if the eternal life obtained is successful."

Saying this, Limitless Demon Venerable extended his arm into the hole.

The other venerables and the various Gu Immortals held their breaths subconsciously, staring at him fixedly.

Limitless Demon Venerable did not activate any killer move, he was using his own body to do this experiment.

He was simply too daring!

Even Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would never attempt this.

Even though they could last for some time in the chaos, that was the result of them using their full strength to defend their bodies.

If they acted like Limitless Demon Venerable, who did not put up any defense, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would be completely obliterated with just a slight touch of the chaos! Unless they managed to cut off the body part in time.

Limitless Demon Venerable placed his arm in simply like this, after a while, he pulled back his arm.

His arm was pitch-black, it seemed like charcoal created after a tree was completely burnt.

But when he clenched his arm, the 'black charcoal' on the surface instantly vanished into thin air, exposing a slightly smaller arm.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's mouth was wide open as he said dejectedly: "Is this... the true realm of eternal life?!"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sigh to herself: "I understand why I did not deduce it now. When you created Crazed Demon Cave, you had constantly been making use of the chaos outside the world. You lunatic!"

Back then, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable nearly destroyed the world, the reason was that he created a huge hole.

And at the deepest part of Limitless' formation, he broke the world boundary and created a tiny hole.

If there was a commotion in the Crazed Demon formation and this tiny hole became larger, it would be trouble. The entire Gu world might be destroyed as a result.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable called Limitless a lunatic, she was not wrong at all.

For the last million years, the world had been on the brink of destruction. And the reason for this was Limitless Demon Venerable.

Limitless Demon Venerable looked at his arm and sighed softly, replying Star Constellation Immortal Venerable: "In my previous life, I had already reached the end of the road. Even when I asked the Heavenly Dao, there was no possibility of eternal life. I was pitifully restrained by fate Gu, after searching long and hard, through laborious planning, I designed this Crazed Demon Cave. I simply had no other choice but to use this method."

"But to play safe, I involved Heavenly Court in this."

"With you guys around, even if a problem occurred in the Crazed Demon formation and the hole got larger, you would do your best to fix it."

Hearing this, how could Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's expression possibly be amicable?

She realized now that the reason why Limitless Demon Venerable drew her into the gamble was not just because he needed her wisdom path attainment or Heavenly Court's strength to derive new heaven path research results. The deeper intention was to bring in Heavenly Court's involvement as an assurance.

If Crazed Demon Cave became a problem, Heavenly Court would have to clean up after Limitless Demon Venerable.

But because of Heavenly Court's perspective, they would spare no expense in repairing it, they would be willing to do so in fact!

"But..." Limitless Demon Venerable added: "This is still not at the level of eternal life. Don't you think so too, Paradise Earth?"

Paradise Earth nodded slowly and expressionlessly.

Fang Yuan had some sort of realization, the true realm of eternal life would be complete indestructibility against the chaos. Limitless Demon Venerable had clearly not reached that stage yet.

"Just a bit more, I am lacking by just a bit." Limitless Demon Venerable continued to shake his head, sighing deeply.

He turned his gaze towards Demon Immortal Qi Jue: "Qi Jue, Qi Jue, can you lend me a hand?"

Demon Immortal Qi Jue snorted coldly: "Why must I help you?"

Limitless Demon Venerable took out practice Gu, smiling: "This Immortal Gu was prepared for you to begin with, Qi Jue, for this moment, I have already waited for you for over a million years."

Demon Immortal Qi Jue laughed loudly until tears flowed out: "So my revival was really part of your schemes. Hahaha, too laughable, simply too laughable. This is so disappointing, so disappointing!"

He was not mocking Limitless Demon Venerable, he was laughing at himself.

He had always felt resentful and unresigned after losing to Limitless Demon Venerable. After revival, he had always wanted to take revenge.

But at this moment, he finally understood the huge gap between him and Limitless Demon Venerable.

Limitless Demon Venerable was quiet as he watched Demon Immortal Qi Jue cry and laugh, afterwards, he tossed practice Gu to the latter.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue had a complex expression at this moment.

He recalled the scene of the deepest memory he had.

"Limitless, you want to become a venerable, but did you ask me? With me around, you can dream on about becoming a venerable!" Demon Immortal Qi Jue sneak attacked Limitless Demon Venerable and succeeded.

Because he knew that once Limitless became a venerable, he would no longer have a chance of winning.

This battle lasted nine days and nights.

Thereafter, Demon Immortal Qi Jue lost.

His eyes were blood red as he called out to Limitless Demon Venerable: "You have passed the tribulation long ago and became a venerable already. Why did you seal your own cultivation level to fight to the death with me?"

Limitless Demon Venerable was bathed in blood, he had struggled at death's doors several times during the intense battle.

He smiled lightly: "Because you are my Dao Guardian, only when I am at the brink of death can I understand the true relationship between a venerable and their Dao Guardian. And the truth has been proven, my guess was not wrong after all. I have already comprehended the secret behind the Dao Guardian."

Demon Immortal Qi Jue stared with wide eyes: "To prove such a guess, you even disregarded your own life? Even though you had already become a venerable, even though you are already invincible in the world?!"

Limitless Demon Venerable replied plainly: "Even though I became a venerable, this is merely another cultivation level. Compared to this, I would prefer to pursue the Great Dao."

...

"Limitless, oh Limitless. Even a million years cannot change your nature. You are still that Limitless I know!" Demon Immortal Qi Jue pointed at Demon Immortal Qi Jue and shouted.

Limitless Demon Venerable smiled: "Like how I am still Limitless, you are also still that Demon Immortal Qi Jue, right?"

Demon Immortal Qi Jue gritted his teeth, he seemed to have become too helpless to rage, he grabbed practice Gu and flew towards Limitless Demon Venerable: "You are right, I am still me. Then let's do it!"

Bright light flashed in Limitless Demon Venerable's eyes: "Good! You are my Dao Guardian, our destinies are intertwined, according to my deduction, only with the help of the Dao Guardian can a venerable go one step further, to break through the realm of venerable and attain eternal life!"

Demon Immortal Qi Jue gritted his teeth: "Then let me see what is true eternity!"

Saying so, he activated practice Gu.

The light of practice Gu enveloped Limitless Demon Venerable's entire body.

Limitless Demon Venerable's body expanded rapidly, he went from a normal person's size to a ten foot giant.

In contrast, Demon Immortal Qi Jue became weaker and weaker, his aura fell to rock bottom, he had no choice but to stop using practice Gu.

As for Limitless Demon Venerable's aura, it was completely concealed, no different from an ordinary mortal.

But anyone could tell that the current Limitless Demon Venerable had become powerful to a point which nobody could fathom. Because even against the investigative killer moves of the various immortals, he was no different than a common man.

The immortals could not see through him!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, Paradise Earth, and the others did not move, they watched in anticipation.

Even if they wanted to stop him, it would be too difficult.

Limitless Demon Venerable took in a deep breath before stretching his arm into the hole of the world boundary again.

A moment later, he pulled back his arm, it was completely intact!

Chapter 2209: Limitless' Death

Everyone was silent.

Even for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, after seeing Limitless Demon Venerable's intact arm, they fell into extreme shock.

After a Gu cultivator became an immortal, they would face earthly calamities, heavenly tribulations, grand tribulations, and myriad tribulations. After becoming rank nine, the calamities and tribulations would become even more terrifying.

Venerables faced a grand tribulation every ten years, a myriad tribulation every fifty years, and a chaotic disaster every one hundred years!

This chaotic disaster originated from the chaos outside the world boundary.

Each time it arrived, the venerable's life would be in danger, they had to use their full strength to fight for a chance of survival.

Ordinary Gu Immortals did not know this, but all the past venerables had gone through these terrifying chaotic disasters, they knew about the terror of this tribulation.

And now, Limitless Demon Venerable tested it with his own body, without even using any defensive methods, he resisted the chaos and returned unharmed!!!

This scene was a huge shock to the present venerables.

As for people like Fang Yuan who knew the details while not having experienced them personally, his shock was not as great as the venerables.

"You did it." A while later, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sighed deeply and said.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable remained silent.

"No, he hasn't. This is not true eternal life yet!" Paradise Earth suddenly spoke, he had a tone and expression of certainty.

Everyone looked towards him.

"Indeed, I have not. This is not considered eternal life." At the next moment, Limitless Demon Venerable agreed with the words as he showed an expression of dejectedness.

Next, he made a shocking move.

He opened his mouth towards the hole of the world boundary and started to suck in.

A large amount of chaos was sucked into Limitless Demon Venerable's stomach!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable watched with contracted pupils, they could not help but take in a deep breath.

If a venerable was considered a child, the chaos would be fire. earlier, when Limitless Demon Venerable placed his hand into the chaos, he was roasting his flesh with the fire. But now, he was even more daring, he was swallowing fire!

After Limitless Demon Venerable sucked in a large amount of chaos, he sat down in a cross-legged fashion.

At the same time, chaos seeped out of the hole and rushed towards his head, shoulders, and body like a flowing river.

Limitless Demon Venerable activated his killer move for the first time, an immensely strong aura burst out and shook the minds of all the immortals present.

Everyone watched silently, they knew that Limitless Demon Venerable was currently giving it a try.

This was an advancement!

He was trying to advance to the true realm of eternal life!!

Ever since he was a child, he had maintained a heart of curiosity.

He was like an innocent child who was filled with desire to explore the unknown.

He wanted to know everything, he wanted to know the truth.

He did not pursue fame or fortune, the status of a venerable did not make him feel any pride or arrogance.

He had once reached the peak of the world, the end of heaven and earth.

But he still wanted to continue moving!

Yet, there was no road ahead of him.

Thus, he planned meticulously and worked with Star Constellation, dragging the entire Gu cultivation world along with his dangerous plan of creating the Crazed Demon formation, he prepared for a million years just for this moment.

All of it was to pursue the truth!

No road remained ahead of him.

Thus, he moved his legs and exerted all his strength to step into the boundless darkness.

He wanted to carve out his own road!

This was the final push.

Limitless was doing his best!

A long time passed, but it felt like an instant.

Whoosh.

Black fire started to spew out of Limitless Demon Venerable's nose and ears.

The immortals' hearts shook.

Next, Limitless Demon Venerable opened his eyes slowly and looked at the immortals, saying plainly: "I failed."

"No! I am still around." Demon Immortal Qi Jue shouted and made his move, using all his strength to activate practice Gu.

A wave of profound light shot towards Limitless Demon Venerable's body from Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

The black fire on Limitless Demon Venerable was quickly extinguished!

Limitless Demon Venerable gained some time to rest, he laughed loudly and shook his head: "Qi Jue, you can stop now."

"How can we determine the result before putting in all our effort?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue rebuked in anger, "Are you willing to give up like this? The true eternal life... I want, I want to see it too!"

Demon Venerable sighed, a complex expression could be seen on his face: "I failed even after a million years of accumulation. Don't you get it? Eternal life — does not exist."

At the next moment.

Bam.

Limitless Demon Venerable shattered abruptly, turning back into countless fragments of truthful floating ice.

"No!!" Secret Schemer and Not Immortal screamed in unison, grieving like they had lost their loved one.

Limitless Demon Venerable failed!

Because Demon Immortal Qi Jue had too close of a connection with him, the chaos instantly approached him, as it swept past him, he vanished without a trace!

The great pseudo venerable did not even manage to last three breaths of time.

The power of the terrifying chaotic disaster was evident with one glance!

The immortals were still in a daze.

This battle in Crazed Demon Cave that took a million years of accumulation and also all the venerables' planning ended like this?

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable revived, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable also revived, Paradise Earth changed to cultivating heaven path, while Spectral Soul Demon Venerable lost his reasoning. In the end, Limitless Demon Venerable suppressed everyone in strength, but he still failed to succeed.

He died, he died on the road of exploration.

Eternal life?

It was a mere dream.

There was nothing!

It did not exist!!

"How could he fail? How could he fail!" Not Immortal shouted.

Secret Schemer held his head and muttered dejectedly: "There is no eternal life... hehe, there is no eternal life... hehe."

He had gone insane!

"Does eternal life really not exist in this world? Venerable is the limit, there is no... road ahead?" Star Constellation Immortal Venerable muttered to herself.

She had asked the question that all the immortals were wondering!

But nobody could answer it.

Limitless Demon Venerable might be the most qualified in this aspect, since he had already surpassed everyone else by a huge margin.

But he had died.

It failed.

He died from the chaotic disaster.

Using his life, it seemed like he exposed a cruel truth to the immortals.

Whoosh!

Right at this moment, the sound of wind could be heard.

Fang Yuan suddenly made his move, snatching a piece of the truthful floating ice!

The immortals were instantly jolted awake.

Limitless Demon Venerable died and turned into pieces of truthful floating ice.

Most of the truthful floating ice had been destroyed in the chaos, but a small portion remained.

The chaos... could not do anything to them!

They were the eternal life results derived by Limitless' Crazed Demon formation, they were definitely the essence of his hard work!!

Limitless Demon Venerable died, but his million years of hard work had not gone down the drain, he left behind abundant results!

Snatch them!!

There was nothing else to say, after the immortals reacted, they attacked almost at the same time.

Rumble...

A large number of killer moves were activated, colliding into each other and exploding loudly.

Heaven shook and the earth cracked!

Not Immortal and Secret Schemer did not even manage to make a sound before they died on the spot.

But the remaining pieces of the truthful floating ice were intact and still shining radiantly!

This was expected.

Even the chaotic disaster could do nothing to them, venerables and pseudo venerables were also unable to damage them with their killer moves.

Rumble...

The scene was chaotic, killer moves influenced each other as the immortals restrained one another.

"Get lost!!"

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable shouted angrily, golden light surged in the sky, exploding fiercely like a crashing tsunami, everywhere it went, nothing could stop it.

Fang Yuan and the other pseudo venerables quickly dodged.

The golden aurora light suddenly turned into a spiral that sucked in a piece of the truthful floating ice.

Seeing this, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted coldly and scattered some flying stars, hundreds or thousands of them radiated with starlight and crashed into the golden aurora, getting mutually destroyed.

As Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not succeed, the truthful floating ice that was taken by the golden aurora was free again, it floated freely in the void.

This was the largest truthful floating ice, all of the remaining truthful floating ice fragments were merely its size after being added up. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was attempting to take away half of this eternal life result that took a million years to nurture, how could that happen? Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would not allow him to succeed!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's gazes were locked onto each other.

Right at this time, Lu Wei Yin suddenly made a move, targeting the small truthful floating ice fragment that was closest to him.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not move, but starlight appeared out of nowhere, sending Lu Wei Yin flying.

At almost the same time, Fang Yuan was also stopped by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

He wanted to target the other truthful floating ices but golden light shot down like needles, almost piercing his body.

The two venerables opposed each other, but they held the same attitude towards Fang Yuan and the rest.

Be it Star Constellation Immortal Venerable or Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, they were very domineering, they did not want the truthful floating ice to end up with anyone else.

Lu Wei Yin and Fang Yuan were obstructed, at this time, the pseudo venerables had to prepare and wait for another moment to arise when the two venerables fought again.

The hole was gradually expanding.

Limitless Demon Venerable had already died. Before he died, he was able to suppress the tiny hole.

But after his death, the power he left behind was weakening, even though chaos did not seep out of the hole in the world boundary anymore, that was going to happen soon.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable took a look at the hole in the world boundary, he spoke calmly to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable: "Star Constellation, why don't we have a ceasefire again and deal with these pseudo venerables first. We can then fix the world boundary's hole and split the truthful floating ice between ourselves. How's that?"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable nodded and replied to him with her direct actions.

Immediately, starlight danced around and shot everywhere, launching fatal attacks towards Fang Yuan and the other pseudo venerables.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's killer move soon followed.

Fang Yuan and the rest had to dodge everywhere, they escaped in distress.

Limitless Demon Venerable died and the Crazed Demon formation was destroyed, without Limitless' retaliation method, the two venerables were free to attack.

Of course, they did not use their full strength, even in the current situation. The reason was that they were guarding against each other.

Even so, Fang Yuan and the rest were in dangerous situations, they were often struggling in the face of death.

"I can't continue resisting these two venerables' power. Everyone, I'm leaving first." Fang Yuan shouted and dragged Qi Sea Ancestor along, wanting to leave the ninth layer.

Paradise Earth frowned immediately.

Crazed Demon Cave only had the ninth layer left now, if Fang Yuan left, the two venerables would not have the opportunity to chase him.

Because anyone who left would be giving the other venerable a chance.

It meant giving up the snatching of the truthful floating ice!

Because next, as long as either venerable made a move to seal the ninth layer of Crazed Demon Cave, the pseudo venerables would have trouble trying to come in again after they leave.

As long as they stalled for some time, the two venerables would be able to keep away the truthful floating ice, after that, they would be able to easily deal with the pseudo venerables!

But right at this moment, the two venerables snorted coldly together.

"Others can leave, but you, Fang Yuan, cannot!"

"Please leave behind the truthful floating ice that you snatched away earlier, you cannot bring this away with you."

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable spoke one sentence each, expressing their honest attitude.

Among the Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan was the first to get a piece. Everyone else including the two venerables had not obtained anything yet.

And Fang Yuan's piece was quite big too, it was at least ten percent of the entire truthful floating ice!

At this moment, the two venerables cooperated again, dealing with Fang Yuan together.

Fang Yuan's expression changed.

Earlier, the two venerables worked together to deal with him, but the pressure now was incomparable to before.

Soon, Fang Yuan was forced to activate reverse flow protection seal again!

Reverse Flow River was nearly depleted earlier, but after it was replenished during this period of time, the river water had risen slightly in sovereign immortal aperture.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's killer moves were quickly reflected back to them.

However, for these two venerables, reverse flow protection seal was only a slight bother, it was a mere obstacle.

As long as they used skillful methods, they would be able to resolve it in some time.

Chapter 2210: Paradise Earth's Death

"Paradise Earth, I am willing to share my truthful floating ice with you. Right now, we cannot afford to leave each other in the lurch, we must be united and work together." Fang Yuan shouted.

Paradise Earth nodded: "Fang Yuan, you are right!"

Saying so, he made his move.

But he disregarded Fang Yuan, he targeted a piece of truthful floating ice.

The truthful floating ice was quickly kept in Paradise Earth's immortal aperture.

At the same time, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable targeted that largest truthful floating ice again!

As long as he obtained this, he would be the biggest winner in this Crazed Demon Cave situation. The two venerables were unable to defeat each other, if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable wanted to leave, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could not stop him.

"Don't think about it!" Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had a cold gaze.

Bam.

Killer moves collided, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable managed to repel Giant Sun Immortal Venerable again, but she could not stop Paradise Earth in time.

Heaven path method!

The heaven path method that Paradise Earth used to take the truthful floating ice was very profound, his aura was initially concealed to the limit, even the two venerables could not detect it. After activation, the move was extremely fast, even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could not stop it in time, allowing Paradise Earth to succeed!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sighed deeply, she took out that mysterious secluded domain of heaven and earth again.

This secluded domain of heaven and earth looked like a lantern, once Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used her killer move, she lifted the lantern and shined it on all the Gu Immortals.

At the next moment, a tsunami made of endless emotions surged into the immortals' hearts!

Their expressions changed abruptly, they resisted with difficulty.

Fang Yuan activated fortitude Gu while Giant Sun Immortal Venerable instilled immortal essence into familial emotion Gu, Paradise Earth activated the killer move emotionless heaven and earth instead to resolve it.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snickered, she took out Book Mountain again.

Book Mountain shined with dazzling light, all sorts of killer moves were replicated and unleashed on the Gu Immortals.

There was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's method, Qi Sea Ancestor's and Demon Immortal Qi Jue's killer moves, Paradise Earth's killer move, and even Limitless Demon Venerable's method!

At this moment, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable finally unleashed her full strength, using the two killer moves with these two secluded domains of heaven and earth as the cores to suppress everyone that was currently present.

Her expression paled immediately, the starlight specks around her dimmed, she had consumed over ten billion thoughts to do this, they were nearly fully expended.

Using this time, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable activated Book Mountain, Limitless' chains flew out to grab the truthful floating ice and send it into her immortal aperture.

This truthful floating ice was not the biggest one, but it contained an Immortal Gu!

Nobody noticed this Immortal Gu except Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Precisely because of it, she was willing to temporarily give up the largest truthful floating ice piece and grabbed this smaller piece first.

After collecting the Immortal Gu, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable immediately stopped her killer move, she stored away Book Mountain and focused on defense.

Her action was very wise.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could no longer control himself.

At the next moment, he shouted loudly, golden light shot out fiercely with his retaliation.

Attacks rained down harshly, forcing Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to retreat continuously, she was like a helpless floating duckweed in the storm.

Using this opportunity, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable took a piece of the truthful floating ice as well.

This was not the largest truthful floating ice piece, but it was the one closest to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Because he knew that he could only suppress Star Constellation Immortal Venerable for a few breaths of time, there was no time to take the largest truthful floating ice!

As expected, at the next moment, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable recovered and attacked Giant Sun Immortal Venerable again.

The two venerables fought intensely, because they were using their full strength while trying to get the truthful floating ice pieces, they did not have the time or energy to spend on other matters. This gave the pseudo venerables a good chance.

Fang Yuan and Paradise Earth took three or four pieces each.

Lu Wei Yin, Shen Shang, and Qi Sea also obtained one or two pieces.

Not long after, the truthful floating ice fragments were all taken except for that final largest piece!

The two venerables had considerable injuries now, their attempts to take it were all thwarted by the other party.

The two venerables raced against time, attacking the pseudo venerables again.

This time, they fought with more motivation. After all, the pseudo venerables all had some truthful floating ice pieces on them.

"Oh?" While the two venerables suppressed the pseudo venerables, they started to feel a little surprised.

Because Paradise Earth was displaying greater battle strength than before!

Almost every breath of time, his strength grew by some extent, his aura was already inching closer to the level of a rank nine venerable now.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's eyes shined with bright light: "So that's it. Paradise Earth, because you converted to cultivating heaven path, and because this truthful floating ice is closely related to heaven path, you can draw strength from it to raise your cultivation level, this is a brilliant method!"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable spoke with a tone of admiration, but her killing intent surged correspondingly as well.

Earlier, when Fang Yuan asked for help, Paradise Earth ignored him to snatch that truthful floating ice, so this was the reason!

Evidently, as long as he could get sufficient truthful floating ice pieces, Paradise Earth would be able to alleviate the flaw of being prematurely revived and become a venerable again.

And this time, he would not be an earth path venerable, but most uniquely, a heaven path venerable!

Once Paradise Earth became a heaven path venerable, his strength would likely rise up to the top of the world.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable were not going to sit around and watch this happen.

Fate Gu had been destroyed, the entire world was pretty much ruled by them. Nobody would want to see the return of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, especially when this Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable would have far greater strength than them!

There was no communication, the two venerables worked together for the third time.

This time, they gave up on Fang Yuan, focusing on Paradise Earth instead.

Paradise Earth activated heaven path killer moves consecutively to block the two venerables' attacks, but soon, he showed signs of being unable to continue.

Even though the heaven path methods were vast and profound, the two venerables had greater strength now.

Paradise Earth fell into a life-and-death crisis, he shouted at the rest: "Please lend me a hand!"

Lu Wei Yin and Shen Shang hesitated for a moment before tossing their truthful floating ice pieces into treasure yellow heaven at almost the same time.

Paradise Earth took the truthful floating ices from treasure yellow heaven and quickly used them to raise his cultivation level.

His aura grew once more, he was only inches away from reaching venerable level.

"I am only one step away, Fang Yuan!" Paradise Earth transmitted urgently.

Fang Yuan snickered: "I can give you the truthful floating ice, but Paradise Earth, can you pay a sufficient price that will satisfy me?"

Paradise Earth gritted his teeth, he immediately sent the Northern Plains Paradise Earth true inheritance into treasure yellow heaven, along with all sorts of heaven path killer moves and his own heaven path cultivation experiences.

Of course, the most important thing was the alliance agreement.

To get the most crucial truthful floating ice, Paradise Earth made a huge concession!

Fang Yuan placed a small piece of the truthful floating ice into treasure yellow heaven, the two quickly made the transaction.

"Haha, Paradise Earth, you can have the final truthful floating ice pieces too!" After the transaction was done, Fang Yuan shouted loudly.

Paradise Earth's heart shook.

Indeed, at the next moment, both venerables erupted with killer moves surrounding Paradise Earth, barraging him with attacks!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable raised the lantern high up, endless emotions assaulted his heart.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable grabbed with his hands continuously, attacking Paradise Earth's luck.

Paradise Earth was covered in terrifying injuries, he was like a mortal hanging on a cliff, moments away from dying.

Shen Shang, Lu Wei Yin, and even Fang Yuan and Qi Sea Ancestor attacked from afar, using killer moves to try to help out Paradise Earth.

But it was no use!

Paradise Earth gritted his teeth, struggling desperately. The truthful floating ice melted gradually, helping him to push to the level of a venerable once again!

But at the crucial moment, Paradise Earth's killer move had a peculiar mistake.

The killer move failed and the backlash triggered, Paradise Earth's cultivation level was stuck at the final step.

The two venerables' attacks arrived and instantly engulfed Paradise Earth.

"Quickly save him!" Lu Wei Yin shouted and was the first to move.

The other pseudo venerables' hearts jumped too as they took action.

The two venerables were not willing to see Paradise Earth getting saved, they chased after him too.

The pseudo venerables used all their strengths and disregarded their own danger, managing to block Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's attacks with great difficulty.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's starlight still hit Paradise Earth's body.

Paradise Earth shouted loudly, veins bulged on his face as he used all his strength to activate a killer move.

With his defensive killer move broken, his body became covered in countless holes that were ravaged by the starlight, but his healing method was still effective, Paradise Earth was forcefully holding onto his last breath.

At this time, Qi Sea made a move, shielding Fang Yuan, who quickly got closer to Paradise Earth's side.

"Fang Yuan!" Lu Wei Yin and Shen Shang jolted, the light of hope shined in their eyes.

The two venerables' expressions sank slightly.

Right as Fang Yuan was about to save Paradise Earth...

Boom!

Fang Yuan's palm slammed onto Paradise Earth's back and penetrated his chest.

Paradise Earth was already at his last breath, Fang Yuan's attack was the fatal blow that he could not endure.

At the moment before his death, Paradise Earth's eyes stared wide as he grabbed Fang Yuan's hand.

"Paradise Earth, rest in peace." Fang Yuan smiled lightly.

At the next moment, Paradise Earth's dwindling aura dissipated entirely.

He died with eyes wide open!

The entire scene shook.

The two venerables looked at Fang Yuan with peculiar expressions.

Lu Wei Yin's lips were trembling, he broke the silence and shouted in a hoarse voice: "Fang Yuan, what have you done?!"

"Fang Yuan, this..." Shen Shang's eyeballs were almost going to pop out.

Qi Sea Ancestor stopped beside Fang Yuan's main body, showing a strange expression as well.

Everyone knew that in this situation with two unrivaled venerables, Paradise Earth was their only hope of resisting them. But the one who killed this hope was not the two venerables, but Fang Yuan himself!

Was Fang Yuan crazy?

He actually did something like this!

It was too absurd.

"Something's not right." Giant Sun Immortal Venerable muttered to himself.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable frowned slightly as well but did not speak.

The two venerables saw that Fang Yuan was keeping away Paradise Earth's corpse into sovereign immortal aperture so calmly, they sensed a slight change in the atmosphere.

"Fang Yuan, how are we going to get out of this?" Shen Shang asked anxiously.

"Without Lord Paradise Earth, how can we resist the two venerables?!" Lu Wei Yin was stomping his feet and staring at Fang Yuan angrily.

Fang Yuan smiled plainly: "It is simple, wouldn't it be fine if I am a venerable?"

Saying so, he no longer concealed his aura, exposing it at this moment.

Rank nine cultivation level!

At once, the entire battlefield went silent.

"Mere tricks." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted coldly, starlight flowed like water as it surged towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan breathed out lightly, a qi tide poured out and blocked all the starlight.

At the other end, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable also tried to probe, golden needles shot down like a torrential rain.

Fang Yuan waved his hand, red aurora filled the sky, incinerating all of the golden needles.

The pupils of the two venerables shrank.

Lu Wei Yin, Shen Shang, and even Fang Yuan's clone, Qi Sea Ancestor, were tongue-tied.

Even against the attacks of the two venerables, Fang Yuan blocked them perfectly, he displayed genuine rank nine cultivation level!

Did he really become a venerable?!

Chapter 2211: Fang Yuan Becomes Venerable!

Rumble...

Fang Yuan's killer moves shot out, forcing Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to retreat.

"What in the world is going on?"

"Since when did Fang Yuan become a venerable?!"

Lu Wei Yin and Shen Shang watched as Fang Yuan fought the two venerables, they had complex emotions and asked Qi Sea Ancestor urgently.

Qi Sea Ancestor was also confused, he smiled bitterly: "I had no clue either."

Lu Wei Yin and Shen Shang were speechless, Fang Yuan had hid this so deeply that he even deceived his own clone!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable remained silent.

Because they found that Fang Yuan's strength had vaguely surpassed either of them!

He was still a rank eight pseudo venerable earlier, how did he turn into a genuine rank nine so suddenly?!

The two venerables were very confused and suspicious.

"Strange, strange, very strange!" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable attacked fiercely, golden light rained down with imposing might.

Fang Yuan responded with a shout, his prepared method was activated, forcefully suppressing the overwhelming golden light.

"The dao marks on his body far surpass Giant Sun Immortal Venerable!" Seeing this, Lu Wei Yin and the rest felt their hearts jumping.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable took in a deep breath of cold air secretly, he focused his eyes and activated a method.

At the next moment, his vision changed, he started to observe the luck above Fang Yuan's head.

Initially, Fang Yuan's luck was completely hidden, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could only see Cooking Luck Pot.

But soon, after Giant Sun Immortal Venerable intensified the force of this move and golden blood flowed out of his eyes, he finally got through Cooking Luck Pot's defense and saw Fang Yuan's true luck.

He saw a silver pillar of light that connected heaven and earth, it was grand and condensed.

At the base of the silvery pillar, there was a brown grave, it had mostly dissipated now, only a small part was left.

Seeing this, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had a thought, he sighed to himself: "This is Paradise Earth's luck, on one hand, it can stabilize the foundation of the silver light pillar, but on the other hand, it is also digging away and replacing Fang Yuan's foundation. It was the biggest threat to Fang Yuan's luck initially, now that he killed Paradise Earth, this threat has been removed! This remaining part of the grave is the foundation of Paradise Earth that Fang Yuan has yet to devour completely."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable raised his head again, looking at the top of the silver light pillar.

Earlier when they joined forces, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had observed Fang Yuan's luck. Compared to then, Fang Yuan's silver light pillar was no longer blocked by three clouds at the top.

It shot right through them, truly looking like it was holding up the heavens and supporting the earth!

The three clouds could only revolve around the top part of the silver pillar.

This meant that the three venerables could no longer hold Fang Yuan down.

Among the three clouds, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's cloud had turned into a golden-blood colored cloud, it was at the top. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's and Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's clouds were below his, they seemed to have the trend of tearing apart.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was moved again: "Is this hinting that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable is quickly breaking free from Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's control?"

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was not surprised.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was someone on the same level as Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, it was already an incredibly shocking achievement that she could control him. But it was unrealistic to try fully controlling a venerable.

"If Spectral Soul Demon Venerable escapes from Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's control later, what will happen?"

"No matter what, in terms of luck alone, Fang Yuan has truly become a venerable!"

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable believed in his own luck path methods, he was finally convinced at this moment.

At this time, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable looked towards Fang Yuan with some rage in his eyes.

How did Fang Yuan become a venerable in the blink of an eye?

Looking at his expression and attitude, it seemed like he held indifference towards rank nine cultivation level, what did he take this venerable status as?

If rank nine venerables could appear so easily, then what would Giant Sun Immortal Venerable amount to?

What would the past venerables amount to?

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was also considering rapidly: "Fang Yuan has rank nine cultivation level indeed. I underestimated his craftiness and shrewdness! When did he become a venerable? Did he have this cultivation level from the start? All the signs do not point to that possibility. He had secretly become a venerable during a certain moment in the Crazed Demon Cave battle. But... he clearly lacked attainment level."

In the contest in Primordial Domain, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable ganged up on Fang Yuan and destroyed the refinement path portion of the Primordial Domain.

"Wait!" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable suddenly turned his head, retreating as he looked at Fang Yuan, asking: "Did the Thieving Heaven true inheritance contain refinement path true meaning? So you had the necessary refinement path attainment level long ago."

Fang Yuan smiled, but his attacks became even fiercer.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was sent flying by consecutive attacks.

Using this timing, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable shot out countless flying stars that flew like lightning, landing on Fang Yuan's back one after another.

Fang Yuan staggered from the hit, he almost lost his balance and fell forward.

But immediately after, he straightened his back and wiped it with his hand.

Starlight specks were shining intensely on his back, they were the dao marks left behind by the flying stars.

But after Fang Yuan wiped them, all of these dao marks were refined into his own!

The power of rank nine refinement path!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's heart jumped.

It was terrible to her that Fang Yuan had such a method. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's combat system did not excel in powerful individual offensive methods, she mainly relied on consecutive hits. And the key to these consecutive hits were the dao marks that the flying stars left behind.

With these dao marks, the following flying stars would be able to deal increasingly greater damage to the enemy.

But Fang Yuan refined these dao marks into his own, the flying star consecutive move was easily broken.

If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable continued to use this move, she would not be fighting Fang Yuan but funding him instead!

Fang Yuan easily got rid of the flying star consecutive move and launched his own counterattack.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could not deal with him head on, she had to temporarily retreat.

"He is very proficient with this refinement path killer move, it shows that Fang Yuan came prepared. But he held back the entire time, waiting for the final moment of this Crazed Demon Cave fight and after he became rank nine to utilize this trump card!"

At this moment, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable finally understood the true extent of Fang Yuan's craftiness.

The killer move was prepared long ago, otherwise, it could not be used so quickly after Fang Yuan became rank nine. If he used it earlier, the effect would be great too, but he refused to activate it, causing Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to assume that he was helpless against the flying star killer move.

At the final battle, he used it and caught Star Constellation Immortal Venerable off guard immediately.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable suddenly had a flash of inspiration, she realized a portion of the truth at this moment as she spoke: "Fang Yuan, well done, you purposely did that during the Primordial Domain contest. You purposely held back and gave up on competing for Primordial Domain, thus Giant Sun and I destroyed the refinement path part of the Primordial Domain. You were purposely pretending to be weak so that we would look down on and put less attention on you!"

Hearing these words, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's heart lit up, he could not help but feel more anger towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan remained smiling as he said plainly: "Star Constellation, you are thinking too highly of me."

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled coldly: "Fang Yuan, don't think of deceiving us anymore. Regardless of whether Thieving Heaven's true inheritance had refinement path true meaning, before you entered Primordial Domain, you were already extremely close to supreme grandmaster attainment level. After entering Primordial Domain, you realized that even if you gave up a portion of the refinement path Primordial Domain, you could still become a refinement path supreme grandmaster by yourself."

"Thus, you purposely held back and let Giant Sun and I seemingly ruin your chances of becoming a venerable."

"There were many benefits in this."

"Firstly, becoming a venerable would mean breaking through the Heavenly Dao blockade, you would need to undergo tribulation and it carries many risks, you have to find the right timing to do so. Once you become a supreme grandmaster openly, we would be on guard against you."

"Secondly, even if you became a venerable quickly, before the three worlds united, Limitless' eternal life result was still far away from us, everyone needed to wait. Furthermore, because of Limitless' retaliation, even if you became a venerable, you could not use your strength."

"Thirdly, if you were not a venerable, we would subconsciously ignore you. In our minds, even if Paradise Earth was just a pseudo venerable, he was still more threatening than you."

"Finally, everyone was holding back during the Crazed Demon Cave battle, a lot of trump cards were not revealed. For example, you did not know how much I had infiltrated the Crazed Demon formation. Thus, you concealed your methods and waited for the situation to become clearer, after we went through our methods, before trying to claim victory!"

While defending against Fang Yuan's attacks, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable analyzed and exposed Fang Yuan's schemes to everyone.

Be they Giant Sun Immortal Venerable or Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, they did not want a third venerable contesting with them.

Paradise Earth was the best example.

He was trying to become a venerable under the attention of the two venerables, in the end, he got heavily injured because of them.

As Giant Sun Immortal Venerable listened to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's explanation, his mind became increasingly clear.

With a loud howling sound, he stepped on a giant golden aurora and charged at Fang Yuan.

At the same time, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also pincer attacked Fang Yuan from another direction.

Chapter 2212: Refine Gu, Refine Human, and Refine Heaven!!

Seeing the fierce attacks of the enemies, Fang Yuan quickly dodged for the time being.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable pursued relentlessly as he shouted: "Back then, when I fought my way into the Door of Life and Death, I wanted to probe Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's trump card and learn of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's current condition. But you also went inside, it was truly a great scheme! If you remained in the outside world, you would need to deal with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, who went out. But if you followed me, you would be able to see the strength of Heavenly Court and my Longevity Heaven."

At that time, because of Heavenly Court's arrangements, the Door of Life and Death was tightly connected to the immortal graveyard, it could not be destroyed forcefully in a short period of time.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable secretly inspected their lucks, after learning of this peculiar change in Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's and Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's lucks, he wanted to find out the reason. If possible, he wanted to ruin this 'intimate relationship' between them.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable knew that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had hidden cards too, but he went inside the Door of Life and Death regardless.

Because he had his own trump cards.

When he used the blood path method to revive, no matter how severe his injuries got, he would be fully healed.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had been trying to make the best use of this trump card, he tried all ways possible to probe more of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's methods.

From Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's perspective, this was the first time he was fighting against a venerable.

Venerables had immense foundation, he needed to probe carefully.

To destroy the immortal graveyard, he had to target the Door of Life and Death. By going inside, he could inspect if there was really a relationship between Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. If possible, he would destroy that connection and save Spectral Soul Demon Venerable before working together. Or if possible, he could even try to take the Door of Life and Death for himself!

With all these intentions, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable managed to find out Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's method involving emotions on this trip.

When Star Constellation Immortal Venerable left the Door of Life and Death, did Giant Sun Immortal Venerable really not have any way of stopping her?

That was not the case.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was happy to see Star Constellation Immortal Venerable leave.

Firstly, the eternal life result still needed some time to nurture, he had already left behind his investigative method in the Crazed Demon formation, that was Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

Secondly, three parties were contesting in Crazed Demon Cave then, other than Green Lotus Great World's Heavenly Court, and Savage Wilderness Great World's Longevity Heaven, there was also Yellow Earth Great World's Paradise Earth.

In the end, through this contest, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable forced Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable to revive prematurely, causing him to only have pseudo venerable cultivation level.

When Paradise Earth went into the Door of Life and Death, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not use his biggest trump card before leaving. Even though he did not save Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, he managed to ally with Paradise Earth.

Boom!

As Fang Yuan retaliated, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's killer move was broken, he was forced back again.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable yelled: "Fang Yuan, I am sure you wanted to see Paradise Earth's premature resurrection as well. Such great acting, truly great acting skills! After leaving the Door of Life and Death, I was hit by Qin Ding Ling's method and fell into a disadvantage. I needed you to take action but you were trapped by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. That was your intentional excuse! You purposely made the Qi Sea clone activate Hu elevation, that way, the Qi Sea clone would be restrained again, while Zhan Bu Du was unable to get away. You managed to watch openly as our two sides fought and expended each other's strength!"

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable said while gritting his teeth.

Back then, he still had an immortal zombie body, he was suppressed by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and schemed against by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, his combat system's foundation was uprooted. Even though the situation was dangerous, Giant Sun was not flustered.

Because he still had the greatest trump card unused!

Giant Sun held back and waited because he wanted to see the trump cards of these other people.

In the end, Paradise Earth made his move.

Paradise Earth did not attack Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, instead, he tried to help Giant Sun, after failing, he immediately saved Fang Yuan.

This showed that Paradise Earth's intentions were not simple either.

However, after Fang Yuan was 'saved', he still refused to help out Giant Sun, instead, he went to kill the unimportant Qin Ding Ling.

This way, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had no choice but to use his blood path trump card, reviving completely.

Fang Yuan succeeded in killing Qin Ding Ling, but how could he deceive Giant Sun Immortal Venerable with such superficial actions.

Giant Sun was very clear of it in his heart, since he exposed his true strength, he immediately changed his position and joined up with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to deal with Fang Yuan.

Because of this, Fang Yuan was attacked by two venerables, he had to expend Reverse Flow River, but still got hit in the end, his immortal aperture suffered calamities and tribulations.

"Wait!" Thinking of this, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable realized and called out: "During that time, you used the opportunity of your immortal aperture getting hit to obscure the aura and use the chance to break through the Heavenly Dao blockade, by stacking tribulation with tribulation, you deceived everyone and got past the final tribulation, becoming a venerable!"

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable finally understood everything.

Back then, he thought that he had succeeded when he inspected Fang Yuan's falling luck and the aura of calamities and tribulations in his aperture. But to think that Fang Yuan was making use of this to secretly tackle the Heavenly Dao blockade and break through an even stronger tribulation.

With just Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's method, he could definitely not create black fire in Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture.

The black fire was the remnant product of the chaotic disaster.

Fang Yuan did not speak, he attacked fiercely, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable resisted with difficulty.

He stared at Fang Yuan and continued to speak: "Through that method, you became a venerable without anyone noticing. I originally thought that you were not skilled in aura concealment methods, but to think that your attainment in this aspect is shocking, you have been concealing your aura the entire time! You actually deceived me, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, and wait, even Paradise Earth was deceived!"

Fang Yuan was the greatest liar, he lied until the very end. All of these venerables were toyed around by him!

Lu Wei Yin and Shen Shang looked at each other, feeling the shock in each other's hearts.

The fight between the venerables was getting more intense, they started using their full strength, causing the rest to be pushed away to the boundaries of the void, along with the Qi Sea clone.

Looking at Fang Yuan who was holding the upper hand, Lu Wei Yin and Shen Shang had complex emotions.

On one hand, they were shocked and in admiration that Fang Yuan broke through successfully to become a venerable, he was even suppressing two noble existences who were famous in history. But on the other hand, Lu Wei Yin and Shen Shang were furious.

They had a close connection to Paradise Earth, while a large part of his death was attributed to Fang Yuan's scheme.

In the end, Paradise Earth had no choice but to expose his great secret — he could absorb truthful floating ice to raise his cultivation level!

Fang Yuan purposely made a transaction with Paradise Earth and shouted so loudly, triggering the two venerables to use their full strength on him.

In the end, the attacks of the two venerables helped out Fang Yuan, he managed to kill Paradise Earth.

Crafty, scheming, evil!

Such words revolved around the hearts of Lu Wei Yin and Shen Shang, they could not help but describe Fang Yuan as such.

Rumble...

As the golden light faded and starlight dimmed, Fang Yuan was incredibly domineering, his aura was surging like a rising tiger over ten thousand li.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable were feeling bitter internally.

After so long, they had already expended many of their trump cards in combat. Their injuries were still lingering, there was simply no time to heal them.

In contrast, Fang Yuan had been staying low-profile and hiding his strength, his schemes were simply too deep.

Boom!

The three venerables clashed again.

Fang Yuan held the upper hand once more.

The two venerables were forced back, they spat out blood together, their injuries becoming more severe.

Fang Yuan wore a snow-white robe, his hair was long and fluttering, he dominated the battlefield, with his aura surmounting mountains and rivers.

He firmly grasped the upper hand as he suddenly recited —

In my youth I knew the hardships of the world,

Yet I still aspired to soar above the clouds.

A journey of cold winds and uncertainty,

A lone traveler experiences a life of ups and downs.

A heart of steel forged from countless setbacks,

A lifetime of effort to forge one sword.

Today my sword aims beyond the clouds,

Refine Gu! Refine Human! Refine Heaven!!

Fang Yuan's attacks were like a surging tide, enveloping all the surrounding battlefield, approaching from all directions of the world.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could not resist them, they retreated time and time again.

Fang Yuan grabbed with his hand, the final truthful floating ice went towards him.

"Don't think about it!" Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted coldly, she had to toss out the Door of Life and Death at the final crucial moment.

The Door of Life and Death erupted with an immense suction force, while Giant Sun Immortal Venerable attacked at the same time, his killer move landing on Fang Yuan.

In order to take the truthful floating ice, Fang Yuan exposed a weakness and was sent into the Door of Life and Death by the two venerables.

"Our tactic succeeded!" The two venerables looked at each other, having expressions of joy flashing at the same time.

But at the next moment...

Dang Hun Mountain, Luo Po Valley, and Reverse Flow River!

A killer move with all three secluded domains of heaven and earth as the cores was activated by Fang Yuan.

A road of life was suddenly formed, extending out of the Door of Life and Death.

Fang Yuan instantly returned to the battlefield, leaving Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, who was extremely furious and agitated behind in the Door of Life and Death.

The two venerables stared with wide eyes!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's eyelids were twitching intensely, this was the move that he wanted Fang Yuan to conceptualize when he was trapped in the Door of Life and Death. Fang Yuan kept delaying it and showed an expression of helplessness, eventually failing in his deduction. But now, seeing that Fang Yuan was using it so proficiently, it was clear that he had already practiced it many times.

Before the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Fang Yuan already had this killer move!

But he still used Dang Hun Luo Po Seal to make an excuse for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and the rest.

Seeing that the Door of Life and Death could not trap Fang Yuan, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable let out a soft sigh.

At the next moment, the Door of Life and Death opened, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable flew out immediately!

He was still in an agitated state, his mind was not clear, he did not attack Star Constellation Immortal Venerable but furiously targeted Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Fang Yuan.

Using this chance, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable wanted to snatch the truthful floating ice.

The scene became very chaotic.

Immortal killer move — Dang Hun Luo Po Seal!

With one attack by Fang Yuan, a thousand of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's arms severed.

After Fang Yuan became venerable and passed the black fire tribulation, his dao marks had already exceeded Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!

Fang Yuan roared and made a push, eventually taking that final truthful floating ice for himself.

"Star Constellation, I've already done my best." From within Spectral Soul's belly, Verdant Great Sun's voice could be heard sighing.

Next, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's expression changed, becoming blank. His roaring and emotions of hatred vanished, he ignored Fang Yuan and Giant Sun as he charged towards the hole expressionlessly.

Bam.

With a loud sound, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had actually used his own body to block the hole of the world boundary.

The immortals were shocked, the entire scene became silent again.